<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7307299" lastUpdate="Tuesday, December 20, 2016 at 6:19:56pm GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7307299.F" expirationDate="Tuesday, December 20, 2016 at 9:00:00am GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of LLOY.L M&A conference call or presentation 20-Dec-16 9:00am GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[Lloyds Banking Group PLC To Acquire MBNA Ltd From Bank of America Call

CHARLOTTE Dec 20, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of Lloyds Banking Group PLC M&A conference call or presentation Tuesday, December 20, 2016 at 9:00:00am GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Antonio Horta-Osorio
      Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive
   *  George Culmer
      Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Chintan Joshi
      Mediobanca - Analyst
   *  Andrew Coombs
      Citigroup - Analyst
   *  Rohith Chandra-Rajan
      Barclays Capital - Analyst
   *  Joseph Dickerson
      Jefferies LLC - Analyst
   *  Tom Rayner
      Exane BNP Paribas - Analyst
   *  Chris Manners
      Morgan Stanley - Analyst
   *  Chris Cant
      Autonomous Research - Analyst
   *  Jason Napier
      UBS - Analyst
   *  Peter Toeman
      HSBC - Analyst
   *  David Lock
      Deutsche Bank - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 A very good morning, ladies and gentlemen, and welcome to the Lloyds Banking Group acquisition of MBNA. It is hosted by Antonio Horta-Osorio and George Culmer. (Operator Instructions). We'd also like to advise all parties this conference is being recorded.
 And now I would like to hand over to your host for today, Antonio Horta-Osorio. Please go ahead.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning, everybody, and thank you for joining the call today at short notice. As you will have seen from our release this morning, Lloyds has agreed to acquire the MBNA UK credit card business from Bank of America, our first significant acquisition since the financial crisis. I will provide a very brief overview of the transaction and George will cover the financial aspects in more detail. We will then have some time for questions at the end.
 Turning to slide 1, for those of you following the website presentation. We have agreed to acquire MBNA's prime credit card book for a consideration of GBP1.9 billion, with the transaction being fully funded through our strong, organic CET1 capital generation. The MBNA portfolio is a low-risk book with strong asset quality, consistent with our own credit card book and our existing risk appetite.
 As I have always indicated, we would only consider transactions that are in the best interests of shareholders. This acquisition is in line with our strategic growth ambitions in consumer finance, is expected to provide strong financial returns, and create significant shareholder value, while not exposing the Group to any future [post] potential MBNA PPI claims.
 We expect the transaction to complete in the first half of 2017, but it remains subject to the usual competition and regulatory approvals.
 Turning now to look at the rationale in a little more detail. MBNA is one of the UK's leading prime credit card providers, with GBP7 billion of assets and around 2.8 million customers. It is strong and profitable, with a prudent risk appetite and customer-focused culture. This transaction will allow the Group to create and best-in-class UK credit card business, with a combined balance sheet of approximately GBP16 billion.
 MBNA's diversified distribution model, along with its data analytics capability, digital strength, and well-recognized brand, will be complementary to the Group's existing multi-brand and multi-channel business model, and provides further opportunities for growth and for delivering excellent customer service. The financial rationale for this acquisition is strong, with underlying return on investment and statutory earnings per share; accretion increasing to 17% and 5%, respectively, in the second full year after acquisition.
 As you know, our simple, low-cost business model provides significant competitive advantage. Leveraging our existing cost management capabilities with our track record of delivering integration programs gives us the confidence that we can deliver cost synergies of around GBP100 million per annum, equivalent to around 30% of MBNA's 2015 cost base.
 This acquisition underscores our confidence in the long-term economic prospects for the UK. It will enable us to operate more effectively in the expanding UK prime credit card market, and advances our strategic aim to deliver sustainable growth as a UK-focused retail and commercial bank.
 I will now hand over to George who will cover the details of the transaction.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Antonio, and good morning, everyone. As Antonio mentioned, the MBNA portfolio is a low-risk, customer-focused business with strong digital capabilities; and when combined with our existing cards proposition, creates a best-in-class credit card business.
 MBNA has a high-quality prime customer base. There's no subprime nor credit repair cards within their books. The new business quality is in line with our own, and the back book's strong asset quality is consistent with our risk appetite. And even under severe stress, such as, for example, the 2016 PRA stress scenario, with unemployment peaking at 9.5%, the MBNA book remains profitable over the plan period.
 In terms of conduct liabilities, our exposure to future potential MBNA PPI is explicitly capped, with the purchase price already assuming provision for such claims. And consistent with our multi-bank strategy, MBNA will be maintained as a challenger brand, complementing our existing high street brands; and our current customer-led, multi-channel proposition will be enhanced through the digital strength and analytical capabilities of MBNA.
 As you know, growing our consumer finance business is a strategic ambition that we shared with the market back in our 2014 strategic update. And since then we've been organically increasing our net lending to this key customer segment. In credit cards, balances were up by 5% year on year as at September 2016, and we currently have a 15% share of the market.
 The acquisition of MBNA enhances our customer offering and creates a combined business with a market share of approximately 26%. This positions the Group well in a profitable and growing sector and provides a further diversification of earnings.
 As Antonio has also indicated, this transaction is expected to provide strong financial returns and create significant shareholder value. Group revenues will increase by approximately GBP650 million per annum, and the net interest margin will improve by around 10 basis points on an annual basis. There will also be the potential for revenue synergies, although these are not included in our current financials.
 From a cost perspective, the synergy opportunities are significant, particularly given the Group's existing cost advantages and our proven cost management capability. We're confident in delivering run rate savings of around GBP100 million per annum within two years, equivalent to around 30% of MBNA's 2015 cost base.
 These synergies will be achieved through the consolidation of IT infrastructure, marketing, property consolidation, and operational efficiencies. The cost to achieve these synergies is expected to be around GBP200 million, and will be taken below the line over two years, with around two-thirds being taken during 2017.
 As previously mentioned, the deal delivered strong financials, and we expect this acquisition to deliver Group statutory earnings per share accretion of 3% in the first full calendar year, and 5% in the second. And the underlying return on investment is expected to exceed the Group's cost of equity in the first full calendar year, again following acquisition, and increase to 17% in the second. And given the strength of these returns, the acquisition multiples are also attractive, with consideration equation to around 6 times price to earnings ratio and 2.3 times book value.
 Finally, as mentioned, this transaction is being funded through the utilization of the Group's strong, organic CET1 capital generation. The acquisition is expected to utilize approximately 80 basis points of CET1 on completion in 2017, and this transaction will further enhance the Group's future earnings and capital generation. As a Group, we continue to deliver strong underlying and statutory performance and continue to expect to deliver around 160 basis points of CET1 capital in 2016, pre-dividend.
 And the Group's dividend policy remains unchanged, and we're confident in delivering a progressive and sustainable ordinary dividend in 2016, and continue to target a payout ratio of at least 50% of sustainable earnings over the medium-term. In line with our policy, the Group's approach to surplus capital distribution at the end of the year will give due consideration to the Board's view of the current level of capital required to meet regulatory requirements, cover uncertainties, and grow the business, which will include the capital impact of this transaction.
 In terms of capital requirements, we still believe that around 13% is the right CET capital requirement for the Group; and in line with our existing guidance of around 12% plus an amount broadly equivalent to a further year's ordinary dividend.
 This transaction represents a significant milestone in the Group's progress, with the work done to build a strong balance sheet and a capital-generative business model now providing us with the ability to execute this transaction.
 And that concludes today's presentation. And we'll now open the call to questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions). Chintan Joshi, Mediobanca.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chintan Joshi,  Mediobanca - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Two areas of questions. First one is (inaudible) dividends. How would you help us think about the dividends now? If I look at slide 6, it suggests a 14.6% CET1, pre-dividends. Take out the 80 basis points for this acquisition; that gets you to 13.8%. And if I think about last year, you paid about 12.8% CET1. That suggests you can pay out more 3.1 [pre-ops] dividends this year, but I'm not quite sure if that's the right way to think about it. And then I have a few other follow-ups on the MBNA performance.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 What was the second question, Chintan, sorry?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chintan Joshi,  Mediobanca - Analyst   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The second one was -- I just have a few on the performance of MBNA. I can see revenues down from GBP700 million in 2015 to your guidance of GBP650 million revenues this year, which suggests revenue headwinds. However, the part on my calculations, adjusting for Visa gains and PPI, seems to be slack if I annualize the first-half 2016 part. So, just trying to think about what are the headwinds to revenues here. What is the cost of risk running at in the first half? And then the operational performance in the first half of 2016 for MBNA.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Well, I'll do that second one first, and then I'll come back to dividends. In terms of the MBNA performance, the key is it's been strong, and it remains strong. Now, comparison with prior years and some of the numbers that we have to disclose is tough, because you're moving from things like US GAAP to UK statutory. We've also got different capital structures. And this is a part of the issue when you look at trends in terms of earnings. So, the capital structure they've got has got a significant amount of capital that will actually be dividended out, prior to us acquiring the business.
 And similarly, I think we disclosed -- for example, hidden in a little footnote on the front page are post-tax profits of about [166], which is what we're required to disclose. But within that you have not just the business that we're acquiring, which is the continuing, but you've also got a discontinued business which we are not acquiring which drives that number. The most pertinent number to look at -- we actually disclose about GBP125 million, GBP123 million for the after-tax for the six months. And that's on a pro forma equity position, and that's the businesses that we will be acquiring.
 So that's about a GBP250 million after-tax business that, pre- any synergies and stuff, we will be acquiring for GBP1.9 billion, which we think makes a strong financial case; and obviously as Antonio said, even stronger, post- the synergies that you push through that.
 In terms of the headwinds, we are buying a high-quality book with a prime offering that has a profile and a credit performance that is very similar to the book that we've been growing, and we will continue to grow this business.
 When you look at our current AQRs, for example, our book is roundabout 1.5% exception. We've assumed a slight deterioration for that. We've stressed it, as we said in the presentation; but this will continue to be very profitable business and will continue to generate earnings, and we will continue to look to grow that business.
 So, within that, and as I said, part of that we'd expect, having spent capital in this business, to come back to your first question, we do expect this business will be capital -- will be earnings generative, will be earnings accretive, and will be capital generative as we move forward.
 In terms of the short term in dividends, nothing has changed. As we said in the presentation, nothing has changed from our policy in terms of our confidence in our ordinary dividend and growing that ordinary dividend, which we spoke about in the half year, the Q3, and I would repeat again.
 In terms of approach to any surplus, again, in line with our policies, the Board will discuss that and make consideration of that at the year end, [while there are] considerable internal and external factors, regulatory uncertainties. So absolutely nothing has changed.
 As part of that, this MBNA deal, which will close and 2017, will be part of that consideration. But absolutely nothing has changed. I'm afraid I can't be more precise about what might or might not (multiple speakers) policies, yes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chintan Joshi,  Mediobanca - Analyst   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, no. I appreciate that. I don't want to put words into your mouth. Just a quick follow-up. So what is the cost of risk in first-half 2016 in that GBP123 million part, if you can give me the number? And secondly just on capital, you're guiding us to, I think, about 13% benchmark, and anything above that is dividend. Is that at least what I can keep as constant?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I can answer the first one. I missed the second. Firstly, look, without getting overly precise, we're 1.5% -- between 2% to 3%, that type of percent in terms of cost of risk.
 And sorry, and the second question was --? Sorry.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chintan Joshi,  Mediobanca - Analyst   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Was -- you keep guiding us to think about dividends, plus to 13% CET1; so we should just keep thinking about it that way?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Absolutely. That's absolutely the position, yes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chintan Joshi,  Mediobanca - Analyst   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andrew Coombs, Citigroup.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andrew Coombs,  Citigroup - Analyst   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Three questions for me. The first is can you just give some guidance on what the through-the-cycle cost of risk is on the portfolio, going back over in a fairly long period of time? And also where it peaked previously. So that would be my first question.
 Second question is if I just take some of your numbers, 17% times the GBP1.9 billion implies GBP320 million to GBP330 million in net profits. And then you are then talking about it being 5% accretive, which would seem to imply that GBP6.5 billion of statutory net profits for the Group. So I just wanted to clarify if that is the case and that's what you are benchmarking this on.
 And then the third question is just a factor question. What would be the split of the GBP7 billion portfolio between purchase and balance transfer cards? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The balance transfer element -- and this is -- they got money market transfers as well -- is about 40%. I think it's between about 36% and 40%, I think, is the proportion which isn't out of line with our book; has about 36% in as well, so it's about 36%. But they also have -- that's balance transfer. We also have some -- so that's the money market, but it's about 36% to 40% for MBNA.
 In terms of the various returns on investments and accretions and that stuff, as I said, yes. So the return on investment, it's sort of -- that's pre- things like amortization of goodwill, et cetera. And that's a big delta between the 17% return on investment and my EPS accretion. We obviously had to take that in account, but it would be inappropriate to do so in terms of the underlying.
 And the underlying is -- so you can look at it relatively simply. In terms of going back to my previous answer, that GBP250 million we're talking about, I'm looking to target GBP100 million or so of synergies. So post-tax, that's about GBP80 million. That gets you a sort of GBP330 million number over my GBP1.9 billion. It's there or thereabouts.
 When you come to the accretion, I won't comment on the implied earnings of the Group. But I have a smaller number because I have to deduct from that things like the amortization of goodwill, the amortization of the purchased credit card relationships. Those become accounting deductions that impact that, so that's the delta between the two.
 And then in terms of credit history, as you know, we're in a different place. I mean I think as we said in the presentation, we've stressed this to 1 in 20, which is a 5% type -- in terms of impairment. The thing still remains profitable over the plan. And we've looked at the last two years, credit for the whole market -- and this is including subprime -- would be roundabout the 2.5%. If you go pre-crisis, you are into about the 3% type basis. But again, that's whole market and that includes subprime. And I would stress that, as we said in the presentation, this is a prime book.
 So, what we've seen in their book -- and as you might expect, we spent an awfully long time DDing this, getting comfortable with the risk profiles, with the balances that are on their book, and we're very pleased with quality of the new business and the back book. And they have a very close relationship to the quality of the book that we already have within the Lloyds business.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andrew Coombs,  Citigroup - Analyst   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's all very clear, thank you. Just one quick follow-up. On the balance transfer proportion at 40%, how much is pre-promo and how much is post-promo?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Now you've got me (laughter). I've got to come back to you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andrew Coombs,  Citigroup - Analyst   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I was just trying to get a (multiple speakers) is the portfolio is of a vintage whereby you've already got a full run rate of through-the-cycle losses?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, we'll come back on that one.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andrew Coombs,  Citigroup - Analyst   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rohith Chandra-Rajan, Barclays.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rohith Chandra-Rajan,  Barclays Capital - Analyst   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning. It's Rohith Chandra-Rajan at Barclays. A couple of quick ones, please. One was just if you can give us any indication of the pace of growth in this book historically. Maybe it hasn't been growing that fast recently, because there maybe hasn't been a huge amount of focus on it, but maybe what you expect from it, going forward. Would you expect it to grow in line with your existing book, which you highlighted was 5%?
 And then the second one was just some clarification around the GBP240 million relating to PPI. Is that GBP240 million in excess of existing unutilized provisions that you will be capped against? Or you will take this first GBP240 million, and the sellers will pay anything above that? Just some clarification on those two would be great. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi, Rohith. Yes, so in terms of GBP240 million, the best way to look at it -- those are the provisions that the business is coming over with. So if you like, it's got GBP240 million of essentially provisions on its balance sheet, so that's already paid for and provided for. The extent to which that goes to GBP241 million, that GBP1 million would then fall back on Bank of America. So, I've got a GBP240 million provision sitting there that will be -- is already paid for and we'll utilize prospective claims. As I said, the extent to which -- if it does go above that, that falls back on -- and that falls back on the seller. Then on the --
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rohith Chandra-Rajan,  Barclays Capital - Analyst   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So -- sorry, George -- so, essentially, there's no further PPI risk related to this book.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Correct.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rohith Chandra-Rajan,  Barclays Capital - Analyst   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No risk to Lloyds, correct.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Absolutely correct. And then in terms of growth, look, there are a number of moving parts and some affinity relationships; there's underlying core balances. And you're right. We've been growing our underlying core balances and something I think we'd look to continue to grow those. How that plays out in terms of overall, in terms of the MBNA book, we will wait and see. We will see.
 But you're right; and actually, sorry, you were right. It's been relatively flat over the last couple of years. You are correct there. But you're right. This has been a business that's been in an interesting position, as you know, over that period in terms of --.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And we will keep this, Rohith, as a challenger brand, like we did with Halifax. Like we do, indeed, with Halifax for the switcher markets. We will keep this brand separately, competing with all the other brands as a challenger brand. So, Halifax-style on current account switches.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rohith Chandra-Rajan,  Barclays Capital - Analyst   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joseph Dickerson, Jefferies.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joseph Dickerson,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just a couple of quick ones, if I may. Are there any funding synergies here? I believe that Bank of America -- sorry, the MBNA UK pays Bank of America about 100 basis points to fund this portfolio. So I'm wondering why that couldn't be substantially reduced or funded out of your free liquidity.
 And the second question is would you agree with [deMaps] that you've got about GBP3.5 billion of excess capital on your 14.6% target, assuming a static RWA base of GBP222 billion? Thanks so much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Right. Look, I'll answer the first one. This is Antonio. You are absolutely correct, Joe. We have one of the lowest cost of funds in the world, as you can see from our credit default swap. In the UK, we presently have the lowest credit default swap, and we have a very cheap cost of deposits, which is going down. And on top of it, we have access to the TFS of the Bank of England.
 So you are absolutely right; our cost of funding is quite low, lower than the one you mentioned. And we are absolutely going to use it in funding this business; and, therefore, that will accrete to the value of this transaction. That's absolutely clear.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joseph Dickerson,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Is that included in your -- Antonio, is that included in the guidance that you've given for EPS accretion?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 It is included in the guidance that we gave you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joseph Dickerson,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And then, sorry, on your capital, you said -- yes. I mean a moment -- as I said, this is all pre-dividend basis. And pre-dividend accrual is 160 basis points; which, you're right, equates to in [pounds and] pence roundabout a sort of GBP3.5 billion. It's sort of GBP2.2 billion for every percent of that order.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's correct, yes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joseph Dickerson,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, guys.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom Rayner, Exane.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom Rayner,  Exane BNP Paribas - Analyst   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just a couple, please. Just on the cost synergies, 30% of target costs is a bit on the high side, I think, sort of typically. Is there anything you can add on exactly what's -- I know you flagged up the IT systems and that. But is there anything that -- any reason why you're so confident you can take out 30% of that cost base?
 And secondly just on the credit quality -- and, George, you've said you've spent some time going through the book. I'm just wondering what assumptions you've used it when you are stressing the MBNA book. Because obviously a lot of independent forecasts are looking for GDP to slow quite sharply next year, interest rates to go up. I'm wondering about things like sensitivity to those people on 0% balance transfers, once interest rates start going up, and then they start to switch over. So I was wondering if you could add some color on both of those issues, please.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Right, Tom. I'll [ask] on the first one. In terms of confidence on the cost synergies, our confidence is very high. You know about our track record on costs. We have the lowest cost to income of the sector. We have a track record of integration, as we did between all systems and Lloyds and HBOS previously.
 And relating specifically to this deal, we have also recently done the integration of the credit cards of Halifax into Lloyds; and, therefore, this will be a very similar process for us, which gives us a very good benchmark on how to assess and project the synergies. We are very, very confident about this. As I told you, I think our track record in costs is clear.
 This is very important, because it's the fact that we have a lower cost to income and a clear integration track record. And this high level of synergies that enables, due to the [field] in which we provide the best conditions to the seller. And at the same time, given the integration benefits, we provide, as George just described, significant shareholder value for shareholders.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, and Tom then on the second: we've looked -- we've run various 1 in 20, so we've looked stressing up to an unemployment rate of 9.5%, I think is what we played through. So I think it's come up to 5%, 6% type. By the way, that includes in terms of zero balance transfers. I would say and, too, we know how to manage these. We've got a good record of managing balances down, and people adhering to the terms of these [stricter] balances as they move from on to the rolloff amount. So, as I said, we've stressed -- as I say, [I think it was down] 10% unemployment, and the thing remained profitable over the plan period.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom Rayner,  Exane BNP Paribas - Analyst   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And sorry, on interest rate assumptions? Sorry, did I miss that?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 On the interest rate assumptions, Tom, as soon as we get this deal concluded, this will be part of our total balance sheet management; and, therefore, we will manage it. As you know, we manage this in a combined way, assets minus liabilities, on a weekly basis, at the top of the organization. And these portfolios will come into that management, which we do in an integrated way. Until we receive the business, this still is matched funding in terms of funding, and therefore it will not be affected by short-term movements from interest rates. We have that locked in, in terms of matched funding.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom Rayner,  Exane BNP Paribas - Analyst   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Sorry, I was thinking more about potential effect on credit quality trends, if rates start to push up on that book over the next couple of years. (multiple speakers)
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I understand. And George already told you what prices we put. And we already told you what cushion of IRR above cost of equity we have. Of course, if interest rates start to go up, you have the other side of the balance sheet where our current account balances is. (multiple speakers) reinvested at successively higher rates. And as I told you, we will include this portfolio in the total, which we told you over the last few years how we manage in a total combined and integrated way.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom Rayner,  Exane BNP Paribas - Analyst   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [47]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Manners, Morgan Stanley.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Manners,  Morgan Stanley - Analyst   [48]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So just a few questions, if I may. The first one was on net interest margins. When you had Q3, you gave quite a firm guidance you'd be able to keep the margin roundabout flat in 2017 versus 2016. Is this going to give you, call it, 10 basis points of improvement (inaudible) is going to complete at the end of the first half, maybe 5 basis points improvement. Should we just tack that onto your existing guidance of around [270], just to clarify that point?
 The second one was on competition and the CMA. Have you had many conversations with the CMA and competition authorities? Because it does look like the credit card market in the UK will get quite concentrated, because yourselves plus Barclays will be over 50% of the market, which does look like quite an increase in concentration; albeit it will still be slightly smaller than Barclays.
 And a third question was on capital. Presumably this deal is only actually going to close next year. So are you going to take into account an 80 basis points capital impact when you consider the dividend this year? Or do you actually have a capacity to pay a special, pay down to [13] at the end of the year, this year; and then, next year, absorb the 80 basis points capital impact?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [49]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi, Chris. Yes, to answer your questions, first one, yes. So, in terms of NIM and could you just see this as incremental to guidance that we've given the market? Absolutely yes. So, this should be seen as incremental to that; so I agree with that.
 In terms of competition, yes, as you might expect we've done quite a lot of work in terms of competition. And you're right, Barclays has something like 28%; this will put us at 26%. What we would point to, though, as you know, this is a market where very recently the FCA has conducted a market study and found this is a well-functioning market with low barriers to new entry; large numbers on products and offerings; good evidence of customers switching; and essentially a healthy, competitive market.
 So, yes, there is obviously a process to go through. We will run MBNA as a separate challenger brand within this. And one of the -- the competition precedents on the deal is the competition approval, but I think we are confident of receiving that approval.
 In terms of capital, then as you said -- sorry, I can't get overly enlighten you, but you're actually correct. The deal will close in 2017; therefore, it's a capital deduction in 2017. I think as we've said, when -- in line with our normal policy, the Board meets at the end of the year and will assess the capital position at that point, and the uses of the capital at that point.
 And the discussion usually -- always reflects things like the regulatory environment, internal knowledge, et cetera. And this acquisition will be form part of that consideration. And I'm afraid it would be wrong for me to say any more than that. It will just be part of that consideration at the year-end.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Manners,  Morgan Stanley - Analyst   [50]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got you. But the 80 basis points impact doesn't actually preclude a special dividend this year, if you think you have enough capital accretion next year to fund the acquisition. Is that fair?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [51]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No, what I've said is that -- the Board will make its consideration at the year-end.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Manners,  Morgan Stanley - Analyst   [52]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [53]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Cant, Autonomous.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Cant,  Autonomous Research - Analyst   [54]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I had a couple, please. Firstly, could you tell us how much intangible asset will be created on the close of the transaction? You've talked about [our motivation]. And if I could just ask a clarification. You mentioned a number, George, of GBP330 million, ex-amortization. So from a capital generation perspective, should we be thinking about this more in terms of 7% accretion, given that the amortization is already (multiple speakers)?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [55]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, no, that's a fair point. That's a fair point, Chris. Yes, you're right. It's GBP1.9 billion, of which about GBP0.8 billion is equity, so I've got about GBP1 billion. As you know, I've got to make the determinations between the different types of goodwill, the purchased customer relationships, the fair value unwinds, et cetera. But you're right; from a -- the intangible perspective, that already doesn't count. And you're right; that's one that you'll get a stronger capital accretion. Correct.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Cant,  Autonomous Research - Analyst   [56]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 But I was saying in terms of that 7% type level implied by that GBP330 million, you're comfortable with that as an output, from the quick maths I've done?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [57]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Am I comfortable with that as an output? Your math is normally okay (laughter).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Cant,  Autonomous Research - Analyst   [58]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. I'll take that as a yes. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [59]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jason Napier, UBS.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jason Napier,  UBS - Analyst   [60]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Two simple ones, please. The first was on RWA density in the acquired business, almost 100%. I just wondered whether there was any scope for incorporating that on to your internal models, and whether you'd have any perspectives on whether the density might change.
 And then the second question -- and I'm afraid this is far simpler maths than those have been covered earlier in the call. But if the first-half annualized profit is about GBP330 million and the applicable tax rate is about 20%, if the cost base is GBP333 million, I don't have any real implied loan losses for the first half. So I'm just wondering whether that GBP650 million revenue is a net of loan losses number, if you follow the path of that question.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [61]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sorry, I missed a bit of that. But about GBP300 million is on a post-tax type basis. If you think it's earning GBP250 million, post-tax and I generate GBP80 million of synergies, post-tax, you're on a sort of GBP330 million post-tax basis, Jason, that would sort of be the number. So you can gross that up, but you're right. It would be a nonbanking entity at a -- sort of 20% tax rate, and will come back up to -- and the RW -- yes, there is. It's sent to migrate back. You're right. They're almost on a 100% -- -- I mean, the equivalent on our book is around about a 90%, 91% in terms of RWA density in terms of utilization of our models. And as we said, should that portfolio ever become a reality, it's useful, but --.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [62]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think on your numbers, Jason, what you are missing is that of course we will not realize the synergies until the two years, right?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jason Napier,  UBS - Analyst   [63]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No. Yes, I get that. So if we do this really simply, annualized post-tax profit in the first half is about GBP246 million. On 20% tax, that gets you to GBP310 million. You've got a cost base which you've told us is GBP333 million (multiple speakers) synergy number, and revenues that are GBP650 million. So GBP650 million, less GBP333 million of costs gives you pre-provision profit of GBP300 million. And we're getting to a first-half pre-tax profit number of about GBP300 million. So I'm just wondering what the run rate line losses were in the first half, or what I'm doing incorrectly.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [64]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (multiple speakers) We'll get back to you on the maths. It is a small number. We can get back to you on the --
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [65]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 A small number, and then we put this number, as we said, into the average across the cycle. And as the two years start to elapse, you create the synergies. And you have the underlying numbers that George was referring to.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jason Napier,  UBS - Analyst   [66]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got it. Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [67]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Toeman, HSBC.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Toeman,  HSBC - Analyst   [68]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, sorry, I was just concerned also, like Jason. I couldn't reconcile your numbers on impairment. You seem to have a very small impairment number. But am I right in thinking this 17% return includes the impairment charge at about 150 basis points?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [69]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Absolutely, and it's of that order. That's correct. A bit high, but -- yes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Toeman,  HSBC - Analyst   [70]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And I gather the book is on a standardized approach, at the moment, for --
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [71]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's correct.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Toeman,  HSBC - Analyst   [72]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And then is there any uplift by moving to IRB?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [73]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's what we said. You get a marginal benefit. So they're roughly about 100%. We're on a sort of 90% type basis, so you don't get a fundamental game change in terms of moving to IRB.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [74]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And we also like strategically this shift to where we increase our weight in customer finance, which as you know is [either] we weigh dense versus our previous overweighting mortgages, which is [either] we weigh light. So this is another positive thing whereby we -- if you want, we fill our under-presence in the credit card businesses. Which is, as you know, RWA in terms even that's also helpful from a total RWA density, in the light of the present regulatory trends as well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Toeman,  HSBC - Analyst   [75]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [76]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Lock, Deutsche Bank.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Lock,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [77]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think most of my questions have been answered, but just a follow-up to Chris's one, really, which is around competition. Appreciate you think you are going to get the competition approval for this. But just wondered if we should expect you to consider -- to continue to look for other potential portfolios or bolt-on acquisitions within the UK space. You've got a 26% credit card market share now. You've got a very strong mortgage market share now. Is this where you see the business being at the right position now in the UK? Or do you think there is more -- there are other areas where you think you could grow? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [78]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. It's Antonio here. Look, we have always said -- and not only always, but also when we presented the second strategic review two years ago -- that the consumer finance area -- and that's why I put it as a separate area in the bank where we wanted to foster growth -- was underrepresented in two divisions of that big division in the two segments. It was underrepresented both in credit cards and in car finance.
 In credit cards we have -- and have around 15%, as George mentioned. With this transaction, we go to around 26%, so we fill that gap with this transaction. Very clear strategic sense, clear value for shareholders, and limited and [caps] risks. So we think we absolutely delivered the transaction that we envisaged in this space, although we were growing organically reasonably well.
 On the car finance base, we are growing very well. And also, given our joint venture with Jaguar Land Rover, as you know, which in retail language, if you want, provided us with an additional important product through a lot of additional outlets. That's why our car finance activities are growing close to 20% a year for the past few years. Therefore, in the car finance space, although we only have a market share of 13%, we are growing organically very well.
 If there were portfolios to be considered, as we have said before, we would. There is no portfolio in this space that we are looking at, at the moment, or that we know is available. And we will continue to grow organically well.
 And in the other areas, as you know, you know what our strategy is. We continue to grow organically in SMEs, gaining market share. And, therefore, there is no other transaction of any special significance to which we are looking, at this stage.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Lock,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [79]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. And (technical difficulty).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Antonio Horta-Osorio,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - Group Chief Executive   [80]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sorry, we lost you now. Hello?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [81]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David, please redial. The line has been disconnected. Please re-ask your question. (Operator Instructions).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Lock,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [82]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Sorry, just a follow-up question. I wonder if you'd be able to share any geographic representations in the portfolio. Is it fair to say it's generally in line with the overall split across the UK? I know you have a slightly different geographic weighting in your mortgage portfolio, perhaps to others. So, I just wondered if you had any color on the geographic weighting of the credit cards. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 George Culmer,  Lloyds Banking Group plc - CFO   [83]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No, there's nothing particular to tell in terms of the geographics. It's a book that is overwhelmingly sourced remotely, online, that type of stuff. But there's nothing particular in terms of geographic concentration that I would point to.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Lock,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [84]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [85]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. There are no further questions. Ladies and gentlemen, if you have further questions, please contact the Lloyds team. That does conclude your conference call for today. You may now disconnect. Thank you for joining, and enjoy the rest of the day.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[Lloyds Banking Group PLC To Acquire MBNA Ltd From Bank of America Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>CHARLOTTE</city>
  <companyName>Lloyds Banking Group PLC</companyName>
  <companyTicker>LLOY.L</companyTicker>
  <startDate>20-Dec-16 9:00am GMT</startDate>
</Event>