<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7308156" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 6:30:48am GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7308156.F" expirationDate="Tuesday, December 20, 2016 at 6:15:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of AMC M&A conference call or presentation 20-Dec-16 6:15pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc to Discuss the Department of Justice Approval of the Carmike Cinemas, Inc. Acquisition Conference Call

Columbus Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc M&A conference call or presentation Tuesday, December 20, 2016 at 6:15:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  John Merriwether
      AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - VP, IR
   *  Adam Aron
      AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO
   *  Craig Ramsey
      AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Eric Handler
      MKM Partners - Analyst
   *  Ben Mogil
      Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst
   *  David Miller
      Loop Capital - Analyst
   *  Barton Crockett
      FBR Capital Markets - Analyst
   *  Michael Greenberg
      MNS International - Analyst
   *  James Goss
      Barrington Research - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Greetings and welcome to the AMC DOJ approval conference call. (Operator Instructions). As a reminder, this conference is being recorded. I would now like to turn the conference over to your host, John Merriwether, Vice President, Investor Relations. Thank you, Mr. Merriwether, you may begin.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Merriwether,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - VP, IR   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Doug. Good afternoon, everyone. I'm John Merriwether. I would like to welcome you to this afternoon's call to discuss the DOJ's approval of AMC's acquisition of Carmike Cinemas. I'd like to remind you that some of the comments made by management during this conference call may constitute forward-looking statements within the meaning of Section 27A of the Securities Act of 1933, as amended and Section 21E of the Securities Exchange Act of 1934 as amended.
 Statements made during this call about management's belief about the effect of the acquisition of Carmike or Carmike and Odeon &amp; UCI, or the effect of the DOJ order on AMC's future business operations and financial performance are forward-looking statements. Forward-looking statements are subject to risks, uncertainties and assumptions that are discussed in our public filings, including our most recent 10-K, 10-Qs and 8-Ks.
 Statements made on this call are based on current estimates and future events and the Company has no obligation to update or correct those estimates. Listeners are cautioned that any such forward-looking statements are not guarantees of future performance and involve risks and uncertainty and that actual results may differ materially as a result of these various factors.
 After our prepared remarks, there will be a question-and-answer session. Joining me on the call this morning are Adam Aron, CEO and President and Craig Ramsay, Chief Financial Officer. I will now turn the call over to Adam.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, John; good afternoon, everyone. We appreciate you joining us today on short notice. We scheduled this call to wish you all happy holidays, to make sure you've seen our beautiful new website launched on November 30, to celebrate adding another 1 million Stubs members since September and to congratulate Disney on Rogue One. Now let's turn to any questions you may have. No, maybe there is a little more to talk about.
 So, needless to say, we are in a good mood in Leawood, Kansas. Today is a glorious day and another great day for AMC. As you know, earlier this morning, the Department of Justice completed its review of our pending Carmike Cinemas transaction. We are very pleased to announce and to report to you that AMC and the Department of Justice have, in fact, reach a settlement that will allow our acquisition of Carmike Cinemas to proceed.
 As you know, in November, Carmike shareholders voted by a significant margin in favor of the transaction. The DOJ approval today was the last remaining regulatory hurdle needed to be crossed and therefore, we are working expeditiously to complete the transaction as quickly as possible and almost certainly before year-end. Naturally, we will alert you by a press release when the acquisition closes.
 As we've maintained since the beginning, all of the latest combination of AMC and Carmike will expand our presence throughout the country creating the single largest movie theater exhibitor in the United States. But even more importantly, it will allow us to introduce our successful guest experience initiatives, proven at AMC, to tens of millions of new customers improving the moviegoing experience for them. It's also expected to broaden our appeal with moviegoers with more people having access to the AMC Stubs loyalty program redesigned in July and our new website, www.AMCtheaters.com and smartphone apps launched just three weeks ago.
 We continue to believe that this transaction combines two great companies with complementary geographic footprints. AMC focuses on large urban areas, especially the Northeast, Midwest and on the West Coast while Carmike's, America's hometown theater chain, strategy serves midsize and nonurban areas primarily in the South and Southeast.
 We believe this diversification will further be beneficial because while there is wide appeal for all film genres in AMC theaters, over the years, we have seen that film genres play differently in different geographic areas. Fast action, R-rated movies tend to play better in the larger urban areas while family-oriented, faith-based and military movies tend to play better in the nonurban and rural markets. The AMC-Carmike combination should help smooth out some of that volatility and allow us to provide something for every moviegoer.
 In total, we are as confident today as we were back in March when this transaction was first announced, that the growth potential for AMC is enhanced by joining forces with Carmike Cinemas.
 As part of the DOJ approval process and as expected, AMC has agreed to certain conditions on which the transaction can move forward. There are two primary areas of focus -- theater divestitures and our activity with National CineMedia and Screenvision.
 Let's review the divestitures first. Just to get your bearings, prior to any divestitures, AMC currently has 392 operating theaters in the United States and Carmike 271 for a combined starting US total of 663 theaters. As originally contemplated in the agreement to acquire Carmike, we will be divesting two theaters from the Starplex acquisition of December 2015 that ironically we sold to Carmike just 12 months back. The completion of the sale of these two former Starplex theaters will take place prior to the closing of the Carmike transaction.
 As part of the agreement with the Department of Justice, we were quite pleased to learn that AMC will be required to divest theaters in only 15 overlapping local trading areas in which we will operate on a combined basis. We actually have a choice of which theaters to divest in these specified markets, so the exact number of theaters to be sold is not yet finalized. We do expect though that it will be a total of between 15 and 20 divested theaters, including the two formerly of Starplex. The divested theaters will come mostly from the existing Carmike circuit. The theater level cash flows of the theaters to be divested are consistent with our original divestiture expectations and in our view are modest in the single digit millions of dollars. We already have identified a buyer for the two former Starplex locations. The remaining theaters are expected to be sold in the next 60 days.
 Now let's move over to the NCM and Screenvision requirements in the DOJ settlement. There are two primary components both reflecting the Justice Department's desire to preserve competition in preshow advertising, essentially between NCM who offers preshow advertising in AMC theaters and Screenvision, who does so at Carmike's theaters. First, our ownership in NCM and Screenvision; second, the theaters participating in each of the two networks.
 On ownership, AMC has been a founding owner of NCM since 2005 and our current ownership position is about 17%. With the completion of the Carmike acquisition, we expect our NCM ownership will increase to over 25%. Carmike owns approximately 20% of Screenvision, a stake that we will be inheriting.
 Under the terms of the settlement we just reached with the DOJ, AMC will sell down over the next 30 months our ownership stake in NCM to no more than 4.99%. During that 30-month period, there are also two interim thresholds. A year from now, our ownership must be no more than 15% and two years from now, it must be no more than 7.5%. We intend to work closely with NCM and do our utmost to handle these NCM stock sales in an orderly fashion over that 2.5 year period.
 We are not at all troubled by this NCM share selldown. We greatly appreciate our solid long-term working relationship with NCM, which is well-protected for both of AMC and for NCM through a detailed operating contract that runs through the year 2037. The sale of the NCM shares will, of course, generate significant cash proceeds, which we expect to use to delever the AMC balance sheet and to invest in deploying strategic growth initiatives at our theaters.
 Additionally, while we don't comment on merger rumors and such, there always is the possibilities of these monies helping us to fund additional acquisitions for AMC in the future. Importantly, whether reducing our debt, reinvesting in our own circuit or exploring other acquisitions, we believe these uses have the potential to be the best allocation and deployment of our capital.
 It goes without saying that there will be tax payments associated with the selling of those NCM shares. However, given our net operating loss carryforwards and some higher basis NCM shares, we do not expect the near-term tax implications to be significant. The possibility also exists that a future tax impact could be further reduced depending upon the new administration's success in achieving tax reforms.
 In addition to the reduction of our NCM share ownership, we will be giving up our one NCM Board seat and our right to select an independent director. We also will be waiving founding-member governance rights, but this is of not concern. NCM is a well-run company in our opinion. We simply do not believe that we need ownership or Board protection given our long-term multi-decade contractual relationship, which endures.
 As it relates to our ownership in Screenvision, we are not required to sell any shares. However, we do expect to convert about half of our current Screenvision shares to be of nonvoting status.
 The second DOJ requirement relates to new screens that accrue to Screenvision and to NCM and a minimal transfer of screens soon between the NCM and Screenvision networks. We expect that Screenvision will pick up service at five of Carmike's current Sundance Cinema locations that have not as of yet implemented an in-theater advertising program. The DOJ is further requiring that we transfer approximately 19 theaters to the Screenvision advertising network that are currently operating under AMC's NCM contract. We will have 60 days to affect this transfer. We will, of course, work very closely with both NCM and Screenvision to minimize any disruption to their businesses from these changes.
 In saying this, I think it's important to note that Screenvision is picking up theaters now prior to divestiture, which is good for Screenvision. As for NCM, there is also good news. Eyeballs at current AMC-NCM theaters have the potential to grow markedly due to the attendance gains that result from our previously announced goal of renovating over the next two years another one-third of AMC's current theaters with plush recliner seating.
 Additionally, going forward, NCM retains its exclusive contractual access to the future growth in the number of AMC theaters in the US that we build or acquire after the Carmike transaction. Those future theaters will operate under the NCM contract unless committed and encumbered to Screenvision or another advertising provider if, as and when acquired.
 As you sort through all this, it may be helpful to remind you that under the terms of our existing NCM service agreement, which will remain in effect for the next two decades going forward, we will continue to receive a monthly theater access fee for participation in the NCM network. Based on our NCM ownership at the time, we still will be entitled to receive quarterly dividends and dividend distributions of excess cash. However, should we elect to take NCM shares for the Screenvision attendance that result from the Carmike transaction, we will also be required to pay NCM a quarterly make-whole payment to compensate NCM for the Screenvision attendance related to Carmike.
 Similarly, we, AMC, should continue to enjoy the economic benefits that accrue to Carmike now under its Screenvision contract, which will also continue over the long haul through July 1 of 2042. In fact, we look forward to establishing a fine relationship with Screenvision.
 In closing, I would especially like to thank the staff and executives at the Department of Justice for their diligence and thoughtfulness in reviewing this transaction. We believe that tens of millions of moviegoers will reap the benefits of AMC's future investments in the Carmike theaters and, in our opinion, the DOJ's approval supports that belief.
 As we extend our appreciation, we also are grateful to David Passman and the people of Carmike who've worked so hard and well this year under difficult circumstances in getting us to this position.
 In summary, I simply cannot contain my enthusiasm that the Carmike acquisition is now clear to go. This is another exciting day for all of us here at AMC in 2016. One of our key priorities for AMC that we announced at the beginning of the year was to grow our Company through acquisition. Well, in 2016, we certainly have done what we said we would do.
 On November 30, we completed the acquisition of Odeon &amp; UCI Cinemas Group, since renamed Odeon and our teams have already been on the ground since day one in Europe working with our colleagues at Odeon to integrate the UK and Europe's largest movie exhibition circuit into the growing world of AMC.
 Now, today, on December 20, we've received the final regulatory approval needed to complete the acquisition of Carmike Cinemas and a closing on this transaction is imminent. Our executives, managers and staff in the United States have worked tirelessly this year on integration planning. I can tell you categorically that, in my view, they are talented and dedicated; they are very well-prepared; and they are raring to go.
 What excites our teams is that, upon completion of the Carmike transaction, AMC will become the largest movie exhibitor in the United States, the largest movie exhibitor in Europe and the largest movie theaters exhibitor in the world. Now, we strive not only to be the biggest, but also to be the best. Thank you for listening. I would like to turn the call back to the operator so that Craig and I can take your questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. (Operator Instructions). Eric Handler, MKM Partners.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Eric Handler,  MKM Partners - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks for taking my question. Two questions for you guys. First, with regards to Carmike, now you've had quite a bit of time to go through the Company's books and assess their assets. I'm just curious how fast do you think you can move in terms of doing some renovations and reseats at the circuit and what have you found from kicking the tires on the assets over the past, what's nearly a year now? And then, secondly, with regards to National CineMedia, do you have the ability to say you want cash or shares as part of the Carmike transaction because I think that would be about 18 million shares, which you would then, of course, have to sell? So I'm just curious who has the option to say either cash or shares will be delivered? And then did you have the option to either divest all of Screenvision and instead keep all of what you have in National CineMedia or did the government specifically want you to reduce your position in National CineMedia?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Eric, I will take two of your three and Craig will take the third. In terms of what we've learned over the year, the blessing of -- we announced the transaction in March. It's now December. So we've had plenty of time to look at the Carmike circuit and to plan for the integration. And I guess before I talk about renovations and re-seats and what we've learned, I probably should talk about timing. Because we've had so much time to plan well, we are going to cut over the first Carmike theater into AMC in the second week of January. And we are essentially going to use this second half of January to pilot at about 13 Carmike theaters, AMC systems, make sure they are working smoothly, that our cutover of these first call it a dozen theaters or so is working seamlessly. We expect that to be the case and therefore starting February 1, we are going to be bringing the Carmike theaters into the AMC network very fast, which means getting our POS system in place, switching the theaters and showtimes from the Carmike website to the AMC website, changing people's points earning capability from Carmike's loyalty program to our loyalty program. That's going to move at, I think, a fairly blistering pace. We expect to be able to get all 271 of Carmike theaters, less whatever number we divest, into the AMC system by the end of April or May. So that's a pretty quick move.
 In terms of what we've learned, we've learned that, for all of our talk, including in my prepared remarks about -- we are in big markets and they are in small markets and actually there is a big chunk of theaters that overlaps and so what we've decided to do is proceed with what we are calling a two-brand strategy, three brands if you count the dine-in theaters as its own sub-brand. You have some theaters that will be branded and taken to the public as AMC and other theaters that have less visitation that might have slightly lower service standards, branded as a second brand, but what we found is that there are plenty of Carmike theaters that are substantial enough in their visitation or locales to graduate, so to speak, into the AMC brand. And there are a lot of AMC theaters that also have lower visitation levels that we think are more like a Carmike theater than like an AMC theater.
 So I would expect that in excess of 50 current AMC theaters will move into the second brand and in excess of 100 Carmike theaters will move into the AMC brand. Now, just because they are different brands doesn't mean that guest satisfaction will be lower in brand 2 than brand 1. It just means that we will offer different levels of service, amenities and price points and better marry consumer expectations to the reality of what's being offered.
 So I think that's what we've learned with one additional caveat. The other thing that we've learned is that when you have low visitation theaters, those theaters tend to be lower margin theaters and therefore being maniacal about cost management is extremely important and for that reason, again, we are pleased by the two-brand strategy because we will have one set of operating standards for the AMC theaters, another set of operating standards for the second brand theaters and that will allow us to be more focused on managing cost at each brand at the appropriate level and I would point out that I think if you look at our financial results in 2016, AMC has demonstrated this year a very good ability to manage its costs and that's something we are proud of and that will continue going forward. So preserving the cost structure of these lower visitation theaters is also important.
 In terms of when we can get started, there is a small get started and a big get started. The small get started is we would like there to be what we call consumer clues at every single Carmike theater, whether it's in the AMC brand or the second brand, that things got better for moviegoers because AMC has arrived as owner. So as an example, it is our intention to get Coke freestyle machines in 100% of Carmike theaters with their 100 choices of drink flavors because we know that consumers love the drink machines from Coke and they love the variety of flavors and they like the free refills and that's something that we think we can get done across the entire Carmike network by let's say the end of June. If that slips a little bit into July or August, so be it, but the vast, vast majority, if not all the Carmike system will be done by June 30.
 In terms of the larger issue, which is the larger getting started -- by the way, another issue with the smaller getting started is signage. We are going to put the appropriate AMC signage up at the appropriate Carmike theaters as soon as we can in 2017.
 In terms of the big getting started, I think what you are thinking about is recliner seats and full-blown theater renovations. We have identified that there are an easy 50 to 100 Carmike theaters that are capable of supporting an AMC-style renovation. I think you'll see those back-end-loaded more in 2018 and 2019 than before, but it's not inconceivable that we could get some theaters done at the end of 2017.
 On the issue of did the DOJ want us to sell off Screenvision entirely, I think I would say that the exact opposite was true. Throughout this whole process, the Department of Justice has been very interested in preserving competition between NCM and Screenvision. We pledged to facilitate that competition by maintaining Screenvision actively at some of our theaters and NCM actively at some of our theaters. So they did not want us to go to an all NCM shop or an all Screenvision shop. They wanted us to have a foot in both camps so that both NCM and Screenvision can prosper.
 As for your third question, I will give it to Craig.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Craig Ramsey,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, the question was about the election of cash or shares. There's really two elections. Adam referenced one in his remarks when he said should we elect to take NCM shares for the attendance, Carmike attendance. That is our election and if we would like to take the shares then there are make-whole provisions that come into play and we've seen that in prior mergers.
 Then the second election is on the part of NCM. They have the right to deliver the value of the shares in cash or shares. So I think the specific answer to your question is NCM would have a call to make on whether they deliver cash or the shares.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Eric Handler,  MKM Partners - Analyst   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Thank you very much. Appreciate it, guys.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ben Mogil, Stifel.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ben Mogil,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good afternoon. Thanks for taking my question. So I just want to make sure on the Screenvision, and I think, Craig, you obviously talked about the two elections, which I fully get, is the way that we should be thinking about it is the NCM shares, which are basically not at all tied to any kind of integration payment, if you will or make-whole payment? Basically what you are looking at is you've got about 24 million NCM shares now and that goes down by about -- you sell about 17 million over the next two years. Is that the way to think about it in terms of those -- where the dividend flow changes? Is that the right way to think about it?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Craig Ramsey,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 24 million today. I think you would then sell down to about 7 million, so of that, 17 million would be sold and that would impact the -- I'm repeating what you are saying as a confirmation -- that would impact the level of dividend that you receive today on the 24 million versus what you would ultimately receive on the 7 million, generally speaking. There's two pieces to the dividend, the quarterly cash distribution and then there's a tax receivable piece that doesn't get pro rata-adjusted down like the quarterly cash distributions would get pro rata reduced.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And Ben, since you are on the point, it wasn't in my prepared comments, but I would like to emphasize it. We do intend to work very closely with NCM to see what we can do to make this a very orderly selldown of shares. We think 2.5 years is a long time to get it done, much longer than the Justice Department often gives us, or gives not us, but gives players the timing to sell down. We actually think that this is very good news for NCM in the sense that this is going to give them an opportunity to increase their float.
 This is the same comment we've been making about AMC since my first conference call with you all back in January that AMC is a company with limited float. NCM is a company with limited trading volume. It's our personal opinion that our shares will trade better and their shares will trade better when institutional investors know that they can amass a position and to get in and get out at their whim without moving the market. So just as we are quite pleased that there was a lot of equity issued to Odeon and Carmike in the transactions, which will ultimately increase our trading volumes and float, we think this is a great opportunity for NCM to see its float increase and its public liquidity increase and its trading volumes increase. And as I said, we will be working with them very closely to try to accomplish this in an orderly manner over 2.5 full years.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ben Mogil,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam, on that point, given that you are losing a Board seat and your stake is below 5% and given NCM trades at a better multiple than your own stock, why not just go down to zero of a stake? Other than the shares that you are going to have to keep -- other than the shares that you may get because of the election for the Carmike transaction. If you've got 23.9 million shares now and you are selling the 17 million, why not just sell down to zero?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Why don't we get down to 4.99 million before we worry about what we do with the last 4.99 million? We have a lot of shares to sell to do it smartly in a way that preserves value for AMC and preserves value for NCM. That's a question for a later earnings call. How's that?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ben Mogil,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Now I know in about a year what I can ask.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Miller, Loop Capital.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Miller,  Loop Capital - Analyst   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Congratulations. A couple questions here. Craig, with this kind of global scale -- and of course, Adam, if you want to chime in, I would love to hear your thoughts -- but with this kind of global scale, over 10,000 screens, pre these deals, you guys have always operated with net rentals of around -- it depends on the quarter obviously -- but around call it 53%-ish, 53.5%. We see no reason why you guys can't lower that significantly. How quickly do you think you can do that in your negotiations with splits with the studio?
 And then, Adam, just as a follow-up, on the 15 theaters that you are divesting, is that generally the number that you were expecting? It sounds like from your tone of voice that you are thrilled with that number. We were expecting a slightly higher number. I just want to know if my thoughts aligned with yours. It sounds to me like you were maybe expecting a slightly higher number, but I would just like to hear it from you. Thanks very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, David. It's 15 to 20, not 15 and, yes, I personally am thrilled with that number. Back when I was doing my back of the envelope in January, February, March, I thought the divestitures would be somewhere between 15 and 35 and so we were coming in at the very low end of that range. Now, having said that, we did spend eight months with the Justice Department of the United States and I will tell you that they work on behalf of the taxpayers quite skillfully and would point out to you that if we are not able, for some reason, to port over 19 theaters from NCM to Screenvision, we could conceivably have to divest an additional 19 theaters. I think there's low odds of that happening because I think we can negotiate something with NCM and Screenvision that is satisfactory to all four parties -- us, NCM, Screenvision and the Department of Justice. So, I think at the end of the day, it will be 15 to 20 and, yes, that's a good number from our standpoint.
 In terms of the global scale and you are correct about your film rental splits, they are between 52% and 54% depending upon who the operator is and what the quarter is. I've been very careful since I got here. Other people in the industry have enjoyed talking about who has more clout with whom, studios or exhibitors, who can smash down the other into getting higher film rent splits if you are a studio fan or lower film rental splits if you are a theater operator fan. I've never engaged in that talk publicly. Clearly, the fact that we have global scale will help our position at the table, but I've said since I got here that my focus was on growing the pie for everybody and making more money for the studios and making more money for us and not focusing as much on how we divvy up the pie between us.
 And examples of that, that's why we work so hard to put in the new Stubs program, which has doubled the size of our database, which is allowing us to communicate with identified moviegoers 50 to 100 times a year, tell them they ought to go to a movie this weekend. It's why we just spent $11 million on creating what we think is a gorgeous new website and smartphone apps, which we believe is already doing a much better job in converting people from being browsers to buyers on the website and on their smartphones. And that's what I would like us to talk about, vis-a-vis studios, which is how we can increase the dollars that we bring in to the total AMC pie.
 We do think the fact that we are going to commit to renovate a significant number of AMC theaters and a significant number of Carmike theaters and a significant number of Odeon theaters is going to cause attendance at those theaters to increase. That's good for studios. That's good for us. So I'm not unaware of your question and I think it's a legitimate one to be had, but I think diplomacy requires that my comments and my focus be about making more money for studios and making more money for AMC rather than arguing between us about the split of what might be a static pie.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Miller,  Loop Capital - Analyst   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, great. Thanks very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett, FBR Capital Markets.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks for taking questions from me. I guess one thing I was curious about, you say that the transaction will close imminently. What has to happen before this closes specifically?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Specifically, we have to complete the sale of the two Starplex theaters because they are actually the subject of a consent decree of December 2015 that we can't own those two theaters, but I did mention we've already identified a buyer of those two theaters. And then we need to wire a lot of money to somebody and issue some shares and there are various merger certificates which have to be filed in some court or statehouse in Delaware, but the answer is not much and I do believe we will close on this transaction toot sweet.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, great. And this part of the transaction with electing to potentially get more shares out of National CineMedia, I think we were estimating that you might, under the documents, be entitled to something like 12 million or so shares and I was wondering if you could comment on the number of shares -- I know you gave a percent -- but the number of shares to help us make sure we got it somewhere in the ballpark?
 And then should we just assume that that is going to happen or is there some sensitivity you have to the share price for NCM that will factor into that? And, if there is, you have to pay for these through the integration payments. Can you give us some sense of what your break price is versus going for more shares or not?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Craig Ramsey,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Your number is in the ballpark. It is a formula that is based upon the number of attendees that would be delivered, which is dependent upon the divestitures. It's also dependent upon the stock price at the day that it is calculated. And so -- but your number is representative, in the ballpark; it's not that far off, but subject to those different variables.
 We will begin discussions -- there are a number of different topics to talk to National CineMedia about and back to this election, whether we elect to take all the shares or part of the shares, it's just too early to start giving guidance on that or really to be speculating because all of the different touch points, the make-whole provision, the number of shares, the porting of screens, all that we need to sit down and have conversations with NCM and it's all wrapped together. So to pick a piece of it apart and talk about an individual piece of those discussions I think doesn't make sense at this point in time. So I would just say -- back to the original point -- in terms of what it could be, the number of shares is -- your math is pretty close.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And then on the other side of the Screenvision arrangement, the moving of screens to Screenvision from National CineMedia, is there a contractual -- does NCM -- do they accept that or would there have to be some type of integration payment from those screens that would be taken out of the NCM network and put into the Screenvision network? How contractually would cash flows work around that and how flexible is that arrangement? Is there some type of agreement or is this contemplated in the contract that you laid out that goes through 2027, the founding partners agreement?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 2037.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Craig Ramsey,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, 2037. I think there's a precedent in the agreement for make-whole payments. I'm not an attorney and I'm not going to parse the words in the contract to say that this is a contractual right, but I will say -- and go back to Adam's comment -- the option is that we have to sell the screens in which case there's really -- there's no remuneration available. So I don't know if that's leverage or not. That's the reality we live with. We need to come to a negotiated agreement with National CineMedia -- and I'm sure we will -- that will benefit both parties.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, I want to just weigh in for a second. Since the DOJ agreement was reached, I've personally had conversations with the senior officials at both NCM and Screenvision and we are going to be the biggest customer or biggest client of Screenvision. We are going to be the biggest customer or client of advertising services in general. We are going to remain a very important customer at NCM. Since we will move from the founding member category to the affiliate member category, we will be the largest affiliate customer that NCM is going to have.
 Our early calls with both NCM and Screenvision have been very positive. We expect our working relationship with both NCM and Screenvision will be very positive for a long time to come and all these issues that you are raising specifically on the additional NCM shares and what we do with them, I'm sure that this will all move into discussions with NCM and I am expecting that, just as we have a very good relationship today after those discussions are concluded, we will have a very good relationship at that time and think that we can get to a good place for both companies.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And then just one final thing and this maybe is something you can't opine on, but you are going to be selling so much stock, do you have any thoughts about whether that would go to a partner like a Regal or a strategic that might be interested or is it more likely to just go to the broad investing public?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 You know, I actually think that's a question for NCM and not for us. Clearly, we have a say in it because we are the seller, but you are now talking about their securities and who their owners and investors are and become and I think we should limit our comment to saying that we intend to work very closely with NCM to have an orderly transfer of shares to somebody and we will let NCM run its Investor Relations as it thinks most appropriate for its company.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Remember that we do have 2.5 years to get all this done. So while we have to move some theaters in the next 60 days, we don't have to move shares at quite the same rapidity.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. All right, I will leave it there. Thanks a lot, guys.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Greenberg, MNS International.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Greenberg,  MNS International - Analyst   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you for taking my call. I just have a technical question. Last week, I think it was the 14th, was an election deadline for Carmike shareholders to elect for AMC stock or cash as per the merger agreement. That implies I think a close tomorrow. Can you give me any insight on if that deadline is going to be shifted given your comments earlier about a close before the end of the year?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The only comment that I can give you is that we expect the Carmike closing to be imminent.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Greenberg,  MNS International - Analyst   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 James Goss, Barrington Research.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 James Goss,  Barrington Research - Analyst   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks. I was wondering if, Adam, if you are prohibited from increasing your stake in Screenvision or even encouraged by the DOJ to do so?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think they were silent on that question. Their overall goal was to balance our investment in Screenvision and NCM so that we did not have a strong economic incentive to favor one of the advertisers over the other, given that we are going to be a big customer of both. And that's why they were so focused on getting us to sell down our NCM holdings. NCM has a much larger market cap than Screenvision has. So it has not really been on the radar screen.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 James Goss,  Barrington Research - Analyst   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Is there a chance you might move Screenvision into some of the bigger markets, or do you think this bigger/smaller split will continue?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The contract is quite specific. With the exception of the divested theaters, which depends who the buyer is and what they do with the preshow advertising contract, we need to keep the current Screenvision contract in place and the current NCM contract in place. So the theaters that are now NCM theaters stay NCM; the theaters that are now Screenvision theaters stay Screenvision regardless of whether they are in the AMC brand or our additional brand.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 James Goss,  Barrington Research - Analyst   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And finally, now that you will have both Odeon and Carmike, how do you look at the allocation of management and financial resources to each platform?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I love my children equally, but may the best man win. We are in the business, as all companies are, of rationally deploying and allocating capital and we will put our monies where we get the best returns as best we can figure out what they will be. There is opportunity for investment at the AMC circuit. There is opportunity for investment at the Carmike circuit and there is opportunity for investment at the Odeon circuit. I expect that you will see us make improvements at each of the three circuits. Although, as I said on the margin, we ration capital where it produces the highest return and so we look at these projects one at a time, theater by theater.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 James Goss,  Barrington Research - Analyst   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 All right. Thanks very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just one other quick question I forgot to ask. You had mentioned that there would be some tax impact from selling the NCM shares. Can you give us some sense of what your cost base is because I thought a lot of those shares came to you from the IPO or I thought there were taxes paid when you IPOed at $21 a share and NCM is trading less than that. A lot of the other shares I thought came somewhere around where NCM is trading right now, so what would you say is the cost basis that we should be thinking about right now?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Craig Ramsey,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - EVP &amp; CFO   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, we have some low basis shares and we have some high basis shares. Given the 30 months that we have to sell these shares, we will be able to time the transactions in the orderly disposition. We will be able to pick the shares we sell first. First of all, we have a fairly substantial NOL that's available to us to offset any tax. We will utilize high basis shares initially when tax rates are 40% and we will push the sale of low basis shares out into the future and in fact, the remaining 4.99% that we own will probably be very low basis shares. The comment we would make, Barton -- we are just not in a position to give you guidance on an average basis. We think that the tax impact on the disposition of these shares will be nominal because of the NOLs and because of our ability to sell high basis shares at high rates and the prospect of lower tax rates in the future.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Just one other thing, you kept talking about a second brand without saying Carmike specifically. Does that suggest that the second brand could be something different than Carmike?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [47]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I did that on purpose. I will tell you when you will know the answer. We have a meeting at the end of January with all the general managers of our theaters. This year -- of all our US theaters. This year, there will be 650 general managers at that meeting because all of the Carmike managers are now, or post-closing, are AMC managers, and they all will be coming to that meeting and we have decided to unveil the brand name of the second brand at the opening of the GM conference. So there will be some excitement and drama within the Company for our own people and so we will ask our investors to wait until we unveil at the end of January. We do know what we are going to do specifically and how we are going to do it and we are excited about it and we think it will be good for the Company and good for consumers and I will hold you in suspense for a month.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Barton Crockett,  FBR Capital Markets - Analyst   [48]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. I will wait with bated breath. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [49]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 There are no further questions. I would like to hand the call back over to Adam Aron for closing comments.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Adam Aron,  AMC Entertainment Holdings, Inc. - President &amp; CEO   [50]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, everybody, for attending. There are a lot of good movies out. Why don't you take your families to the movies for the holidays? Happy holidays to one and all. Thank you for participating today.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [51]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ladies and gentlemen, this does conclude today's teleconference. Thank you for your participation. You may disconnect your lines at this time and have a wonderful day.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc to Discuss the Department of Justice Approval of the Carmike Cinemas, Inc. Acquisition Conference Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>Columbus</city>
  <companyName>AMC Entertainment Holdings Inc</companyName>
  <companyTicker>AMC</companyTicker>
  <startDate>20-Dec-16 6:15pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>