<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7325241" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 5:00:10pm GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7325241.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:00:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of DOKA.S M&A conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 1:00pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[dormakaba Holding AG To Acquire Mechanical Security Businesses From Stanley Black & Decker Second Call Conference

NEW BRITAIN Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of dormakaba Holding AG M&A conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:00:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Riet Cadonau
      dormakaba Holding AG - CEO
   *  Bernd Brinker
      dormakaba Holding AG - CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Francesca Caramenti
      UBS - Analyst
   *  David MacGregor
      Longbow Research - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning, ladies and gentlemen in North America, and hello to the participants in Europe. It is Riet Cadonau speaking. Thank you for participating in this analyst call. With me here today is our CFO, Bernd Brinker.
 As you have seen, we announced this morning that we agreed with Stanley Black &amp; Decker to acquire the major part of their mechanical solutions businesses. We have issued a comprehensive press release and presentation and I assume you could read it; that's why I will not go through the entire presentation in this call.
 After a short introduction of me and Bernd, we will open the lines for your questions.
 This deal is a very important strategic milestone for us. We'll become a top three player in North America, which is the most profitable market in our industry. The acquisition is in line with our stated strategy and builds on the successful dormakaba merger and the recently completed acquisition of Mesker in North America.
 It will add substantial scale, mainly in North America, and a large installed customer base that will provide us with an attractive repeat business including the possibility for future upgrades. And we will get BEST, one of the most recognized brands in our industry for the last 90 years, as well as established spec writing capabilities that will open access to new construction projects.
 Regarding valuation and finance impact, I would like to hand over to Bernd.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you , Riet. So good morning and good afternoon also from my side here.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sorry to interrupt you. (Operator instructions.) This conversation will be recorded.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I will continue. I would like to give you, again, another brief introduction to the valuation and the financial impact. You have seen that we have agreed on a purchase price, an all-cash consideration, for an enterprise value of $725 million. This is an enterprise value EBITDA multiple, on 2016 basis, of 13.8 times, pre-synergies, which translates into 9 times EBITDA multiple, post expected revenue and cost synergies, as well as expected tax benefits.
 With regard to revenue synergies, we expect cross-selling opportunities and additional revenues by leveraging the BEST brand and the large installed base, which we have already referred to, and we expect to gain scale in attractive additional verticals.
 On the cost synergy side, we also expect some cost synergies from the production footprint optimization from some insourcing of OEM products, as well as from using our shared service function platform.
 In addition, we have tax benefits as they are associated with the deal structure. It's basically the majority is an asset deal structure in the US, and we are able to do stack ups for certain assets, which will give us benefits on the tax side.
 If we balance both benefits and synergies from the cost and revenue synergy side, we expect 50% of the difference between the clean pre-synergy multiple and post synergy multiple. So 50% comes from revenue and cost synergies while the other 50% comes from tax benefits.
 Within cost and revenue synergies, we expect two-third to come from the cost side and one-third to come from the revenue side. At the same time, we expect implementation costs of roughly $15 million, which will accrue over a period of four years with the majority to apply in the year one and the year two.
 The impact on our financials, we expect this to be neutral from closing, and on revenue as well as on EBITDA margin. And we expect an accretion on the EBITDA margin side beginning 2019/2020, so a significant impact from 2019/2020 onwards.
 EPS-wise, we expect that this transaction will be accretive from day one.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. So conclusion for our Group, this acquisition will significantly enhance prospects for further profitable growth. And with that, I would like to ask the operator to open the lines for questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti,  UBS - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti, UBS. I have a quick question on the market share. You said that you will be the top three player and how much in percentage do you expect as market share in US only?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. With regard to US, the two largest players in that market are Assa Abloy and Allegion with 25% market share each, and we will have about half of that, half of 25%, so a very strong top three players play there in US.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti,  UBS - Analyst   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Perfect. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Further questions?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 At the moment I have no further questions. (Operator Instructions). David MacGregor.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David MacGregor,  Longbow Research - Analyst   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 As you approach the US market, clearly a big part of the strategic rationale for this transaction is accessing the US market, as you've indicated. Can you just talk about your priorities as you said about growing your business in the US, specific verticals perhaps, specific geographic regions? And do you have supporting distribution to facilitate that growth?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you for the question. So first of all, in general we continue to focus on commercial, not on residential. That's important to understand. With regard to verticals, as you know dormakaba today is strong in three verticals: hospitality, hotels first; second, multi-housing; and third, government.
 With that acquisition here from Stanley Black &amp; Decker, two additional verticals we will join, which is healthcare, hospitals, as well as education. So we will focus on those five verticals in future, beside commercial in general. Does that answer the question?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David MacGregor,  Longbow Research - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. How's your distribution? Do you have adequate distribution to support your early stage growth plans?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 First of all, distribution in the meaning of direct and indirect? Do you refer to the go-to-market model?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David MacGregor,  Longbow Research - Analyst   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Correct.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Go-to-market is different from product group to product group; I'm going to explain. Hospitality, as an example, is a direct model, while other product sets such as door hardware is normally indirect based. And with that acquisition, we will get a lot of indirect go-to-market power as part of our Company.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David MacGregor,  Longbow Research - Analyst   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 At the moment I have no further questions. (Operator Instructions).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. If there are no further questions, I would like to thank you for participating. If there are further questions, please get in contact with us; I think Schwirzer is available.
 With that, I can wish you Merry Christmas and a successful New Year from here, from Switzerland and, again, all the best and have a great day. Bye-bye.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Bye-bye.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[dormakaba Holding AG To Acquire Mechanical Security Businesses From Stanley Black & Decker Second Call Conference]]></eventTitle>
  <city>NEW BRITAIN</city>
  <companyName>dormakaba Holding AG</companyName>
  <companyTicker>DOKA.S</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 1:00pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>