<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7328508" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 8:05:21pm GMT" eventTypeId="5" eventTypeName="Corporate Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7328508.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:30:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of LXRX conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 1:30pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[Lexicon Pharmaceuticals Inc to Discuss the inTandem2 Phase 3 Top-line Results Conference Call

The Woodlands Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of Lexicon Pharmaceuticals Inc conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:30:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Chas Schultz
      Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - Senior Director of Finance and Communications
   *  Lonnel Coats
      Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO
   *  Pablo Lapuerta
      Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer
   *  Jeff Wade
      Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO
   *  Praveen Tyle
      Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Liana Moussatos
      Wedbush Securities - Analyst
   *  Jessica Fye
      JPMorgan - Analyst
   *  Chris Shibutani
      Cowen and Company - Analyst
   *  Alan Carr
      Needham &amp; Company - Analyst
   *  Yigal Nochomovitz
      Citigroup - Analyst
   *  Stephen Willey
      Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst
   *  Kelly Close
      [Neatrid] - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning. My name is Crystal, and I will be your conference operator today. At this time, I would like to welcome everyone to the Lexicon Pharmaceuticals inTandem2 investor conference call. (Operator Instructions)
 Thank you. I will now turn the conference over to Mr. Chas Schultz. Please go ahead.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chas Schultz,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - Senior Director of Finance and Communications   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Crystal. Good morning and welcome to the Lexicon Pharmaceuticals sotagliflozin inTandem2 Phase 3 top-line results conference call. I am Chas Schultz, and with me today are Lonnel Coats, Lexicon's President and Chief Executive Officer; Dr. Pablo Lapuerta, Lexicon's Executive Vice President and Chief Medical Officer; Dr. Praveen Tyle, Lexicon's Executive Vice President of Research and Development; and Jeff Wade, Lexicon's Executive Vice President of Corporate and Administrative Affairs and Chief Financial Officer.
 We expect that you have seen a copy of the press release that was distributed earlier this morning. If you would like to view the slides for today's call, please access the Lexicon website at www.lexpharma.com. You'll see a link on the homepage for today's webcast.
 Before we begin, I would like to state that we will be making forward-looking statements, including statements related to Lexicon's clinical development of sotagliflozin and telotristat ethyl. These statements may include characterizations of the results of and projected timing of clinical trials of such compounds and the potential therapeutic and commercial potential of such compounds.
 This call may also contain forward-looking statements relating to Lexicon's growth and future operating results, discovery and development of products, strategic alliances, and intellectual property, as well as other matters that are not historical facts or information. Various risks may cause Lexicon's actual results to differ materially from those expressed or implied in such forward-looking statements.
 These risks include uncertainties related to the timing and results of clinical trials and preclinical studies of our drug candidates, our dependence upon strategic alliances, and ability to enter into additional collaboration and license agreements, our ability to obtain patent protection for our discoveries, limitations opposed by patents owned or controlled by third parties, and the requirements of substantial funding to conduct our drug development and commercialization activities. For a list and a description of the risks and uncertainties that we face, please see the results we have filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission.
 I will now turn the call over to Mr. Coats.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, good morning and thank you, Chas. I want to say thank you to all who are joining us this morning. And as always, we start off our calls by thanking the extraordinary men and women here at Lexicon who work every day to advance our science to patients. This is, indeed, an exciting morning for us. It is a major milestone for Lexicon in achieving our second successful pivotal trial for sotagliflozin. It's also a remarkable day for patients for people who are living with Type 1 diabetes. We are excited about these data that we are about to share with you, and again, I will remark on how exciting it is for us as a company to have reached this milestone in being able to achieve now two successful pivotal programs for Type 1 diabetes. We will walk you through the design of this second trial and talk to you about the top-line results and certainly open the phone up for questions that you may have.
 With that being said, I'm going to turn the call over to Dr. Lapuerta to walk you through the design, as well as the results.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you very much, Lonnel. This is an exciting day, and I'm very pleased to share the results with you.
 A word about sotagliflozin. It is a first-in-class dual SGLTI, SGLT2 to inhibitor. As you know, SGLT2 is a major glucose transporter in the kidney. Its inhibition allows the kidney to release glucose in the urine, providing better blood glucose control. It's independent of insulin, but it diminishes with declining renal function. What is unique about sotagliflozin is the SGLT1 inhibition. That occurs in the gastrointestinal tract. It provides reductions of post-prandial glucose and elevates gastrointestinal hormones. The reductions in post-prandial glucose, we believe, are very well suited to helping people who live with Type 1 diabetes.
 Next slide has the Phase 3 program for sotagliflozin for the treatment of Type 1 diabetes. The three main studies are inTandem1, inTandem2, and inTandem3. InTandem1 results have already been reported as successful where sotagliflozin significantly reduced A1C versus placebo with adequate safety.
 Today, I will present to you the results of inTandem2 with the same primary endpoint of focus on A1C reduction versus placebo on optimized insulin. InTandem3 is a large safety study. It's ongoing, and we'll provide results in the middle of 2017.
 Let me review the inTandem2 design and objectives. Slide 6. InTandem2 randomized 782 people, all from Europe and Israel. The primary endpoint is the change in A1C at week 24 that we will share with you today. Patients are randomized to either placebo, 200 or 400 milligrams of sotagliflozin, all on top of optimized insulin therapy. The study was double-blind. It does include some studies which we'll report later on continuous glucose monitoring and on body mass composition.
 The population is one with Type 1 diabetes. Patients entered the study either using insulin pumps or multiple daily injections. They were adults with A1Cs between seven and 11, a glomerular filtration rate greater than 45 and triglyceride less than 600.
 The next slide has the study outline. There was a screening period of two weeks followed by insulin optimization, six weeks which is very important to the execution of this study. Afterwards, patients went on 24 weeks randomized either placebo 200 or 400 milligrams of sotagliflozin, and we are reporting today the 24-week primary endpoint. Patients continued double blinded in the study, and they will receive up to 28 weeks more of treatment for a total of 52 weeks there. So the study is still ongoing.
 Next slide. Optimized insulin therapy is a very important element of the study design. It's a rigorous six-week program. The objective is to improve glycemic control as much as possible to ensure that insulin has been used to its full potential. Patients are then maintained on that optimized insulin, and they're randomized to one of two doses of sotagliflozin or placebo. That review and assurance that insulin has been optimized continues throughout the study period, reviewed by a committee of independent experts providing feedback to investigators. That's why the mean baseline A1C is less than 8% in its study at baseline. It's between 7.7% and 7.8%.
 It's important because it provides an assurance that the efficacy of sotagliflozin in this setting is above and beyond what insulin alone can provide.
 I will now share with you the top-line results of inTandem2. First, the baseline characteristics. The characteristics were well distributed -- evenly distributed among the treatment groups. The mean age was around 40 years. About half the population was male and half female. The population was mostly white, consistent with the demographics of Type 1 diabetes.
 Patients had lived with Type 1 diabetes on average for 18 years. For that amount of time, they still had not been able to overcome the limitations of insulin therapy. Body mass index was 28. The majority of patients were receiving multiple daily injections. They received adequate doses of insulin at about 0.73 to 0.76 units per kilogram, and the population was non-intensive. Next slide.
 The A1C at screening was high. It was above 8%. Intensive optimization of insulin therapy brought it down to 7.7% to 7.8%. At week 24, there were no further reductions of A1C on placebo, but there were additional reductions of sotagliflozin 200 and 400 milligrams bringing patients closer to gold.
 On the next slide, we have the statistics around the primary endpoint. The primary endpoint was meant successfully. These results fully replicate the results of our first pivotal study, inTandem1. There was no significant reduction in A1C during the 24 weeks on placebo. There were significant reductions on both 200 milligrams and 400 milligrams. The placebo subtracted differences were minus .036 with 200 milligrams and minus 0.35 on 400 milligrams. The results were very highly significant. These are clinically meaningful results. These are results in a range that has been recognized as clinically meaningful by regulatory authorities.
 The next slide has the adverse event profile. The safety of sotagliflozin in the study was excellent. The proportion of patients with adverse events was similar between placebos, sotagliflozin 200 and 400 milligrams. The incidences of serious adverse events were very similar, placebo 200 milligrams and 400 milligrams at around 4%. There were not many discontinuations due to adverse events. We did have in this program the first two deaths that have been observed. Those were two deaths. They were both on placebo.
 Adverse events of special interest on the next slide. We have focused previously with inTandem1 on diarrhea and genital mycotic infections. Diarrhea is related to clinical SGLT1 inhibition in the gastrointestinal tract. As in inTandem1, there is an increase in diarrhea with sotagliflozin 400 milligrams compared to placebo.
 This is not a problem of discontinuations. Discontinuation rates due to diarrhea were less than 1%. Genital mycotic infections are increased in the setting of urinary glucose excretion. There was an increase in genital mycotic infections with sotagliflozin compared to placebo. This was not an issue of discontinuation with discontinuation rates to genital mycotic infection of less than 1%.
 The next slide has what's perhaps the most important safety results of this program, a focus on severe hypoglycemia and diabetic ketoacidosis. Severe hypoglycemia rates were very low and similar in placebo sotagliflozin 200 milligrams and sotagliflozin 400 milligrams. Patients were treated safely. It was not an issue for discontinuation. Diabetic ketoacidosis adjudicated by an independent committee showed a low incidence. It was only 1% of sotagliflozin 400 milligrams. It was less than one-half of 1% on sotagliflozin 200 milligrams. We were very pleased with this safety experience.
 In summary, inTandem2 met its primary endpoint. Sotagliflozin significantly reduced A1C, providing efficacy above and beyond optimized insulin therapy. It's the second successful Phase 3 trial for sotagliflozin, the first being inTandem1. The results are entirely consistent with those of inTandem1.
 Together, inTandem2 and inTandem2 are the first successful Phase 3 trials of an oral anti-diabetic for Type 1 diabetes. The profile we are seeing with sotagliflozin in both efficacy and safety is related to its mechanism of action, dual inhibition of SGLT1 and SGLT2. It is consistent in inTandem1 and inTandem2. We have the efficacy beyond what optimized insulin can provide, and we have low rates of severe hypoglycemia as the focus with SGLT1 inhibition has been on post-prandial glucose control.
 We have low rates of DKA with only 1% on 400 milligrams and less than one-half of 1% on 200 milligrams. These results are promising. While the studies are still ongoing to complete a full 52 weeks, the primary endpoints have been met. The safety profile in those first 24 weeks is supported. We've see an important opportunity, and we have greater confidence that we will be able to support the first regulatory filings for an oral agent for the treatment of Type 1 diabetes.
 Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Dr. Lapuerta. Appreciate that very much. As I said before, we are remarkably pleased with these results. As Dr. Lapuerta has said, this is the first oral anti-diabetic agent to be able to show statistical significance against optimized insulin with a low rate of side effects, unmanageable rate of side effects, so the balance is there. We believe that balance will allow us to be able to begin to have conversations with our partner and begin our strategy around registration.
 So we are remarkably thrilled. This is a remarkable moment in the history of Lexicon to start this program and to have executed extremely well, very efficiently, and then very appropriately to be able to deliver these results that we have shared with you today.
 With that being said, we will go from this point forward and have more dialogue with our partner, Sanofi, and come up with our regulatory planning and strategy. Because, at this point, we have achieved successes in both programs, pivotal programs, and believe that it can support regulatory filing.
 I will stop there and open the lines up for the questions from our audience.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions) Liana Moussatos, Wedbush Securities.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Congratulations and thank you for taking my question. I think the number one thing that investors tell me they want to know is, what are the sequence of events and the timing that you can let the Street know that the FDA has decided whether or not to accept an NDA just for Type 1 given the inTanden3 data midyear and finishing inTandem2 long-term extension and then meeting with FDA and waiting for the minutes? So what kind of timing and events should we expect?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana, I think that's a very good question. I'm going to turn that one over to Jeff.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, we have had two pivotal studies, both meeting the primary endpoint and demonstrating what we believe to be a favorable balance of safety and efficacy. So that opens up the opportunity for us to have a dialogue with our partner, and we could have had an ongoing dialogue about this and then with the regulatory agencies. We would expect to have a dialogue -- that dialogue to happen the first half of next year while we are completing the Phase 3 program. As you know, both of the pivotal studies have a 52-week total duration, so they will be continuing through the first half of next year or so. And the third safety study is -- we would have data from the middle of next year. So our plan at this point is to have those -- have that dialogue during the time that we are wrapping up the Phase 3 program and to be in a position should that dialogue be favorable to be prepared to file once the full program is ready to go, which wouldn't probably be before the early 2018 timeframe.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (inaudible - microphone inaccessible)
 Well, I think as we go to the process and make decisions, we will provide updates as to where we are in that process.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, what I can say to that point: I think these results excites us all, and I think -- as we align with our partners, we approached the agency I think with a little bit more timely than I think what we may have originally thought through. And, therefore, we should be able to give some guidance -- to Jeff's point, we will be able to give some guidance as we get into -- beyond the first quarter of next year. So I think we have some great results here, and I think we are going to line around the approach with the agency, and that will be sooner than later.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 When you say guidance beyond the first quarter of next year, you mean 2017?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 2017, yes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And you are going to let the Street know through a press release about submitting an NDA or before that after you meet with FDA and get the minutes back or FDA acceptance for review? Which one of those do you think that you would let us know?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think as we get additional data from the program, it will also give us the opportunity to update us in terms of our strategy. So we will have additional data in 2017 from this program, and there will be some natural opportunities for us to update as to our plans and as we go forward with the registration process.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. Liana, we're not being cagey, but we try to align with our partners on timing so that we are pretty much aligned around what guidance we give between both companies.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you very much and congratulations again.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye, JPMorgan.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hey, I wanted to talk a little bit about now that you have the second page story here, your latest thoughts on 200 versus 400. When I look at this data, it looks like 200 is clearly more tolerable or safe from a DKA standpoint. And it's unclear to me just how much of an efficacy benefit 400 is really adding, particularly without more information on time and target glucose range and that kind of stuff. But you are generating all the safety data at 400. It's -- to the extent that 200 ends up looking like the most viable dose, is there a possibility that you would need to generate more safety data at that dose, or are you kind of covered because you've got it at the higher 400?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So our expectation would be that we would be covered because we have safety data at the higher dose. We're obviously very pleased with the safety and efficacy for the 200 milligram dose. And you hit on the relevant question, which is before we really make any final determination about what we want to do with these two doses, we also want to see the data relating to time and range and other key secondary endpoints. So clearly the 200 milligram dose in this study as in the inTandem1 performed very well on both safety and efficacy.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And to the extent that we do see a rate of DKA that's a little higher than we want to see or that we want to move forward with the 400, acknowledging that that data will exist, will you then be in a position that you need to put 200 more patients to really prove out that it is lower than 400 on DKA? Does that make sense?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think we have -- really, we have fully characterized the safety and efficacy of this compound in this target population through these two pivotal studies. What we're really trying to do with the additional safety study is to get additional safety exposure broadly, and I think we will have that that study will succeed in that effort.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Got it. And just -- maybe a little bit of comparing your cross studies here, but it looked like in inTandem1, acting both arms had a lower rate of severe hypoglycemia relative to placebo, which is pretty encouraging here. It looks like it may be a little bit more of a wash. And how should we think about the overall profile of this product as it relates to severe hypoglycemia? Should we think about it as having a benefit or just no detriment?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great question, Jessica. As you know, this trial was created to be able to show that we can achieve an efficacy benefit beyond optimized insulin alone without increasing severe hypoglycemia as well as other safety events.
 With that being said, we think we have achieved that, but I will turn it over to Dr. Lapuerta to add any other color to it if he likes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, these rates are low with no increase in severe hypoglycemia. I think to get a full understanding of the potential for hypoglycemia, it would be very helpful for us to have continuous glucose monitoring data where we see the amount of time patients stay in the proper range.
 However, I can say that it is very positive to be able to provide this A1C efficacy without any increase in severe hypoglycemia. It's actually unusual, and this is a first in Type 1 diabetes to be able to do that. You can't do that with insulin. Trying to do this with insulin, you can get lower A1Cs, but that's the barrier to control. It is the severe hypoglycemia. That's why patients in this program had lived with Type 1 diabetes for 18 years and were unable to achieve target goals. They could not overcome the limitations of insulin, and in this study, they made important progress in doing that without severe hypoglycemia. So, overall, we're looking forward to learning more from continuous glucose monitoring data, which we will report out later, but we are pleased with this profile and these incidences of severe hypoglycemia.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Got it. And maybe just one last one on DKA. Do you know if the events in the study were patients who were on pumps or not, and can you remind us how to think about the mix of pumps versus multiple daily injections for the larger safety study?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I will take that one over to Jeff.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So it was predominantly -- as we have seen in the past, we are seeing it's more on pumps than on placebo. I mean more on pumps than on multiple daily injection just generally in the program. That is what is consistent in this study as well. So that's going to be something that we continue to learn from the data about what can we do to mitigate that. But it is predominantly on the pump side.
 In terms of the inTandem3, so the inTandem1 was a US -- mostly US study, North American study and had about 60% pumps, 40% multiple daily injections. This study had about 25% pumps, but 75% multiple daily injections. InTandem3 is a global study, so it has sites in North America and in Europe in some other countries. So we would expect it to be somewhere in between those two in terms of proportion of pumps versus multiple daily injections.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, Jessica. While the DKA rates are low and we are pleased how well the drug has performed, we need to understand better why are we seeing the incidence rate with pump use, and that is just going to take some time for us to go through and catalog every patient to understand that a little bit better. So we can better be able to inform when it happens, why it happens, and how best we mitigate that risk. So while we have low rates, I think we can continue to work to reduce those rates as we understand more about why is it happening with pump use.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, that seems like a pretty easy to identify population. I guess based on the geographic mix you are enrolling in inTandem3, do you expect it to be closer to the 60% pumps or closer to 25%?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think it's going to be pretty much somewhere between. It's not going to be close to either one of those. It's going to be pretty much in between.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thanks, guys.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I don't know exactly, though.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Fye,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Shibutani, Cowen.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Shibutani,  Cowen and Company - Analyst   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks very much. Congratulations on the data updates. Can you talk to us a little bit about some of the other secondary endpoints either from this European study or what you know so far from the US study that you reported almost three months ago now? In particular with regard to weight and weight loss, it's a point of differentiation potentially from when we have spoken with KOLs. Can you comment about what you are seeing and, if not yet, when we can expect to see that data?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I will turn that question over to Dr. Tyle.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris, the other secondary endpoints besides the primary endpoint we reported today are net benefit, body weight, bolus insulin dose, and fasting plasma glucose, and we also have a couple of qualitative questionnaires being done at secondary endpoints, besides the two subsidies which Dr. Lapuerta talked about.
 Our goal is to report that at the end of the study after the 52-week period, so sometime towards the middle of next year.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 But I think, Chris, one of the things that's important and as we have been reporting additional studies as we've gone along, we don't have the data from the pivotal studies, but we have shown consistently across multiple studies weight loss relative to placebo in patients treated with sotagliflozin. And we, frankly, believe that that is part of the profile that (inaudible) expect from this.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, Chris, we just don't have this data collected and cleaned yet, and that study is not reporting yet.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Shibutani,  Cowen and Company - Analyst   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And then to follow up on the DKA, obviously one of the concerns with the Type 1 patients is the incidence of euglycemic DKA, and I think you provided us with some measures in the past of the patients who had DKA, but had glucoses less than 250 and less than 150. Could you perhaps provide us with that similar update from the European study you just reported this morning?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Dr. Tyle?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris, we have not dug that data deeper simply because these patients are already ongoing in this study, so we have not unblinded that portion of the database.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Chris Shibutani,  Cowen and Company - Analyst   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Alan Carr, Needham and Company.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Alan Carr,  Needham &amp; Company - Analyst   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi. Congratulations. Thanks for taking my questions. Can you comment more on the discontinuations? You mentioned what some of them were tied to. Can you fill us in on some of the other ones for this trial?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I will turn that question over to Dr. Lapuerta.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Discontinuations were due to a range of factors. There was no single pattern that stood out. One of the things that I mentioned in discussing the adverse events is there were two deaths on placebo. These patients discontinued. One died of lung cancer, and one appeared to have a sudden cardiovascular death that is still being adjudicated.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Alan Carr,  Needham &amp; Company - Analyst   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And then with respect to Tandem or inTandem3, the 1400-patient trial, Jeff, what do you know about the baseline characteristics in that trial other than you mentioned that pump use was somewhere in between the other two? But is there anything else you know about baseline characteristics for that trial that might give us a sense of what to look for when those results are announced middle of the year, baseline A1C, that sort of thing?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jeff Wade,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, Corporate and Administrative Affairs and CFO   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 It's a similar population range of A1C as with the two pivotal studies, the 7 to 11. The main difference from a design perspective is that we're not doing the insulin optimization. So I think that you are -- we are going to expect to see a range of patients coming into the study that is in that same 7 to 11 range that we've had in two pivotal studies just without driving down the A1C before baseline.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Alan Carr,  Needham &amp; Company - Analyst   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Thanks very much and congratulations again.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [47]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz, Citigroup.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [48]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks for taking the question. Congrats on the results. On inTandem2, can you just clarify why you decided not to implement insulin optimization, and also given that that is how you are doing the study, are you expecting to see larger A1C drops with sotagliflozin in that one versus inTandem1 and inTandem2? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [49]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, Yigal, this is Praveen. You know, the primary goal of doing inTandem3 study is really to collect more safety data. Actually our primary endpoint is not even reduction of A1C, but it is the net benefit which has the component of A1C.
 So, like we have discussed earlier, the reason we are doing this safety study is to comply with the ICH guidance in terms of exposure. And we want to do this as a real-life study rather than in patients where we want to see the effectiveness of sotagliflozin after insulin has been optimized. So this will provide really real-life study for safety purposes, and it is more or less for registration.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [50]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So one of the things, Yigal, that you are going to hear us talk more about in the next few months is this net benefit design, which looks at the ability to reduce insulin and do that in a safe way without increasing severe hypoglycemia and DKA. So Praveen, why don't you talk a little bit about net benefit and that overall design?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [51]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, Yigal, the net benefit which is also a secondary endpoint in our two pivotal trials has three components to it. The three components are patients who will achieve an A1C below 7% at the end of the study with no DKA and no severe hypoglycemia. So it will basically provide a numerical number -- a quantitative number for patients who have achieved benefits and with no safety adverse events, and we will compare the advantages between placebo and the active arms. So it will essentially say, hey, who are the people who are able to achieve their goal of reducing A1C with no safety event, especially severe hypoglycemia and DKA. So we will be talking about these numbers from all these three studies inTandem1, 2, and 3 as 2017 unfolds.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [52]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. But just so I'm -- I guess what I was driving at, just so I'm clear: it wouldn't be an unreasonable expectation that given that you are not optimizing the insulin in a real-world setting, that you would expect sotagliflozin to give you more reduction on A1C. Is that a fair assumption?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [53]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, if you look at the data from inTandem2 which Dr. Lapuerta reported just a few minutes ago, the difference between baseline and screening was approximately a reduction of 0.6% A1C. So, if you don't optimize insulin, we can potentially see that perhaps the A1C might be a little bit more higher than the bottom line between baseline and end of the study.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [54]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, Yigal, I think the design of that study, as Dr. Tyle has mentioned, is to give us the exposure. But I think we will have efficacy data to be able to show in a real-world setting sotagliflozin should perform extremely well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [55]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And then a few other questions. Are you -- what is your current thinking on whether the FDA is going to want to convene any kind of advisory panel to discuss the data next year or, I guess, in 2018?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [56]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal, that's a great question. Don't know. That's the whole point of sitting down with, I think, our partners and having a good conversation sooner than later with the agency and trying to get clarity around those kinds of things. But I think right now what we have shown is the tremendous benefit relative to risk and believe we have every opportunity to expect to have some success in not moving the regulators.
 What method they will use to try to understand this better, we won't know that until we have those meetings.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [57]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And just on the safety profile, maybe Dr. Lapuerta could just comment. In inTandem2 and I guess for inTandem1 as well, how were the patients with the DKAs managed? Were they taken off the trial? Was there a dose reduction? Can you just clarify how that works? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [58]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, we allotted the decision on this to be up to the investigator and the patients as to whether or not they continue. And if there were a couple of discontinuations that I showed on the slide on DKA -- on the 400 milligram dose, but other patients stayed in the program and continued, and they did well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [59]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, and then finally, on Type 2, obviously there's been some postings on clintrials for the Type 2 program. Any comments on when we can learn more about what Sanofi -- how Sanofi is going to approach that strategy?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [60]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's a great question. I'll only say that we are -- we couldn't be more excited with Sanofi and how they are thinking about Type 2. I also say that they are very excited with these results as well.
 So I would say stay tuned. I think Sanofi is going to have a lot more to say. We're not going to try to say it for them, but I think they have a lot more to say in the very near term here about that program, that Type 2 program. So stay tuned, I would say.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz,  Citigroup - Analyst   [61]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thanks very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [62]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey, Stifel.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [63]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (inaudible) and congrats on the data. Just a quick question on the insulin optimization. Does that generally result in an overall increase in the total daily insulin dose?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [64]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Dr. Lapuerta?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [65]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, it does. As patients get into the program, it's more common to increase the insulin rather than to back off from it.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [66]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And is insulin optimization continuing in the inTandem1 and inTandem2 patients for the remainder of the follow-up through 52 weeks?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [67]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, it is. I would describe it as a maintenance. The insulin dosing is still being reviewed. The large optimization effort is in those first six weeks, and then there's maintenance and that the expert committee reviews changes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [68]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And then the sub study data, the CGM and [sat mass], is that being collected through 24 weeks only?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [69]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. Actually I believe the sat mass may be a later endpoint. I will have to check on that. It may be 52 weeks because it provides information on bone density as well. So that was one of our interests with body compensation. We're getting both bone density and lean body mass and sat mass.
 One last thing asking about insulin. I think the evidence of optimization is a mean total daily insulin in terms of units per kilogram, and that was between 0.73 and 0.76. That is very good. It shows adequate insulin for this population. We often think of about 0.6 when we think about the insulin needs of some Type 2 diabetes. And we have evidence that patients are getting above that. And we also have evidence that from screening to baseline, there was an improvement in A1C. It's because the insulin use went up.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [70]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And then you have previously insinuated that the complete data from these two pivotals could be most likely presented, I guess, at ADA in June. So just wondering if we should expect to see the sub study data as part of that presentation, and I'm presuming that you will have 52-week follow-up data from at least inTandem1 at that point. Is there a possibility that that also gets included within that presentation?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [71]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Actually, Steve, the deadlines for submitting that duration data don't really -- we don't have time to do that with ADA because the deadlines will be cut off before we would have the full data. We may actually have some of that data sort of midyear, but we wouldn't have the opportunity to present the 52-week data at ADA. It would end up being a later scientific conference.
 We will have some presentations. We do expect to have some presentations at ADA from the data from this program, but just not that duration data will be available in time to the conference.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [72]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Understood. And then just lastly, just kind of going back to the dose selection conversation. I guess I understand the context of it, but if you look at the inTandem4 data and you see that the 400 milligrams is essentially giving you almost a doubling in post-prandial glucose reduction versus the 200 dose and ultimately the benefit of this drug is on glycemic variability, not on A1C, I guess how is 400 not the go forward dose in Type 1? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [73]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think we're going to look at the overall safety efficacy across a bunch of parameters. It may also be the different patients would benefit from different doses. And you mentioned that the effect from the other study on post-prandial glucose -- we're going to want to see the glycemic variability data that we are generating as part of the CGM sub study. As we go forward and think about what decisions we make with that dose and then there's also as you probably remember as well, there was quite profound effect on blood pressure as well with the 400 milligram dose. We have a good effect on 200 as well, but 400 -- more of an effect. So I think that all of those factors will be evaluated once we have a complete data set in terms of how we think about the dose selection.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [74]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, I think the great news for us, we know we have our minimally effective dose, and I think that's great news with 200. We will be examining 400 and its application on all these secondary measures to make sure that the A1C that we are achieving is high-quality A1C. We're going to look at all the variables to make sure we know that.
 This is going to be -- and I have said this before. What excites me is that this is going to be the largest Type 1 trial ever for an oral antidiabetic agent. We will have more data than anybody else, and we will be able to give clear guidance and direction as we complete these trials going into the mid-part of next year on all of these secondary measures to look at the quality of the A1C that we are delivering with sotagliflozin.
 And then we will find that balance between 200 and 400. Today, in these pivotal programs, we know one thing for sure, which is what the agency likes from a regulatory standpoint is we have a minimally effective dose that is characterized both on efficacy and safety. We will look at the rest of it and determine how we go forward based on that data and what's the optimal opportunity for us to approach the regulatory agency for filing.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Praveen Tyle,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP, R&amp;D   [75]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I believe you had asked about the CGM and body mass data. I want to confirm what Pablo was saying earlier, which is the CGM data is up to 24 weeks, but the body mass data and bone density data, we are collecting up to 52 weeks. That's why the data won't be available until the end of the study.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stephen Willey,  Stifel Nicolaus - Analyst   [76]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Understood. Thanks for taking the questions.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [77]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos, Wedbush Securities.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [78]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 What other medical conferences would you present data besides ADA? Are there any in the first half and which ones in the second half that -- or maybe Q4 that you could present the longer-term data?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [79]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana, great question. We will give more guidance around those as we work with Sanofi because they also are working through how they want to discuss and talk about Type 2 program. And so once we have aligned around -- now we have these data and have those conversations, we will align around strategically where we would start to put our data. Those conversations are ongoing, and we will finalize them. So, when we know that, we will certainly speak back out to the Street.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liana Moussatos,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [80]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [81]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 [Kelly Close], [Neatrid].
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Kelly Close,  [Neatrid] - Analyst   [82]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning and I joined the call a little bit late, so you might have spoken to this already. But I just wanted to say congratulations. Type 1s have never really had anything that's easy to take to add to their daily management, and that will be easy for their positions. And I was just wondering if you could talk a little bit about what the reactions of patients have been. I mean people know -- people must know who are on it. And then also if they -- if any of them have seen the data -- the CGM data, 2.5 hours more in the zone is really meaningful. That was from the data that you shared with us on the last trial. And I'm wondering if you could talk about that? I don't know if you talked about the timing zone data on today's news yet. So, thank you very much, again, for all that you are doing.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [83]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Kelly. We have not talked about the time and the range data for these trials because we are collecting all of that data, and we will report that out data. But, from a patient point of view, I will let Dr. Lauerta talk about that as he has done a lot of good work here to make sure we collect patient experiences.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [84]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We don't have any formal data on patient experiences. We have general feedback from sites, and we've had some of their actions previously with patients who took sotagliflozin for the treatment of Type 1 diabetes, and the feedback has been very positive. It's been very encouraging and has really inspired us. I think the main thing that we hear is that patients see a better glucose profile throughout the day.
 And one patient put it this way. He said, before I took sotagliflozin, my glucose profile throughout the day and after meals and between meals was like mountains and canyons. He said, now, with sotagliflozin, it's like hills and valleys. And I think what was really is most prominent is the reduction of these mountains -- to go from mountains where you have a meal and you have a big spike in glucose to just a reasonable hill where there is only a modest elevation in glucose after a meal. It provides a lot of peace of mind. It simplifies the management of diabetes, and that's the thing that patients have spoken to us most about. It's been very positive.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [85]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Dr. Lapuerta, I know we have added in some interview questions into this design. Can you talk a little bit about that?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Pablo Lapuerta,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - EVP and Chief Medical Officer   [86]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We have two instruments in inTandem1 and also in inTandem2, and the two treatments are the diabetes treatment satisfaction questionnaire. We are looking forward to having those results. We haven't viewed them yet. And, indeed, the other one is the diabetes stress questionnaire. A two question version.
 One of the things that we will get from that is a sense of the stress and the issues of managing Type 1 diabetes and in particular the concerns with the fear of hypoglycemia. And the two instruments together will cover concerns that patients have about hypoglycemia and hyperglycemia as well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [87]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Dr. Lapuerta.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Kelly Close,  [Neatrid] - Analyst   [88]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks very much. The patient (technical difficulty)
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [89]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Kelly.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Kelly Close,  [Neatrid] - Analyst   [90]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 -- is an increase of one-third. One-third more of the target rates. That is unbelievable. And so we -- I know that I speak for many patients when I say I think it is so great that you can give FDA this data and get us beyond thinking about only A1C.
 So, thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [91]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Kelly. Thank you very much for your commentary.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [92]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 At this time, there are no further questions in queue.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Lonnel Coats,  Lexicon Pharmaceuticals, Inc. - President and CEO   [93]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, I will conclude and say thank you for all who have called in this morning. I will just close again by saying how exciting this is for Lexicon, but more importantly I think Kelly just closed out her commentary the best way for us to end. This is about patients. This is about people living with Type 1 diabetes and how can we as an innovator improve the lives of patients and people living with Type 1 diabetes. And I think today, we are closer to having impact in that regard than ever before. And we have a strong commitment to working with our partners to do everything we can to meet with regulators and make this become a reality in the marketplace.
 So, thank you for joining us and look forward to having more conversations with you as we go forward.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [94]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 This concludes today's conference call. You may now disconnect.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[Lexicon Pharmaceuticals Inc to Discuss the inTandem2 Phase 3 Top-line Results Conference Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>The Woodlands</city>
  <companyName>Lexicon Pharmaceuticals Inc</companyName>
  <companyTicker>LXRX</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 1:30pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>