<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7332866" lastUpdate="Tuesday, December 27, 2016 at 8:02:45pm GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7332866.F" expirationDate="Thursday, December 22, 2016 at 7:30:00am GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of TNET.BR M&A conference call or presentation 22-Dec-16 7:30am GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[Telenet Group Holding NV Acquisition SFR BeLux Call

Mechelen Dec 27, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of Telenet Group Holding NV M&A conference call or presentation Thursday, December 22, 2016 at 7:30:00am GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Rob Goyens
      Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR
   *  John Porter
      Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO
   *  Birgit Conix
      Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Paul Sidney
      Credit Suisse - Analyst
   *  Stefaan Genoe
      Degroof Petercam - Analyst
   *  Joost van der Sluis
      Kempen &amp; Co. - Analyst
   *  Roshan Ranjit
      Deutsche Bank - Analyst
   *  Vikram Karnany
      UBS - Analyst
   *  Michael Bishop
      Goldman Sachs - Analyst
   *  Frank Knowles
      New Street Research - Analyst
   *  Guy Peddy
      Macquarie Research - Analyst
   *  Nawar Cristini
      JPMorgan - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good day and welcome to the Telenet conference call on the acquisition of SFR Belgium and Luxembourg. Today's conference is being recorded.
 At this time, I would like to turn the call over to Mr. Rob Goyens. Please go ahead.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rob Goyens,  Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, operator, and good morning, everyone. We are thankful for your flexibility this morning and having been able to join this call despite the relatively short time frame. I trust you all received our press release this morning regarding the acquisition of SFR's activities in Belgium and Luxembourg.
 With me on this call are our CEO, John Porter; and our CFO, Birgit Conix. As far as the protocol of today's call is concerned, both John and Birgit will walk you through the proposed transaction, after which we will open it up for Q&amp;A. And all three of us will be available to take your questions later on.
 Before we start, as usual, however, I'm obliged to advise you that certain statements in this conference call are forward-looking statements. These may include statements regarding our expectations with respect to SFR's Belgian and Luxembourg's 2016 adjusted EBITDA; the costs, benefit, and impacts on the proposed acquisition, including annual run rate synergies, one-off investments, and integration costs; but also the impact of the transactional [now] operations and financial performance, and other information and statements that are not historical fact. For more details on these factors, we refer to the Safe Harbor disclaimer which you can find at the end of our press release.
 With that, let me now hand over to our CEO, John Porter, for the highlights concerning this acquisition.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Rob, and good morning, everyone. This is a big day for us; just celebrated our 20th anniversary as a company. But I think this transaction has reared its head about once every two or three years across that whole 20-year period. Well, we're pretty excited to be able to extend our footprint outside of our core Flemish cable network and, more significantly, into Brussels with some critical mass, getting us to two-thirds of total of the Brussels region.
 And on top of that, we have -- there are commune in Wallonia and Luxembourg; and a couple of Flemish communes, including Wemmel, which is also -- has a huge potential for us. The strategic rationale is pretty straightforward. Nothing succeeds like buying the cable system next door, at that's exactly what we've done here. It's a very digestible transaction, with 280,000 homes passed in Belgium and Luxembourg, but just over 100,000 unique customer relationships. So, plenty of upside in the footprint.
 At the same time, we will become active in 60 [new] municipalities in Brussels, with us then covering, as I mentioned, two-thirds of the Brussels region and becoming the capital's largest cable operator.
 We are also building up some scale in Wallonia, and we'll become active outside of our home country for the first time through SFR's Luxembourg-based operations. More importantly, we are also achieving a bigger geographical overlap between our cable plant and the nationwide BASE mobile network which we acquired back in February.
 In fact, an interesting statistic here says 30% of our total out-of-footprint mobile subs are in the SFR footprint, which is going to support both our fixed line and our mobile business as we work successfully towards an FMC strategy in the former SFR region.
 So let's focus a little bit on the financials and the implied value. Today it's EUR400 million acquisition. [Buy these] SFR Benelux at 6.5 times 2016 EBITDA, including projected run rate synergies. We believe this reflects an attractive forward-looking multiple compared to current trading multiples for most cable companies, including Telenet.
 And, with that, let me hand it over to Birgit for some financial highlights, which we will follow up with some Q&amp;A.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Tom, and good morning to all of you on the call. The proposed annual run rate synergies of EUR16 million by 2021 which John just mentioned are quite evenly split between, firstly, incremental EBITDA derived from revenue-related synergies such as being able to introduce attractive quad-play offers and also getting more scope on the B2B side; and secondly, cost-related synergies, including, amongst others, the benefits of a running an extended operation in Brussels.
 Now, in order to be able to offer an amazing customer experience over the acquired cable network and to be able to effectively compete for market share, we plan to invest around EUR12 million in the acquired network over the next two years, above the normalized CapEx run rate of around 24% to revenue.
 In addition, we will also incur one-time integration costs of around EUR4 million. We intend to finance this acquisition through a combination of existing cash and cash equivalents on the hand, and the draw-down of available liquidity under our revolving credit facilities on the other hand.
 Today we have full access to EUR520 million of available commitments under our revolving credit facilities, of which EUR400 million is only maturing in June 2023.
 So, with that, let me hand over to Q&amp;A -- and to the operator for Q&amp;A.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions). Paul Sidney, Credit Suisse.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Paul Sidney,  Credit Suisse - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I just have three questions, please. Firstly, interested in the timing, I don't think anyone's really doubted the strategic logic of the potential deal. But can we just get some [insight] on why the timing is right now? And is it simply price, or is it something else?
 And secondly, do you see a path to further improving your footprint going forward into Wallonia and the rest of Brussels, either on a municipality-by-municipality basis, or perhaps even an acquisition of [the whole of] VOO?
 And just thirdly, could I just check the 90,000? Is that 90,000 cable households and not products? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I'll answer the last one first, because that's a quick one. That's distinct customers; they have a very high penetration of triple play, just under 50%. That gives us confidence that their network is in decent condition, because they are marketing a 200 megabit per second broadband solution in their triple play. I think because of their high triple play penetration their RGUs as a function of those customers is about -- it's a little bit under 2.5. I think it's, like, 2.3 or 2.2. So, their RGUs would be obviously more than double.
 In terms of our timing, I think it's fair to say that we've looked at this asset, up one side and down the other, for the last decade. All of the transactions [mooted] previously, the price was north of the price that we paid. Now, you could say that, okay, if you wait longer maybe the price is going to go down, because it hasn't really been competing that successfully with Proximus in its core region.
 The issue is you -- there's probably two lines that intersect. One is price and the other is quality. So you really don't want the asset to diminish in quality to the point where, yes, it's cheaper; but you are unrecoverable from a quality standpoint, from a customer relationship standpoint, and from a brand standpoint. So we felt that those two lines intersected right at the price that we paid.
 It is not a Telenet, but it is not a poor quality network. Like I said, there are a lot of indications that it would lead us to believe that it's a decent quality. With a little TLC and focus, we think -- and clearly you can see there's massive penetration upside potential in the numbers that we presented -- that this is the right time to do the transaction.
 And also because the scope of this thing is not huge; it represents about 4% of Telenet's installed base. So we're pretty confident that we won't miss a beat integrating this business into Telenet's business, into the new Telenet Group business.
 In terms of our further ambitions into Wallonia or even Brussels, I think we've been -- clearly stated that see ourselves as a national player. This was a transaction which we always felt we could get done at the right price. VOO is much more complex. But like I've said before, we continue to stay close to VOO. We work with them on a number of different levels. There is a potential, down the road, to do more things together.
 On a commercial basis, and if they ever decide that they wanted to sell the asset, we would be in position A. So, we will see where that all goes. And like I said, our ambition is to essentially have a quad-play footprint, FMC footprint, across the whole country. But the next step is going to be (multiple speakers).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Paul Sidney,  Credit Suisse - Analyst   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stefaan Genoe, Degroof Petercam.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stefaan Genoe,  Degroof Petercam - Analyst   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Two further questions. You indicated the [upside indeed] on the RGUs and then the triple play. On the B2B, with being the business operated in the Brussels region, do you see more B2B potential than your average within the Telenet scope? And did they already serve some of the small office, home office, or the family offices?
 And then secondly in terms of synergies, you do indicate 50% sales, 50% costs. Could you give us some indications on the cost synergies? It's also French-speaking parts, so not a Telenet-based language, I would say. So there should be also some additional costs, so could you give some more color there? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, let me answer the B2B question. B2B is very much a part of the investment thesis of this acquisition. The city of Brussels, which is where most of the government activity, large enterprise; but also small-medium is very, very underserved by the cable companies. Our B2B business has been growing low-double-digit for the last few years. We think we bring a lot of unique products and services and omni-channel sales capability to the B2B market.
 So, it's very, very much a part of our -- it will be a part of our strategy to try to leverage the B2B opportunity. And there is some B2B -- I think very conservative B2B revenues in the synergy assumptions.
 You want to talk about the synergies?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, okay. So on the synergies, so the cost for the total synergies are EUR16 million, as I mentioned earlier; and, indeed, 50% revenue-driven, 50% costs. And then the costs, to give you some examples based on, like, marketing; it's one brand; also backbone integration, not consolidation. We also will have some procurement savings, as we always -- I mean continuously do. And then also some limited FTE reductions that would -- that would be half of the total EUR16 million.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stefaan Genoe,  Degroof Petercam - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And perhaps one final question in terms of current positioning in terms of pricing. You mentioned Proximus has been quite aggressive in the area. Do you believe they are well positioned today in terms of pricing? (multiple speakers)
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, they're not -- they haven't really gone to market with a fresh challenge or strategy, although the perception is that they are. But I think their ARPU is, like I said, a pretty strong triple-play penetration of their existing customer base. So, I think it's very manageable.
 We do feel that ultimately we will harmonize pricing with Telenet. That's part of the strategy. And we're not that far out of the ballpark for us to be able to do that. So I'm pretty confident that -- we compete with Proximus fairly well with a slight premium to Proximus. So we think that over time, we will -- it's very manageable. I don't know if that answers your question.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Stefaan Genoe,  Degroof Petercam - Analyst   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Yes, that's clear. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joost van der Sluis, Kempen.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joost van der Sluis,  Kempen &amp; Co. - Analyst   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Two questions from my side, please. First on the top line, what do you see -- currently the top-line trends for SFR; and how do you see that evolving going forward? And secondly, is it correct to assume that you will introduce that Telenet brand in the SFR footprint?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, I think to get the synergies we are looking for over time, we will definitely be introducing the Telenet brand. The Telenet brand is not as strong in the South as it is in the North, but there's very much -- there is at least a perception that it's affordable quality. So, on the car scale, it's a BMW 320. It's acceptable, but it does represent quality. We're confident that we can use the Telenet brand. The Telenet brand has been used in Brussels, and the communes are -- will give us a more contiguous footprint in Brussels. So there's no reason not to (technical difficulty) the Telenet brand.
 In terms of top-line growth, Birgit is going to (multiple speakers) that one?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, so the revenue has been declining due to competition and less focus on customer service and migrations out of footprint. So we do see revenue synergies, as we mentioned earlier. So when we look at the plan, so the first year still, it will be somewhat in decline, the revenue. But then as of 2018, we project to have revenue growth and substantial revenue growth, and also synergies kicking in, et cetera. So 2017, we will not see that; it will still be a decline in (technical difficulty).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joost van der Sluis,  Kempen &amp; Co. - Analyst   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And maybe one follow-up question. Do you see some more upside in terms of the base synergies? I can imagine that you have more offloading of mobile data in the SFR region. Or is it already included in the cost synergies of the SFR deal?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We don't have -- it's more revenue synergies, so it's more being able to offer WIGO FMC type solutions. We've been quite successful in Flanders in -- successful; I mean, we've been cannibalizing the BASE customers and bringing them into a Telenet FMC product. We see some very strong potential revenue upside in putting the fixed and wireless networks together on a solution for the customers in Brussels.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rob Goyens,  Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think also in addition to that, as John mentioned earlier as well, so 30% of the current of footprint subscribers of BASE has grown; meaning those who are not currently within our cable network reach. And they are actually in SFR's network area, so they are all already on the BASE network so that things from a synergy perspective -- we don't have to migrate these customers from the MVNO because they are already on the BASE network.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Joost van der Sluis,  Kempen &amp; Co. - Analyst   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, that's clear. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Roshan Ranjit, Deutsche Bank.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Roshan Ranjit,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just a quick question on the CapEx side. Now, you have earmarked EUR12 million investment in the CapEx, I think. John, you mentioned maybe the fixed infrastructure wasn't compatible to the Telenet network. Now, does this investment include the level of quality to your existing fixed upgrade program which you've got running in the rest of your network here in Flanders? Or will that potentially require further investment? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No, that's our initial crack at getting the network to the [XXL, or grow to network for what we should call it here] standard. So we will get it up to 1 gig of capacity; and ultimately with the 3.1, et cetera, it will be potential for 1 gig of speed. They actually have -- because it's a very dense network in Brussels; we got a lot of homes passed per kilometer -- it doesn't seem that expensive, I guess, EUR12 million to get the network up to speed. But that's our first crack at it. And we're pretty confident maybe we can work through that network pretty quickly.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Roshan Ranjit,  Deutsche Bank - Analyst   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Vikram Karnany, UBS.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Vikram Karnany,  UBS - Analyst   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just a few questions here. Firstly, in terms of the EBITDA contribution, I just wanted to check that the margins that you have in terms of your underlying cable business -- is it aligned with the margins that you have? And also on an accounting basis, there's no further adjustment required, like it was the case in BASE?
 Secondly, on the recent investment plan for Proximus for fiber rollout, do you think it will have any impact on your B2B ambitions that you are having with your asset, and also combined together?
 Then finally, with the leverage around 3.6 times, post- the deal, and the visibility on VOO is low, do you think there is a case over here in terms of increasing shareholder or probably -- shareholder remuneration part of the discussion in 2017 earlier than what you were expected? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Firstly on the margins: so the current margins of the SFR are higher than our own margins, because it's also because a lot of activities are shared with the headquarters in France. So that is why they are higher. They will be more in line with our own EBITDA margins going forward, once it's fully integrated.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 But post-synergies, I think it's -- we're still -- I mean, this [isn't] really incremental to our core business. So you have to look at it as incremental cash flow and not base cash flow. Because it's not going to -- incrementally, it will have higher margins than Telenet's overall business.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Correct. But given the size of it (inaudible) it will not really affect our overall margins going forward. It will still impact up the road, so it's exactly -- be on plan.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 On the shareholder remuneration question, obviously that's something the Board will consider. They usually do so after the -- as they are thinking about the full-year results. But I think you can see that, pro forma, our leverage only goes from 3.4 to 3.6. So I'm sure they will be thinking hard about shareholder remuneration in 2017. But I wouldn't want to predict what they're going to do.
 On terms of Proximus's fiber rollout, we've only got, nationwide, sort of 12% -- 11%, 12% -- of the total B2B market, which is about -- it's under a EUR2 billion domestic market. There is plenty of upside for us. I think we always expect that we're competing with Proximus fiber in B2B. But we are installing our own fiber, as well. We have a project called Nexus, which is tentatively a fiber rollout in business parks, primarily in Flanders, up till now. But we can certainly now look at extending Nexus down into the SFR area as well.
 We expect Proximus to be a strong competitor in B2B. They are very good at any enterprise business. That's why they have such a dominant share. They've got a 70% share, I think, of the total B2B market. We wouldn't expect them not to be a strong competitor with a lot of fiber, but we can still win a lot of business, and we do. In the [fluxion] of the market we -- people who are considering us their telecom supplier -- we picked up just under half of the flux in 2016. So we're pretty confident that we have a -- some pretty interesting solutions as well (technical difficulty).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Vikram Karnany,  UBS - Analyst   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's helpful. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Bishop, Goldman Sachs.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Bishop,  Goldman Sachs - Analyst   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just firstly on content: is there much incremental investment you'll have to make, effectively, to match your content rights that you currently have and cross-sell that content into the new footprint?
 And then secondly, just to follow up on the margin question. So if I'm correct, the EUR45.7 million doesn't include the management recharge that currently happens; and, therefore, you should assume that EUR45.7 million is marginally above the Telenet current margins. Is that correct?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rob Goyens,  Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So Michael, with regards to the second question, so the EUR45.7 million is -- so is the EBITDA contribution expected through 2016, as per the acquisition plan. But in line with our accounting policy, so we already -- I had an alignment of accounting policies, as we also did with the BASE acquisition earlier this year, just to make sure that we don't -- I mention an EBITDA number which, in the end, does not seem to be the right number because of accounting interpretations and restatements. So that's a clear number that we are presenting here for 2016.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And on the programming costs, it's really around the margins. There's not a lot of negative synergies in harmonizing the programming lineup. We looked pretty closely at that. And if you also consider the fact that we can extend our premium content down there and get more scale into our premium content, it's pretty much a wash.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rob Goyens,  Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Maybe so, Michael, in addition to that, that John also mentioned in the beginning of a call that a lot of focus in the release goes to Brussels and Luxembourg, where we are of course expanding our footprint at Luxembourg -- obvious one because we were not active in that region before; Brussels because we are getting now two-thirds of the footprint; but also, two additional municipalities in Flanders are being added back. And then also some of the Brussels ones which actually have a fairly dense penetration of Flemish-speaking households.
 So when you think about just the fact that you are able to roll out your existing products in those areas, also on the entertainment side, it seems like an incremental upside.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Bishop,  Goldman Sachs - Analyst   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. That's great, guys. And just maybe quickly just on regulation. You mentioned in the release you don't expect any real issues. So I was just wondering whether you've had preliminary talks with the local regulators already, or whether that's just an expectation.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 They don't give anything away. We, of course, have been sort of handicapping that this transaction could be coming down the pike with them, but they don't give anything away. But I think there's massive precedent in Europe for -- and in Belgium, for that matter -- for (technical difficulty) which do not compete head-to-head, be as they are complementary, receiving competition authority approval. Big Ziggo-UPC comes to mind.
 The precedent is all in our favor, in terms of getting this done. And we actually -- I made a lot of calls this morning, and there's real political support for this transaction. Because I think they feel that this business in Brussels hasn't quite put its best foot forward to their expectations. And they think it will be great for the city and for the consumers. And so we got a lot of political support behind this transaction as well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Michael Bishop,  Goldman Sachs - Analyst   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's great. Thanks so much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Frank Knowles, New Street Research.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Frank Knowles,  New Street Research - Analyst   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I apologize if this was dealt with at the early part of the call. I missed the first 10 minutes or so. Could you just -- in the -- I gather that Altice has said they will provide some sort of transitional services, and so on. Could you just give an idea of the scope of -- how long that will last, what sort of services are we talking about, and is that part of the compensation? Or is there additional payments you will be making to Altice for those services over time? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The primary -- we have a transition -- the TSA, transitional services agreement, which we are quite comfortable that we have enough time to do the things that we need to do. A lot of the TSA deals with IT and the building stack. We happen to be under -- we happen to be developing new building stack for -- through the Telenet-BASE merger. So we're very comfortable that we can -- I mean, once again, the scale of this thing is it makes it very manageable. We could put a bunch of people in a room, and they could manually enter every customer that these guys have.
 I'm pretty confident that we'll be able to move reasonably quickly off the TSA. And it gives us the flexibility to do so. I think of the probably total value of the TSA, two-thirds of it is the IT support. And once we get our hands around the business, we will have a much better idea of what it's going to take.
 Does that answer your question?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Frank Knowles,  New Street Research - Analyst   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. And in terms of the sort of amounts we're talking about, is it pretty much rounding errors in the context of the cost side?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 A couple million.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Frank Knowles,  New Street Research - Analyst   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Per annum.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Guy Peddy, Macquarie.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Guy Peddy,  Macquarie Research - Analyst   [47]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I just wanted to try and think forward on the direction of numbers, and just wanted to confirm that actually this asset you are buying is a declining business. So, pre- the deal, it would continue to decline; so that when we think of the synergies in the longer term, probably the best EBITDA you could have would be now, plus synergies. And obviously that's going to be lower because the business is declining. Is that the right way to think of things?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [48]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, we don't see it declining in a forward look. We see it -- what has been decline is what we see as opportunity. We have 64% digital market share in Telenet's business. These guys have 100,000, of which only about 60% are digital in 283,000 homes. We see there's real upside, both in the B2C and the B2B markets. And I think we've been very conservative in terms of what we've taken in the investment case and in the synergy target that we've gone public with. I'm pretty confident there's quite a bit of upside in the revenue, and that we're going to turn it around fairly quickly.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Guy Peddy,  Macquarie Research - Analyst   [49]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [50]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Nawar Cristini, JPMorgan.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Nawar Cristini,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [51]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I have two questions on my end, please. Firstly, I wanted to ask: are there any tax considerations that we should be thinking about regarding this transaction?
 And secondly, just coming back to your ambition to be a national player, of course VOO seems to be the obvious route there, but this is a deal that has been talked about for many years now. If you come to the conclusion, at some point, that VOO is a very difficult plan, would you consider rolling out your own network in Wallonia? And what time frame would you give yourself to consider that? Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [52]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Go ahead.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Birgit Conix,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CFO   [53]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 On the tax, no, there is a -- the deal is driven in terms of strategic upside, et cetera. So nothing really that matters on the tax side; so, no.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Porter,  Telenet Group Holding NV - CEO   [54]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We didn't see this as a two-stage investment at all. I think we would like to extend our footprint further, but there are a lot of different options available to us. So like I said, other than acquiring VOO, which is not for sale, there's commercial opportunities which could be interesting. That could be asset swaps, or these kind of things that we would certainly consider.
 And also they have -- with what we're putting into the mobile network, and the fact that we just did a field test of LTE Advanced, or 4.5 network, at over 1 gig of data speeds off of a wireless network. The idea of mobile fixed substitution is also an option for us, and particularly in the cities, in Wallonia. We're open to a lot of different ideas. And I wouldn't handicap one of them versus the other at this stage of the game.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Nawar Cristini,  JPMorgan - Analyst   [55]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [56]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Gentlemen, I would now like to hand the call back to Mr. Rob Goyens for any additional or closing remarks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Rob Goyens,  Telenet Group Holding NV - VP of Strategic Planning, Treasury, and IR   [57]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you, operator. Ladies and gentlemen, that concludes today's conference call on the acquisition of SFR Belgium and Luxembourg. Should you have any further questions, please reach out to us directly.
 As we will be reporting our full-year 2016 results in mid-February, we will enter into a quiet period as of January 9.
 On behalf of Telenet's management, our entire Board, and all of our employees, we would like to wish you a Merry Christmas and a healthy, prosperous 2017. Bye-bye.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [58]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That will conclude today's conference call. Thank you for your participation. You may now disconnect.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[Telenet Group Holding NV Acquisition SFR BeLux Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>Mechelen</city>
  <companyName>Telenet Group Holding NV</companyName>
  <companyTicker>TNET.BR</companyTicker>
  <startDate>22-Dec-16 7:30am GMT</startDate>
</Event>