<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7325242" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 5:48:42pm GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7325242.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 5:45:00am GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of DOKA.S M&A conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 5:45am GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[dormakaba Holding AG To Acquire Mechanical Security Businesses From Stanley Black & Decker First Call Conference

NEW BRITAIN Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of dormakaba Holding AG M&A conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 5:45:00am GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Riet Cadonau
      dormakaba Holding AG - CEO
   *  Bernd Brinker
      dormakaba Holding AG - CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Tobias Fahrenholz
      MainFirst - Analyst
   *  Francesca Caramenti
      UBS - Analyst
   *  Andreas Mueller
      Zurcher Kantonalbank - Analyst
   *  Martin Flueckiger
      Kepler Cheuvreux - Analyst
   *  Bernd Pomrehn
      Bank Vontobel - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good morning, ladies and gentlemen, this is Riet Cadonau speaking. Thank you for participating in this analyst call at such short notice. With me here today is our CFO, Bernd Brinker.
 As you have seen, we announced this morning that we agreed with Stanley Black &amp; Decker to acquire the major part of their mechanical solutions businesses.
 As we have laid out on slide 3 of the presentation, this deal is a very important strategic milestone for us. We will become a top three player in North America, which is the most profitable market in our industry.
 The acquisition is in line with our stated strategy, and builds on the successful dormakaba merger, and the recently completed acquisition of Mesker in North America. It will add substantial scale, mainly in North America, and a large installed customer base that will provide us with an attractive repeat business, (spoken in German), including the possibility for future upgrades.
 And, we will get BEST, one of the most recognized brands in our industry for the last 90 years, as well as established spec-writing capability that will open access to new construction projects.
 For our Group, this acquisition will, therefore, significantly enhance prospects for future profitable growth.
 Bernd will now walk you through the transaction details on page 4. Bernd?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, thank you, Riet. Good morning, to everybody in the call. So, I would like to run you briefly through the transaction highlights which you can see on slide 4.
 As already mentioned, we are going to acquire the majority of the Stanley Mechanical Security businesses; we're talking about consolidated net sales of $276 million, and an EBITDA of roughly $52 million.
 The transaction comprises commercial hardware, as well as GMT which is the Chinese activity.
 The transaction does not include -- for those who are very familiar with the Stanley Mechanical Securities business, it does not include Sargent &amp; Greenleaf, which is a safe lock business.
 Our consideration. We pay $725 million as an enterprise value, and it is an all-cash consideration. This translates into an acquisition multiple of 13.8 times EBITDA for 2016 expected, pre-synergies.
 Post-synergies it is 9 times, and we take into consideration revenue and cost synergies, which we are going to achieve within four years, as well as tax benefits.
 The financial impact. We expect that this transaction will be neutral from closing on revenue growth and EBITDA margin, but accretive from the financial year 2019/2020 onwards.
 With regard to earnings per share, the transaction will be accretive from day one.
 How do we finance the transaction? This is will be a fully debt financed transaction. We will increase our available credit facility from today's CHF500 million to CHF1.15 billion; so, this is already available.
 Timing. The transaction, obviously, is subject to customary closing conditions and regulatory approvals, but we expect closing to happen with Q1 of calendar-year 2017.
 With that, I would like to hand back to Riet.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 On page 5 you see the acquisition business profile. As we said, this is going to be a leading player in an attractive market. The business, when it comes to commercial hardware, it's based in Indianapolis, with three main sites in North America and about 1,000 employees, plus a production facility in Taiwan.
 As you can see here, the net sales for 2016 is estimated of $229 million, and an EBITDA of $51 million, with a margin of 22%.
 The other part is GMT, a China-based business, which is an established provider of access products and commercial hardware, with about 600 employees; net sales of $48 million; and an EBITDA of $2 million; so, a relatively small business.
 On slide 6, let's have a look at the North American market. Why is this market so attractive for our industry? Well, North America is the biggest economy in the world and North America represents a fairly large amount of our accessible market, the global access control market, which is estimated to be $40 billion globally.
 Also, the access solution market is already quite consolidated in North America, with two major players in North America, both retain a market share of about 25% each. It's, therefore, not as segmented as elsewhere.
 It is also a homogenous market with only one standard, the [ONCI] standard, and there is a good growth momentum for our industry.
 Taking these characteristics together, this makes North America a very attractive and, in fact, a most profitable market in our industry. This is reflected, as you know, in the good margins our major peers, as well as dormakaba, enjoy in North America.
 We have so far been a distant number four player in this market, clearly behind the two big players. With this transaction, we will now become a serious, a strong, top three player in North America.
 On slide 7, I would like to explain the major benefits of this deal in some more detail.
 First, we take a major leap forward with regard to sales and EBITDA in the North American market. As I said, we become the top three player in North America; and, we will have the ability to offer the full portfolio of door hardware and access control solutions to our customers.
 Second, we will add the well-recognized industry brand BEST to our brand portfolio.
 Third, and this is a very important value driver, we are acquiring a large installed customer base with an attractive repeat business and the potential to leverage our dormakaba products.
 Fourth, we get established spec writing capabilities, specification writing capabilities, through which we'll gain access to previously inaccessible bids in new construction.
 And last but not least, we are strengthening our position in growing vertical markets, such as education and healthcare.
 Slide 8 shows you how our presence in specific product categories will be strengthened significantly, thanks to the acquisition announced today, as well as with the recently completed acquisition of Mesker Opening Group.
 With Mesker we got access to mechanical doors, which was our missing piece, in order to manage the opening; manage the opening.
 Now, with Stanley, we will add substantial scale in key areas of our industry, North America, like master key systems and mechanical locks.
 The last, by the way, is a key component in door hardware. Just to give you a figure, 60% of turnover in mechanical hardware is generated with mechanical locks.
 Beside Assa Abloy and Allegion, we are now the third player in North America that can provide comprehensive access solutions out of one hand.
 Page 9. The access to an extensive installed base of around 350,000 end-user sites is one of the key drivers of this deal. One of the key elements in this installed base is the BEST core, the BEST cylinder, that you see here on slide 9.
 It is a differentiating product that you will find all over North America and, therefore, marks a high entry barrier to this business and it would take a very long time to build up this position organically. As I said, the brand is 90 years old.
 Generally, the large installed base we are acquiring drives an attractive and stable repeat business, that means recurring revenues.
 On top, we can leverage the existing relationships. If we own the relationship, we own the business. We have the opportunity to generate additional business by upgrading mechanical cylinders with electronic solutions that are available, both in the acquired and in our existing dormakaba portfolio.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I would like to show you on slide 10 why we are -- why we think this is a fantastic opportunity to us to create value.
 We expect, on the one hand side, revenue synergies, because this opportunity gives us the foundation to drive for further growth. You can see two examples on the page, how we want to generate revenue synergies.
 In addition, we are going to target also significant cost synergies by going to further optimizing the production footprint by insourcing certain OEM products and, also, by establishing shared service functions for finance and the HR in the future.
 If you try to identify the split of revenue and cost synergies, those two basically represent 50% of the synergy and benefit bases. The difference between 13.8 times and 9 times EBITDA multiple is, basically, represented by cost and revenue synergies. Within cost and revenue synergies, the cost synergies basically represent two-thirds of the overall synergies here.
 With regard to tax benefits, this transaction is, to a majority extent, an asset transaction and, as it is quite typical for US asset transactions, we are able to generate certain tax benefits.
 Those tax benefits will be available already from the year 1. Those tax benefits represent the other 50% of the potential of synergies and benefits.
 With regard to timing, as I said, tax benefits will be available from year 1 on, while revenue and cost synergies will be achieved within a period of four years.
 As far as implementation costs are concerned, we expect a magnitude of $15 million implementation costs. They will accrue over four years with the majority to apply in year one and in year two.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think you are familiar with slide 11, which we showed for the first time at our Capital Market Day on April 5 this year, and since then is an integral part of our presentation.
 It outlines the six pillars of our strategy and what the strategy is founded on: global brand power and sustainability. How does our acquisition fit into this strategy? I will give you a few examples.
 We are obviously expanding our presence in North America, in particular. On top, we are strengthening our market position in growing verticals: education and healthcare.
 In terms of a superior offering, we'll add product, such as the BEST cylinders, I explained before, and other interesting products, such as panic and fire exit devices, just to name a few.
 In addition, we are expanding our offering out of one hand from mechanical to electronic and cloud-based solutions.
 This brings me to the third point I would like to mention: innovation leadership. We have not just acquired a mechanical business, about 20% of the sales of BEST is actually generated with high-tech wireless electronic access control systems or systems controlled by a cloud. That is the so-called shelter product family. So, we do, in fact, get attractive IP rights and R&amp;D development expertise with this deal as well.
 To sum it up on slide 12. The acquisition we have announced today is a very important step and in line with our strategy: to become the trusted industry leader for access solutions. That is because it adds a strong presence in North America, the most profitable market in our industry. It adds a large installed customer base in a high-margin business. That means recurring revenues plus upgrading opportunity.
 It adds the BEST brand that is very well recognized in our industry. And, it adds considerable value enhancement opportunities for dormakaba.
 So, from our perspective, a very strategic move; a very important milestone on our journey to become the trusted industry leader.
 Thank you for your attention. We are now opening the lines for your questions. We are just approaching the operator, in order to make sure that you can start to ask your questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions).
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tobias Fahrenholz,  MainFirst - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tobias Fahrenholz, MainFirst. A quick one on the track record. Could you provide us some figures here for the acquired business? What kind of organic growth rates did they achieve in the last, let's say, cycle? And what's your target for this operation going forward? Also, are there big differences with regards to return on capital employed?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, Tobias, thank you for the question. I think you might be aware that Stanley commented in the past on their intention to make a strategic evaluation of this security mechanical business. They experienced, I think, relatively lower growth. It was in the single-digit area, on the lower end, and this was also part of the reasons for considering that.
 As we have seen also their press announcement, the evaluation was also driven by the question whether this is a business which really fits to a tool company. So, that also raised the question of the better owner. They also brought up the point that we might be a better owner for that business. So, low single-digit growth rates in the past.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tobias Fahrenholz,  MainFirst - Analyst   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And return on capital employed, any indication here?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I don't want to go into that direction, because then we are in the area of trying to -- the capital employed base as well as the main drivers here.
 What I can tell you, however, is the performance was driven by, on the one hand side, a relatively high profitability, and also by a very solid working capital management.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tobias Fahrenholz,  MainFirst - Analyst   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Further questions?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti,  UBS - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I have a question on the synergies. I just wanted to ask how much you expect in total, and how it will be split then in cost -- in cost and revenues, if you already have an idea?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, Francesca, a pleasure to answer. So, as I outlined during the presentation, we expect the cost synergies, as well as revenue synergies and tax benefits. You can divide those into two parts.
 On the one hand side, the tax benefits, as said, driven by the US asset deal structure. We are able to step up or to make step ups for all the assets we are going to acquire. This will represent, basically, 50% of the difference between the 13.8 times and the 9 times EBITDA multiple.
 Therefore, 50% is also with cost and revenue synergies. Within that area, we expect two-thirds to come from cost synergies, so very much in our own hands. While, we expect one-third to come from the revenue side, driven by what has been outlined from Riet, so our better access to a lot of verticals, our cross-selling opportunities in the market.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, we can summarize 50% of our synergy gains will come from tax rate, from total in cost synergies; cost synergies being the more relevant part.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Francesca Caramenti,  UBS - Analyst   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Right, thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Next question, please.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andreas Mueller.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andreas Mueller,  Zurcher Kantonalbank - Analyst   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I was wondering about the production footprint in the US and China. Do you see -- how do you see that changed after the transaction? Is there more overlap with Mesker? Or is it -- would you integrate that also in your already existing dormakaba production footprint with the fab in Mexico? How should I look at it?
 Also, in Taiwan you seem to have a facility? What's there the fate? Is that kind of a strategic entity as well there in Taiwan?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. First of all, Andreas, Mesker is not impacted. This has nothing to do with Mesker. Mesker is commercial doors in North America, and has nothing to do with the Asian industrial footprint of this deal. That is important to understand.
 When we refer to the industrial footprint of this deal, we speak, on one hand, from a Taiwan facility, which is part of commercial hardware. That is primarily an OEM supplier to the North American market. Minority goes into commercial hardware of this deal. That is one aspect.
 The other one is GMT, which is a totally isolated business from commercial hardware.
 What we are going to do, or how we are going to manage those sites, is, clearly, under the leadership of the local AS APAC, access solution APAC, management, which is a very experienced local management, as you know, which has successfully, by the way, successfully, turned around Wah Yuet, or former Kaba. Therefore, we will hand over that responsibility to these experienced and successful managers.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andreas Mueller,  Zurcher Kantonalbank - Analyst   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And what's going to be the tax rate for the Group after the transaction?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think we get significant additional exposure from the US part, as you can see from the numbers. Our expectation is that we will -- as a result of the tax benefits, it's only an expectation that needs to be done at the time after closing. We need to do purchase price allocation. But our expectation is that we will build significant deferred tax asset in the balance sheet, so that the tax impact will not go into the P&amp;L.
 With the -- however, on the cash side we expect to be able to benefit from the tax situation in the US. So, our tax rate overall will go down from today's, what we expect below 27% to 28%. So, we see a certain relief on the tax side, on the cash tax side.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Andreas Mueller,  Zurcher Kantonalbank - Analyst   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Next question?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Flueckiger Martin.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Flueckiger,  Kepler Cheuvreux - Analyst   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Actually, I have a few. I'd like to start off with the first one, which is the question on the market exposure in the US and China.
 In your presentation, and I believe in your press release, you've highlighted the exposure in North America to education and healthcare. I was wondering whether you have other significant market sector exposures there, and what the situation is like in China. That would be my first question.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Let's start with North America. As you are aware of, dormakaba today has already certain verticals which we serve successfully, such as hospitality, so the hotels; or multi-housing; or government.
 With this deal, we are going to add two additional significant verticals, which we, today, do not really serve, which is education and healthcare. So, beside the installed base, in general, for commercial hardware, we are going to add two verticals, which we really like, because in these verticals, you normally can generate profitable growth.
 So, that is with regard to North America, which is again the major part of that transaction.
 The smaller part is, as you could see, GMT. There, this is a generic access business in the S3/S4 level, as we call it. So, it's not the high end, which dormakaba is [doing]; it's rather the middle-class cars, so to say, in S3/S4 access hardware.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Flueckiger,  Kepler Cheuvreux - Analyst   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thanks. But maybe just a follow-up question. Education and healthcare, are we talking mainly public sector education and healthcare? Or are we talking maybe predominantly about the private sector here, because, if I remember correctly, public sector education and healthcare, construction spending was rather weak over the last few quarters. If you add some color there, it would be helpful.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Clearly, both; clearly, both. As you know, especially healthcare is highly driven by the private sector in US and it's, clearly, both.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Flueckiger,  Kepler Cheuvreux - Analyst   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thanks. Then my next question would be on the EPS accretion and value enhancement effect. You've outlined it in qualitative terms. I was wondering whether you could provide a little bit more quantitative color on that; whether you're expecting single- or double-digit EPS accretion over the next three years; and, as of which year, you're expecting a value enhancement effect.?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes. Martin, I'll try to give you, again, an overview. We are not in a position to give you detailed numbers as the impact on EPS is also driven by the purchase price allocation and the question to what extent we are able to identify deferred tax assets, because this will have an impact. Therefore, the statement is only that it will be EPS accretive from day one.
 In terms of EBITDA margin impact, we expect, in the first two years, the majority of the implementation costs. But, at the same time, we expect to be able to absorb that in our current guidance.
 So, we expect to be able to maintain our current guidance for the current fiscal year. No impact here will absorb those implementation cost in the current fiscal year.
 We also should not expect any negative impact from the transaction for the following year. But we expect, let's say for 2018/2019, again, only a minor impact. Therefore, 2019/2020 will be the first year when we will see, let's say, something -- a significant impact on the EBITDA margin.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Flueckiger,  Kepler Cheuvreux - Analyst   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, many thanks. I'll stand back in line.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Next question, please?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Pomrehn.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Pomrehn,  Bank Vontobel - Analyst   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Obviously, an impressive pace you are setting just 1.5 years following the merger with DORMA. One question please.
 How difficult do we expect the carve-out to be from the Stanley Black &amp; Decker group? Obviously, they retain their commercial electronics security business, as well their automatic doors business, so how complex will the carve-out be for you? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, first of all, this has been managed totally separated from the automatic doors and from the system integration business; that is important to understand.
 Second, we will -- we have negotiated a transition time of 24 months. So, we will have sufficient time to go for that carve-out.
 As far as I assess the situation, and I have already in my career made a more complex carve-out, I am of the opinion that we will professionally manage that within the given timeframe. I'm not concerned about that carve-out.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Pomrehn,  Bank Vontobel - Analyst   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, excellent. Thank you; very helpful.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Next question, please?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 There are no further questions, at the moment.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good. If there are no further questions, Bernd and I would like to thank you for attending this telephone conference. If there are any further questions, please get in contact with us.
 And with that, I would like to finalize and finish and wish you a great day. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bernd Brinker,  dormakaba Holding AG - CFO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Bye, bye.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Riet Cadonau,  dormakaba Holding AG - CEO   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Bye, bye.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 This conversation will be recorded.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[dormakaba Holding AG To Acquire Mechanical Security Businesses From Stanley Black & Decker First Call Conference]]></eventTitle>
  <city>NEW BRITAIN</city>
  <companyName>dormakaba Holding AG</companyName>
  <companyTicker>DOKA.S</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 5:45am GMT</startDate>
</Event>