<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7328416" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 7:55:34pm GMT" eventTypeId="5" eventTypeName="Corporate Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7328416.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:30:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of MRUS conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 1:30pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[Merus NV and Incyte Corp Global Strategic Research Collaboration - Conference Call

WILMINGTON Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of Merus NV conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 1:30:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  John Crowley
      Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO
   *  Ton Logtenberg
      Merus N.V. - CEO
   *  Hui Liu
      Merus N.V. - EVP and Chief Business Officer

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Brian Abrahams
      Jefferies LLC - Analyst
   *  David Nierengarten
      Wedbush Securities - Analyst
   *  Jon Wolleben
      JMP Securities - Analyst
   *  Tony Butler
      Guggenheim Partners - Analyst
   *  Ian Somaiya
      BMO Capital Markets - Analyst
   *  Peter Lawson
      SunTrust Robinson Humphrey - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, everyone, for joining our conference call to discuss the collaboration agreement with Incyte Corporation that was announced earlier this morning. I am very pleased to be joining you as Merus's newly appointed Chief Financial Officer to discuss this announcement.
 Joining me on the call today is Dr. Ton Logtenberg, Merus's Chief Executive Officer; Hui Liu, Chief Business Officer; Shelley Margetson, Chief Operating Officer; Mark Throsby, Chief Scientific Officer; and Andres Sirulnik, our newly appointed Chief Medical Officer. Following our brief prepared comments, we will be available to answer your questions.
 Before we begin, I remind you that remarks made on this call that are not historical in nature may be forward-looking statements and are subject to a number of risks and uncertainties. Our actual results may differ materially.
 Such remarks may include, but are not limited to, those involving the potential impact of the collaboration with Incyte on our pipeline, our business, and our financial position; potential payments under the collaboration agreement; the timing of future developments and updates; the potential impact of bispecific antibodies; and our business and commercialization strategies and expectations of future growth.
 Please see our most recent filing with the US Securities and Exchange Commission for additional information on the risks that could cause our actual results to differ. As a reminder, statements we make today are as of today, December 21, only.
 I will now turn the call over to Merus's Chief Executive Officer, Dr. Ton Logtenberg. Ton?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, John, and good morning to everyone joining us today. We are very pleased to announce today that Merus has entered in what we believe is a transformative, strategic collaboration with Incyte Corporation. This agreement is focused on the research, discovery, and development of therapeutic bispecific antibodies utilizing Merus's proprietary Biclonics technology platform.
 Biclonics are capable of binding to two distinct targets, enabling therapeutic effects that cannot otherwise be obtained with conventional monoclonal antibodies. Their full-length IgG format retains and captures the attractive characteristics of conventional monoclonal antibodies during manufacturing, as well as the [former] application in patients, such as long half-life and low immunogenicity.
 As a reminder, our most advanced bispecific antibodies are outside the scope of this agreement. They are MCLA-128, targeting HER2 and 3; MCLA-117, targeting CD3 and CLEC12A; and MCLA-158, which targets Lgr5 and EGFR. The first two of these assets are currently in clinical studies, and the last is moving towards IND.
 This global collaboration with Incyte is designed to allow us to rapidly expand our proprietary pipeline with the potential for territory or profit share options, and up to three of the programs emerging from the agreement; as well as our pipeline, with the opportunity to work with a strong leader in innovative drug development on up to eight additional programs.
 Furthermore, this agreement provides substantial funding to the Company both in the form of an upfront payment and an equity investment, as well as access to potential substantial milestones or royalties over the term of the agreement, which John will detail in a moment.
 It was an important strategic goal for Merus to enter into a platform collaboration, as it further exploits the potential of our Biclonics platform. Today we have succeeded in this goal in what we believe is a truly transformational agreement for Merus.
 This collaboration aligns us with a world-class partner, Incyte, and further validates our Biclonics technology. We look forward to working with Incyte under this collaboration, as well as with other partners, and to progressing our most advanced proprietary assets in the clinic. We expect a number of important developments within our proprietary programs in 2017.
 I would now like to turn the call over to our Chief Business Officer, Hui Liu, who will review a few more of the details. Hui?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hui Liu,  Merus N.V. - EVP and Chief Business Officer   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Ton, and good morning, everyone. As Ton indicated, we believe this is a truly transformational deal for Merus. Together with Incyte, we will focus on improving and extending the lives of patients with cancer and other serious diseases. This is a long-term collaboration that provides Incyte with the rights to up to 11 programs, including two of Merus's pre-existing preclinical programs. Of the programs subject to this agreement, Merus will retain US development and commercial rights to one program.
 In addition, Merus will have the option to co-fund 35% global development costs in exchange for 50% of US profits on two additional programs, with the right to co-detail a product in one of those two additional programs.
 Merus will retain the rights to its technology platform, as well as its clinical candidates, MCLA-128 and MCLA-117; the pre-clinical candidate, MCLA-158; and any future programs emerging from Merus' platform that are outside the scope of this agreement.
 We, along with Incyte, believe that bispecific antibodies have the potential to play a significant role in the future of biotherapeutics. This agreement, our second such collaboration following our agreement with Ono Pharmaceuticals, serves as potent validation of that belief.
 And now I'd like to return the floor to John Crowley to review some of the financial details. John?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Hui. As part of this agreement, Incyte has agreed to make an upfront payment of $200 million, comprised of $120 million of cash and an $80 million investment in Merus's common stock. For the equity investment, Incyte has agreed to purchase 3.2 million shares at $25 per share. These shares are subject to customary lockup and standstill provisions.
 In addition, upon progression of certain programs, Merus is eligible to receive development, regulatory, and sales milestones of up to $2.8 billion from Incyte, representing $350 million of potential milestones per program across eight programs, if all development, regulatory, and sales milestones are achieved across all programs in all territories.
 Upon commercialization, Merus is eligible to receive tiered royalties ranging from 6% to 10% from Incyte on future sales of any bispecific antibody emerging from this collaboration.
 This investment significantly strengthens our balance sheet. As we previously announced, Merus had cash and cash equivalents of EUR66.3 million at the end of the third quarter of 2016. We look forward to updating our runway guidance, including the use of our proceeds from this agreement, in one of our future updates.
 This transaction is expected to close in the first quarter of 2017, subject to the early termination or expiration of any applicable waiting periods under the Hart-Scott-Rodino Act, and customary closing conditions.
 This concludes our prepared remarks. And at this point, we'd now like to open the call for your questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions). Brian Abrahams, Jefferies.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Abrahams,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Congratulations on the collaboration. A few different questions. First off, I was wondering if you could maybe provide any color on the identity of some of the programs under the collaboration with respect to the pre-existing preclinical programs. Does this include 134, the PD-1/TIM-3; 114, the CD3 myeloma; or 145?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Brian. We don't comment at this stage on the preclinical candidates, on the targets. As we go forward, and once these program mature further, we will give you further color into what programs are included in what specific areas.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Abrahams,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got it. And then maybe just a financial question on the milestone payments. Can you maybe clarify for those first three programs, the one where you retain US rights and where you have the 35% co-development, that 50-50 profit split option, can you talk through the milestone payments on that?
 My understanding was that $350 million was only applicable to those earlier eight programs. And then maybe help us understand in general -- with the milestone structure, how should we be thinking about the degree to which those are back-end-loaded on the regulatory and commercial side versus developmental.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John, can I ask you to answer that question?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, no, sure. So the $350 million relate to the eight programs in which we don't have the profit share or US rights. There was one program where we have US rights, where we share the development costs for each of our respective regions. And the other two, we have an option to opt in for profit sharing, which will be royalties. But that's exclusive of the $350 million for the eight programs.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Abrahams,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got it. And then in terms of the back-end-loaded versus developmental, broadly speaking?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, I would say that broadly speaking, these milestones are in line with what you expect for a collaboration of this nature, but we're not disclosing the details of those milestone payments.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Abrahams,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got it. And then last question: what does the infusion of cash mean for the potential expansion or acceleration of your current clinical programs, like 128 and 117? Should we look for either an acceleration or expansion of those programs, or an acceleration of some of the late-stage preclinical programs into the clinic with the additional funding? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Our goal is to -- (multiple speakers)
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John, I'll take that; thank you. Our goal is to continue to advance our clinical candidates, as well as work to expand our pipeline through internal discovery. And of course this is all very recent. So having said that, we plan to provide an update on our strategic priorities and timelines, giving access to these expanded resources.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Abrahams,  Jefferies LLC - Analyst   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Well, thanks for taking the questions. And, Ton, congrats again to you and the team on the deal.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Brian.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Nierengarten, Wedbush Securities.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Nierengarten,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I was curious as to the guidelines for your choosing which candidates you might choose to work on, or exercise the co-promote option. Is that totally up to your discretion to choose those candidates, or is there a joint committee. Or does Incyte have any first rights of refusal, or anything like that, to take the candidates they want? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, David, for this question. No, this is -- the prioritization is managed by a joint research committee, consisting of Merus and Incyte scientists and management. We have some candidates that we are currently already have in view as taking forward. But there's also certainly room for new target pairs, and new ideas and new biology that we want to include in our bispecific programs. That will certainly be a joint discussion and decision.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 David Nierengarten,  Wedbush Securities - Analyst   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yigal Nochomovitz, Citi.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Unidentified Participant   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 This is [Yau] for Yigal. Congratulations on the agreement. I have two questions. The first one is, can you give us some colors on what process Incyte has done to evaluate this opportunity? Does Incyte evaluate other bispecific programs at other companies? So what's your feedback on your program in comparison to other programs, if there's any?
 And my second question is regarding the stock purchase agreement. How does you and Incyte reach to the $25 per share purchase price? If you can provide any color, that would be great. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks for this question. I will take the first question, and I'll ask John to comment on the second question. We cannot speak for Incyte. And we have no full view on the process they went through selecting Merus as the company for the bispecific antibody.
 Having said that, I'm sure -- and given the thoroughness of the Incyte organization, is that they see many of the advantages of the bispecific platform that we have. And we have reiterated this over the last years in our many interactions with investors. And in short, those are the full-length IgG format, which gives us molecules that we know how they behave in vivo -- so long half-lives and low immunogenicity -- and also provide us with a very dependable and predictable format for manufacturing.
 And that tied in with our ability to perform functional assays on thousands of bispecific antibodies that we generate for any target pair. And as we have communicated in the past, this is really critical to find those bispecific antibodies that are differentiated in their modes of action: so, cell-based, bispecific [greening], the full-length IgG format. And I think the unusual modes of action that we have demonstrated, not only for a T-cell engager approach, but also for targets expressed by cancer cells, or other combinations of targets that go outside and beyond the engager approach.
 John, can I ask you to answer the second question?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 John Crowley,  Merus N.V. - EVP and CFO   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sure. So, the $25 premium represents a 60% premium over the volume weighted average price over the past month, and reflects the value that this collaboration brings to the -- to Merus and to the parties. I think this is consistent with other strategic deals where similar premiums have been made.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Unidentified Participant   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Liisa Bayko, JMP Securities.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jon Wolleben,  JMP Securities - Analyst   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi, Jon Wolleben on for Liisa. Just a couple of quick questions; and thanks for taking, and congrats on the deal. If I heard correctly earlier, the decision to opt in for those two programs, that would be a joint decision, correct? And then when would we expect that to be triggered, or what would trigger that decision?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The decision to opt into those programs is entirely Merus's decision. So it's up to us to commit to the opt-in, and to progress with those two programs in that situation.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jon Wolleben,  JMP Securities - Analyst   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And can you provide any guidance on what you'd be looking for, or when we might expect an update on the opt-in?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We're not disclosing the exact timing of the opt-in.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jon Wolleben,  JMP Securities - Analyst   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. And what are the stage of the other eight programs? Have targets been identified, leads generated? Or is Incyte going to have input on designing and discovery of these compounds?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, so as I mentioned in our explanation of the deal, this is really a program that allows for novel targets and novel biology to be explored. So that is a situation where targets pairs have not been identified, or we're just beginning discussions on those.
 And then there are other programs that are more advanced, and are part of Merus's preclinical pipeline; and, for example, in the space of immuno-oncology. And those programs include two of Merus's current preclinical immuno-oncology discovery programs. So there, target pairs are well defined, and these programs have advanced quite a bit in the preclinical stage.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jon Wolleben,  JMP Securities - Analyst   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Perfect. Thanks for taking the questions.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tony Butler, Guggenheim Partners.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tony Butler,  Guggenheim Partners - Analyst   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton, was there any -- two questions. Was there any discussion -- and by the way, congratulations on the transaction. Was there any discussion about the current clinical programs -- including 128, 158, and 117 -- perhaps being crafted in the transaction, even in a larger way?
 And number two is, what happens if there needs to be a collaboration -- I would say outside of the collaboration with Ono -- but there needs to be a collaboration to use someone else's molecule in conjunction for some clinical development. Who makes that decision? Is it the combined Board or group, or how would that work? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Tony. Thanks for the congratulations and your questions. As we stated, this is entirely preclinical platform-based, and we're not really commenting on business development activities concerning our clinical programs. Clearly, these programs are outside of the scope of the agreement, and I think that makes this a very clean, platform-based collaboration agreement.
 With regard to your question on other interactions with other partners: yes, we have absolutely full freedom to interact with other partners. We're looking forward to strike those kinds of interactions, based on target pairs or biology that we believe is worthwhile to pursue with bispecific antibodies and using our platform.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tony Butler,  Guggenheim Partners - Analyst   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, Ton.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions). Ian Somaiya, BMO Capital Markets.
 If you have your phone on mute, could you please unmute it and go ahead?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, sorry, apologize for that. And good morning, everyone, and congratulations on the deal. A couple of questions. First, if you could speak to the manufacturing of the potential antibodies. Who has the manufacturing rights, or where would the antibodies be manufactured?
 Second, just from a tax standpoint, where is the IP -- where will be IP be domiciled for the products?
 And third, from a therapeutic standpoint or a disease standpoint, is it limited to hematology/oncology, which has been your focus? Or is there an opportunity to go beyond that?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks for these questions. On the manufacturing part, Incyte will nominate programs and support pharmacology and mode of action activity, and be responsible for manufacturing and clinical development of the programs. Incyte will also be responsible for global commercialization of any products arising from the collaboration, with the exception of the program where Incyte has ex-US development and commercialization rights.
 In the agreement, Merus will be mainly responsible for generation of common light-chain human antibodies and large collections of bispecific antibodies; functional screening; antibody engineering; and the biophysical development of lead candidates to be nominated for development.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And for the IP, where is that being held?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Of course, Merus retains the full rights to its technology platform, and gives rights where needed for product development.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And disease focus -- are they going to be limited to oncology/hematology, or are we going beyond that?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 The initial focus is clearly on oncology, which is a focus for Incyte as well as for Merus. But the agreement does not exclude other serious disease areas where bispecifics may play an important role.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just one last question. The eight potential programs, is there time constraints on -- and Incyte's decision-making? Do they need to make decisions on these programs within a certain time frame?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 We haven't really disclosed the length of the collaboration. But this is clearly a long-term collaboration, encompassing the discovery and development of these molecules.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay. All right. Thank you very much for taking my questions.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Lawson, SunTrust.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Lawson,  SunTrust Robinson Humphrey - Analyst   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I'd just like to add my congratulations on the deal. Wanted actually to talk through the reasons for picking Incyte as a partner. I'm sure you've had other potential partners or other potential suitors. I'd just like to hear your reasons for picking Incyte over others.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [47]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, thanks for your question. It is our strategy to become a product company. And in our interactions with Incyte, the collaboration provides for product rights assigned to Merus. That's a critical element of our business development activities. Incyte is a company, like Merus, that is very ambitious at developing new products for cancer patients in oncology, and has similar beliefs in how that should be approach.
 So, for us, they are an ideal partner based on their culture, based on how they look at the future of bispecific antibodies. And it does fulfill our goal to strike a strategic deal rather than individual, small deals. And that is what happened in the interaction with Incyte.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Lawson,  SunTrust Robinson Humphrey - Analyst   [48]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. And then have the target types already been selected, or have some of those already been selected? Or is there any way of partitioning what you put into this collaboration, versus own yourself versus partner with others?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [49]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I would like to begin to say that the target space for target combinations is extremely large. And we are, for the newest programs, looking at new target combinations with exciting biology that we believe will make a difference in developing differentiated cancer therapeutics.
 From the Merus current preclinical pipeline are two of our immuno-oncology discovery programs are part of this deal. And beyond this, we are not disclosing any target pairs or areas of biology that we are considering.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Lawson,  SunTrust Robinson Humphrey - Analyst   [50]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Got you. Thank you. And then just anything around timelines of when these things could reach the clinic, or where we see the initial data around these collaborative molecules?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [51]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 No, we're not commenting on that today, but we will keep you informed as these programs mature.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Peter Lawson,  SunTrust Robinson Humphrey - Analyst   [52]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Okay, thank you so much, and congratulations.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [53]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. As we have no further questions, I will return the call to our speakers for closing comments.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ton Logtenberg,  Merus N.V. - CEO   [54]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, operator, and thanks again for joining us on this call. Incyte is a recognized leader in the field of drug discovery. And we view this collaboration as a strong endorsement, not only of our technology but also the broader potential of bispecific antibodies in the development of new treatments for cancer and other serious diseases.
 We look forward to leveraging our unique and complementary strengths to jointly expand our product pipelines and offer new hope to patients in need of new treatment alternatives. And I'm looking forward to providing future updates on our joint progress, and to seeing many of you next month in San Francisco during the JPMorgan Health Care Conference. And again, thank you for joining us.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[Merus NV and Incyte Corp Global Strategic Research Collaboration - Conference Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>WILMINGTON</city>
  <companyName>Merus NV</companyName>
  <companyTicker>MRUS</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 1:30pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>