<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7330148" lastUpdate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 8:45:56pm GMT" eventTypeId="5" eventTypeName="Corporate Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7330148.F" expirationDate="Thursday, December 8, 2016 at 10:30:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of RH conference call or presentation 8-Dec-16 10:30pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[Q3 2016 Restoration Hardware Holdings Inc Video Presentation

CORTE MADERA Dec 21, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of RH conference call or presentation Thursday, December 8, 2016 at 10:30:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Karen Boone
      Restoration Hardware Holdings, Inc. - Co-President, Chief Financial and Administrative Officer
   *  Gary Friedman
      Restoration Hardware Holdings, Inc. - Chairman, CEO

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Gary Friedman,  Restoration Hardware Holdings, Inc. - Chairman, CEO   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 American poet Robert Frost wrote, "Two roads diverged in a wood and I -- I took the one less traveled by, and that has made all the difference." In a world defined by duplication with little incentive for innovation, we find ourselves surrounded by sameness, the same products on similar websites IN the same stores with similar signs providing the same service, sending the same emails with the same promotions driving lower and lower prices.
 I wasn't quite sure how to react to a headline from an analyst report published the Monday after Thanksgiving that read, "Amazon Beats the Competition in Black Friday Pricing Study". It went on to report that online prices declined an average of 3.5% for Black Friday for the exact same items across four companies they compared.
 Make no mistake, many retailers find themselves in a race to the bottom, a race we AT our age have chosen not to join, and we believe that choice will make all the difference.
 I am sure our short-term results will be misinterpreted by many as choosing the wrong road as we continue to invest in differentiating and redefining the RH brand. While we have expected to endure some short-term pain in exchange for long-term gain, we are nearly through the most uncertain stages of our transformation and are becoming more certain with each passing quarter as to what lies ahead.
 Looking forward to 2017, we will anniversary the cost related to the launch of RH Modern, which we have estimated at approximately $20 million. We will we be on the timing issues related to the launch of RH membership, and we expect membership revenues and earnings to increase approximately $20 million in 2017.
 We began to cycle our efforts to reduce inventories and rationalize our SKU count. We expect product margins to rebound meaningfully year-over-year beginning in the first quarter of next year.
 We expect revenues will increase in 2017 as the fall 2016 interiors book builds and we benefit from the second mailing of RH Modern in-home next spring. Additionally, our business will continue to be driven in 2017 by growth in new stores and new businesses. Let me take a moment on each.
 As it relates to new stores, despite the delay mailing our sourcebook in 2016 and the macro factors affecting our business, we are pleased with the performance of our new galleries. Our real estate transformation should enable us to more than double our store volumes while also driving a lift in our direct business in every market.
 Regarding new businesses, you should anticipate that we will continually invest into the development and expansion of our brand and platform. Our plan is to aggressively capitalize on the development and expansion of RH Modern, as it is proving to be incremental, opening up our brand to an entirely new market.
 This spring, we will unveil new collections from several renowned designers from around the world such as -- (video playing).
 We announced that Brendan Sodikoff has joined us as President of RH Hospitality. Brendan has assembled an exceptional team to build on our success at the historic 3 Arts Club in Chicago. We believe we have created a unique and differentiated hospitality concept beautifully integrated into the retail experience unlike anything seen before in our industry. The cafe continues to drive traffic into our gallery and expose our brand to new and aspiring customers.
 Here is a video clip sent to us by our Chef John Asbaty from Sunday morning, November 6. It has been over a year since opening, and, as you can see, we still have a line that forms around the block every weekend to get a table for brunch in our courtyard. We plan to integrate cafes, wine vaults and coffee bars into five of the six new galleries opening in 2017.
 As you know, the prestigious bath and kitchen brand Waterworks joined the RH family this year and positions RH as the only fully integrated luxury brand servicing every room of the home. We expect Waterworks to be additive to our growth in 2017, and we look forward to sharing the longer-term view of the opportunity with you in the future.
 Let me shift their attention to our customer experience and supply chain. Under leadership of Co-President, Chief Operating, Service and Values Officer DeMonty Price, we continue to make investments to enhance the customer experience and optimize our operational infrastructure. DeMonty has added several new key leaders to the team, including Alex Krueger, Chief Supply Chain and Customer Experience Officer, who joins us from Amazon; Tom Kirtz, Senior Vice President, Customer Experience, who joins us from Nike and previously worked with Alex at Amazon; Dave Newman, Senior Vice President Supply Chain Operations and Technology who was in leadership positions at Target and Apple. The team is currently working to redefine the customer experience, redesign the supply chain, and build a culture of quality that is consistent with the RH brand.
 Lastly, while we are clearly disappointed with our short-term results, we have demonstrated an ability to navigate through challenging periods before and emerge an even stronger business and brand.
 I believe what's important to take note of is the series of choices we have made over the past decade and how, together, they form an integrated branded business that has no peer. In 2008, when many in our industry lowered quality to reduce prices, we went the opposite direction, raising the level of quality and design. While others have reacted to the threat of the Internet by closing stores and shrinking their retail footprint, we are building some of the most inspiring and productive retail experience in our industry.
 During a period that is being defined by a stream of endless promotions, we have once again chosen our own path, building our brand around membership, design, quality and value. We began this journey as a nearly bankrupt business selling nostalgic discovery items with a $20 million market cap and have transformed into a multibillion-dollar luxury home brand that is redefining its marketplace.
 We are confident that our choices, while nonconforming, will prove to be the right ones, driving long-term sustainable growth and shareholder value. Many times over the past decade, two roads diverged in the wood, and we, we took the one less traveled by, and that has and will continue to make all the difference.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Karen Boone,  Restoration Hardware Holdings, Inc. - Co-President, Chief Financial and Administrative Officer   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 While our results in fiscal 2016 are well below our expectations with many temporal factors affecting our business, we continue to believe the key decisions we made this past year were the right ones in order to position our brand and our platform for long-term, sustainable growth. We see a clear road to profitable growth and cash flow generation in fiscal 2017, and firmly believe that we will drive topline reacceleration, operating margin expansion, and significant earnings growth in every single quarter of fiscal 2017.
 Let me start with our revised outlook. As we discussed previously, there are a combination of factors that are impacting our business in fiscal 2016, including moving the annual sourcebook mailing and newness introductions from spring to fall, timing issues related to the launch of the RH Members Program, our efforts to rationalize and optimize our inventory, the costs related to the launch of RH Modern, and luxury consumer headwinds.
 While we began mailing our spring 2000 (sic - "2017") sourcebooks in September, the vast majority of the circulation is just getting in homes in the last few weeks, which is approximately a month later than planned. This is resulting in a shift of sales that would have been booked in the fourth quarter into the first quarter. Given the slower in-home of our fall sourcebooks than anticipated, a weaker consumer environment in November, which we attribute to the presidential election and lower holiday sales than expected, total revenue is expected to be in the range of $562 million to $592 million in the fourth quarter.
 There are several factors impacting adjusted gross margin in the fourth quarter. First, due to the weaker holiday sales, we are taking a much more aggressive approach to clearing the seasonal merchandise as this is not a business we plan to be in the long-term. Second, we are taking a more aggressive approach to rationalizing our SKUs, and there is expected to be a higher penetration of these sales. Third, the lower sales outlook and higher proportion of promotional volume is driving deleverage of our fixed occupancy and shipping costs. These factors are expected to result in gross margin deleverage of approximately 150 basis points versus the prior year.
 We have also made investments that further position the Company for a reacceleration in growth as we exit 2016 and for the long term, which include our supply chain and delivery initiatives and the expansion of our hospitality business.
 Fourth-quarter adjusted EPS is now expected to be in the range of $0.60 to $0.70, including approximately $0.19 from the temporal issues impacting gross margin. We are lowering our fiscal 2016 revenue growth outlook to flat to 1%, or $2.11 billion to $2.14 billion. We now anticipate adjusted diluted EPS in the range of $1.19 to $1.29.
 Let me recap the previously discussed temporal costs and margin-related issues that are impacting our fiscal year 2016 earnings. First, our more aggressive approach to rationalizing our SKU count and optimizing inventory and higher penetration of these sales is now expected to result in an approximate $0.40 to $0.45 reduction to fiscal 2016 earnings. Second, accommodations, largely due to RH Modern production delays during the first half, resulted in an approximate $0.30 negative impact to fiscal 2016 earnings. Third, is an approximate $0.25 negative impact related to deferred membership revenue, which will not be recognized in the period collected. This is lower than our prior outlook given the lower fourth-quarter sales outlook. As we look ahead to next year, we expect to cycle many of these one-time costs and investments and expect sales to reaccelerate, operating margins to expand, and to be free cash flow positive. We believe we are making the necessary investments in 2016 to position our business for the long term and for higher growth and cash flows beginning next year.
 Let me now turn to our recent results and third-quarter performance. Total revenues during the third quarter increased 3% on top of 10% last year. Approximately 5 points of growth during the third quarter resulted from the addition of Waterworks. While written orders were lower than anticipated during the quarter, our conversion of orders into sales was better than anticipated given our strong in-stock levels and supply chain improvements and related consumer preferences, which drove higher than expected net revenue growth during the period. In addition, our non-comp next-generation design galleries and standalone RH Modern store contributed to our growth in the third quarter.
 Comparable brand revenue declined 6% during the quarter, largely driven by the 3% decline we experienced in our direct channel. The decreases in our direct channel and comp store sales were largely driven by the lack of a spring sourcebook mailing this year, as well as the fact that we have not introduced any meaningful newness in our core business or made any significant changes to our legacy store floor sets in over 16 months.
 During the quarter, we added five outlet locations in conjunction with our SKU rationalization and inventory optimization efforts. Outlet sales did not contribute to our growth during the quarter as we were up against last year's annual warehouse sale volume.
 Adjusted gross margin decreased 440 basis points to 32.3%, consistent with our expectations. As we have discussed in the past few quarters, our gross margin is being impacted by several temporal factors that are a drag on margins this year that we do not anticipate occurring next year. Most significantly, gross margin in Q3 was impacted by the higher discount rate offered through the RH Members Program versus our prior promotional cadence in the third quarter of last year. In addition, SKU rationalization resulted in an approximate 120 basis point negative impact to gross margin in the third quarter, and the membership deferral impacted margin by approximately 30 basis points during the quarter.
 Transportation costs in the quarter were also higher due to the incremental and one-time shipping and transportation costs associated with the reset and remodel of our retail stores during the quarter.
 Adjusted SG&amp;A delevered 170 basis points during the third quarter driven by Waterworks-related employment and other corporate cost of 70 basis points, one-time costs associated with the retail floor resets and addition of design Antilles in our galleries, and other corporate costs, offset by advertising leverage as we moved our spring sourcebook mailing to the fall. Our adjusted earnings per share of $0.20 includes approximately $0.14 related to the temporal costs and investments impacting gross margin.
 Turning to the balance sheet, inventory at the end of the third quarter was up 2% versus last year. Excluding the addition of Waterworks, RH inventory was down 2% compared to last year, reflecting the significant progress we have made in our inventory optimization efforts. Our diligence in this process has allowed us to remove inefficient SKUs from our assortment, eliminate the need for additional DC occupancy, and improve our working capital.
 Our inventory growth is expected to end the year roughly in line with sales growth as we are benefiting from our SKU rationalization efforts.
 As a result of continued capital discipline, we are lowering our fiscal 2016 CapEx outlook to a range of $180 million to $190 million from our prior range of $180 million to $210 million.
 We opened four next-generation design galleries in fiscal 2016 and remain on track to open five in fiscal 2017, including galleries in West Palm Beach, Toronto, New York, Portland, and Nashville, in addition to a billboard location in the Napa Valley. Accordingly, new store months, excluding Waterworks, are expected to accelerate from 42 in fiscal 2016 to more than 60 new store months in fiscal 2017.
 We are pleased with the progress we are making as it relates to our real estate transformation and the performance of our next-generation design galleries opened thus far, all of which are tracking at or above expectations despite the later sourcebook and macro factors impacting our business in 2016.
 In addition, we are extremely pleased with the performance of the RH Members program. We now have approximately 260,000 customers who have become RH Members, and over 90% of sales in our core business have come through membership since the launch of this program. While we have experienced short-term margin pressure associated with the 25% discount without the full benefit of the membership fee, we believe the program is the right thing for our business and our brand in the long term. As we enter 2017 and anniversary the program, we expect margins to expand as we benefit from both the deferred membership revenue and the renewal of current members. Based on the nature of our business and home-buying cycles, we also expect to continue to attract new members to this program year after year.
 In closing, while there are temporary factors impacting our business in the short term, our long-term growth strategies remain firmly intact. We continue to believe that we have an opportunity to reach $4 billion to $5 billion in North American sales, midteens operating margins, improved returns on invested capital, and drive significant value for our shareholders over the long term.
 We wish you, our team, and all of our partners a very happy holiday season.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[Q3 2016 Restoration Hardware Holdings Inc Video Presentation]]></eventTitle>
  <city>CORTE MADERA</city>
  <companyName>RH</companyName>
  <companyTicker>RH</companyTicker>
  <startDate>8-Dec-16 10:30pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>