<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7330709" lastUpdate="Tuesday, December 27, 2016 at 6:24:15pm GMT" eventTypeId="5" eventTypeName="Corporate Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7330709.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 9:30:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of AVXS conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 9:30pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[AveXis SMA Type 2 Conference Call

BANNOCKBURN Dec 27, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of AveXis Inc conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 9:30:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Jim Goff
      AveXis Inc. - VP, IR and Corporate Communications
   *  Sean Nolan
      AveXis Inc. - President and CEO
   *  Suku Nagendran
      AveXis Inc. - SVP, Chief Medical Officer
   *  Brian Kaspar
      AveXis Inc. - Chief Scientific Officer

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Biren Amin
      Jefferies - Analyst
   *  Ian Somaiya
      BMO Capital Markets - Analyst
   *  Gbola Amusa
      Chardan Capital - Analyst
   *  Yanan Zhu
      Wells Fargo Securities - Analyst
   *  Katherine Breedis
      Stifel - Analyst

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Good afternoon, ladies and gentlemen. (Operator Instructions)
 I would now like to introduce Mr. Jim Goff, Vice President of Investor Relations and Communications. Please go ahead.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jim Goff,  AveXis Inc. - VP, IR and Corporate Communications   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, operator. Hello, everyone, and welcome to this AveXis conference Call to discuss the clinical study on AVXS-101 in SMA Type 2. With us today are Sean Nolan, President and Chief Executive Officer; Dr. Suku Nagendran, our Chief Medical Officer; and Dr. Brian Kaspar, our Chief Scientific Officer are available for questions and answers.
 This conference call and webcast is being recorded. To access the playback, please go to the investors and media section of our website at AveXis.com.
 I would like to remind callers that the information discussed on the call today is covered under the Safe Harbor provisions of the Private Securities Litigation Reform Act. I caution listeners that the company's management will be making forward-looking statements. Actual results could differ materially from those stated or implied by our forward-looking statements due to risks and uncertainties associated with the company's business.
 These forward-looking statements are qualified in their entirety by the cautionary statements contained in today's press release and the company's SEC filings. The content of this conference call contains time-sensitive information that is accurate only as of the date of this live broadcast, December 21, 2016. AveXis undertakes no obligation to revise or update any forward-looking statements to reflect events or circumstances after the date of this conference call, except as required by law.
 This afternoon we issued a press release detailing the content of today's call. A copy can be found within the Investors and Media section at Avexis.com. We'll begin with prepared comments and then we'll open the call for your questions.
 I'd like to now turn the call over to AveXis' President and Chief Executive Officer, Sean Nolan. Sean?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Jim. Good afternoon everyone and thank you for joining us today. As you know, AVXS-101 is our gene therapy candidate currently being studied in an ongoing Phase 1 open-label trial for the treatment of spinal muscular atrophy or SMA Type 1.
 Today, we are reporting that encouraging progress and data emerging from our ongoing manufacturing process development work and ongoing discussions with FDA have led to a strategic decision to use the intended commercial GMP derived product in our plan initial Phase 1 study of AVXS-101 using the intrathecal delivery method for the treatment of patients with SMA Type 2.
 As a brief reminder, SMA is a severe neuromuscular disease caused by a genetic defect in the SMN1 gene and is characterized by the loss of motor neurons leading to progressive muscle weakness. There are several subtypes of SMA but all have the same genetic root cause, which is the deletion or point mutation of the SMN1 gene.
 AVXS-101 is designed to address this monogenetic root cause of SMA by replacing the loss or defective primary SMN1 gene with a fully functioning human SMN gene. SMA Type 1 is the most severe form of the disease and typically has onset in patients younger than six months of age. Symptom onset for SMA Type 2 typically occurs between 6 and 18 months of age. SMA Type 2 is generally characterized by having three copies of SMN2 in contrast to patients with SMA Type 1, who generally have two copies of the SMN2 gene. The hallmark of patients diagnosed with Type 2 SMA is that they will never walk without support. Tragically, more than 30% of patients do not live past the age of 25. There are approximately 5,000 patients who are suffering from SMA Type 2 in the United States.
 Today, we reported that based on emerging data from our intended commercial Good Manufacturing Practice or GMP development work and ongoing discussions with the FDA, that we have made a strategic decision to use the intended commercial, scalable GMP derived product in all future studies of our proprietary gene therapy candidate AVXS-101 including the planned initial Phase 1 trial in patients with spinal muscular atrophy Type 2.
 Originally, we have planned to use existing product inventory for this initial study of Type 2 and then switch to the final commercial process later in development. We see several advantages to using a continuous manufacturing process throughout the study. First, by using the same process for the duration of the Type 2 clinical program, we eliminate the need for a comparability analysis later in development.
 Second, this approach simplifies the development pathway by using one consistent product. And the FDA in general prefers use of a consistent product process and program development, if possible.
 Lastly, this approach potentially accelerates the time frame for gathering clinical data that maybe used as part of the dataset to support a future SMA Type 2 indication by eliminating the product comparability analysis later in development.
 For these reasons and because we have made significant strides with our intended commercial GMP efforts to date, we believe the optimal approach is to use the scalable GMP derived product in our clinical evaluation of AVXS-101 in the SMA Type 2 from the outset. While we had expected to initiate the trial in the second half of 2016, we now expect to initiate the planned study of AVXS-101 in SMA Type 2 patients in the second quarter of 2017, assuming a positive outcome from our plan Type B manufacturing meeting with the FDA.
 We believe the time taken now to allow for the use of the commercial process will result in an overall faster path to potential approval for the Type 2 program for the reasons previously mentioned. As we have previously described, our manufacturing strategy is based on three initiatives which afford us the greatest optionality as we work to evolve our manufacturing capabilities.
 First, we have executed and completed the like for like transfer from the NCH -- of the NCH process using the existing adherent cell process, an HEK293 cells to a third-party manufacture. Second, in parallel with the tech transfer, we have been conducting extensive process development work with other third-parties both upstream, looking at factors such as transfection, harvest, cell growth, cell density, etc. And downstream, looking at purification, collection, empty to full ratio with the capsids with the goal of finding improvements in process efficiency and yield that we can consistently replicate. To be clear in this path, we are continuing to use the same master cell line and maintain an adherent cell approach.
 We are pleased to report encouraging progress to date in regard to those efforts including the fact that we have produced successful engineering runs and we have recently initiated our GMP manufacturing campaign. This recent progress was a key factor in making the strategic decision to use the intended commercial GMP derived product in all future studies of AVXS-101 in SMA including the SMA Type 2 program.
 And third, we are also making great progress on the construction of our own manufacturing facility. As we previously indicated, we continue to expect the clinical trial and perhaps initial commercial supply will be produced by third parties with our facility contributing to the mix as it comes online.
 We are continuing to gather data and we'll submit it to the FDA in advance of our Type B CMC meeting, which we continue to expect the schedule in the first quarter of 2017. Recall the purpose of the Type B CMC meeting is to gain FDA feedback on our intended commercial GMP process. We look forward to sharing additional information once we have received the minutes from that meeting as we did following the previous Type B meeting regarding the clinical development path.
 The approach we've announced today is intended to potentially expedite the SMA Type 2 program and there's no impact to what we have previously stated about the SMA Type 1 program. We remain on track to initiate the U.S. pivotal trial in SMA Type 1 in the first half of 2017 and we used the same intended commercial process in that study.
 In concluding our prepared remarks, I would like to add in an effort for continued transparency that we wanted to provide you this update on the timing of the Type 2 study today. There were a confluence of factors that contributed to the timing of the announcement including the real-time date we received as part of our work to advance the intended commercial GMP derived product.
 Although the strategic decision will impact the plan initiation of the SMA Type 2 trial, we believe it has the potential to streamline the development of the dataset for AVXS-101 in SMA Type 2. Ultimately, we believe the strategy we've shared with you today is the optimal path and potentially the fastest path to developing a dataset that might be used to support an indication in SMA Type 2 and allow us to best realize our goal of getting the therapy approve for as many SMA patients as soon as possible.
 We will now open the call to your questions. Operator, please poll for questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ladies and gentlemen, the question-and-answer queue is now open. (Operator Instructions)
 We'll be taking our first question from the line of Salveen Richter from Goldman Sachs. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Unidentified Participant   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi, this is actually [Tom] on for Salveen. Thanks for taking the question. The decision seems logical given it could potentially allow expedite development in SMA Type 2. I'm just curious given you are starting the Phase 1 now with commercial material, is there any chance that the design of that trial could actually be a pivotal Phase 1/2 for example, or do you expect just to run a second trial there? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Tom, great question, thank you very much. We'll definitely be providing more insight into the trial design once we announce the initiation of the trial. Obviously, we do as much advanced planning, contingency planning upfront to think about and make sure that we have the greatest flexibility to provide a study design that will allow for optimal flexibility based on the results derived from that initial study. Hopefully, that helps you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Our next question comes from the line of Biren Amin from Jefferies. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Biren Amin,  Jefferies - Analyst   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, thanks guys for taking my question. Sean, I think you mentioned on the prepared remarks that you saw some emerging data from your GMP work and also you had discussions with FDA. Did you have -- have you shared that GMP data with FDA and as a result came to this conclusion?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So basically the way to think about this Biren is that we are -- we are in very, very close dialogue with the FDA on a number of matters and where we are right now with the manufacturing process is continuing to gather information in a very real-time basis. So, what we're sharing with you today, again, is data that's coming in -- essentially daily we're getting progress reports on things of that nature.
 What we're doing in our plan is essentially to go to the FDA with the most fulsome package we possibly can to have that CMC Type B meeting in the first quarter. So, what we want to do is collect all the data we possibly can and leverage that to have the most -- the productive discussion with the FDA in a very similar fashion to how we've approached other discussions with them including the request for breakthrough designation.
 So, we're in the process of continuing to collect all information that we think is most necessary and actionable for that meeting and we plan to hold that meeting in the first quarter and as we've indicated, we will then share the results and the outputs of that meeting with you once we have the minutes.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Biren Amin,  Jefferies - Analyst   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 And just a follow-up, the analysis that you're gathering, are you focus on, I guess, potency, its identity, and genetics ability of the product and are you comparing it -- that nationwide product that was produced and is that what's going to be submitted to FDA ahead of that Type B meeting?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 There's a great deal of information. Obviously, that's going to be submitted in advance of that meeting. Part of that package obviously will be a reconciliation of the comparability of the NCH product to what we're defining to be our commercial manufactured process. So, that is part of the package that will be submitted to the FDA.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Biren Amin,  Jefferies - Analyst   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay and then just a last question. As it relates to the commercial readiness for Type 1, is this something that could potentially influence your ability to be ready for potential accelerated application for the Type 1 indication?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Can you clarify that question just a little bit? I want to make sure that I answer specifically what you're asking.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Biren Amin,  Jefferies - Analyst   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So if you're able to proceed forward with an accelerated file for the Type 1 indication at some point in 2017 based on completion and review of the Phase 1 data that's currently underway, will you be able to transition to this commercial product and will that be in the filing application if you're able to file on an accelerated basis at some point in 2017?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I think -- I think the short answer to that question, Biren, is it's -- it would be a discussion we have at the end of Phase 1 meeting, right. So, the plan is that we have the -- just to do it sequentially. We're going to have the CMC Type B meeting with the FDA in the first quarter. That's where we're going through and with them our recommendation of the commercial process. That product obviously -- our agreement, congruence there allows us then to proceed with the study that we're talking about here, the Type 2 study but also enable the pivotal U.S. study as well.
 The next step is an end of Phase 1 meeting with the FDA. Likely, that will be in the second quarter, it could be in the third quarter and I'll explain why that could be in just a moment. That meeting will be to go through the final study, end of study results from the ongoing Phase 1 SMA Type 1 trial. And as the FDA has outlined and we've communicated in previous disclosures, step one in that meeting is to talk about the viability and the strength of the existing dataset to support overall registration. And based on the strength of that data, could open a discussion around a potential accelerated approval path.
 That's where, again, I think there's a number of scenarios that could occur. One of which would be -- the FDA wanting to see on one extreme see us run the confirmatory study with the new product and complete that study and then submit the results. At the other end of that would be a scenario where they feel that the comparability data that we're submitting is sufficient and if we initiated and begin enrolling the confirmatory study, potentially we could be talking about an accelerated approval there or there could be one in the middle.
 And there's probably a continuum here where the FDA may want to see a number of patients for some period of time of being treated with this product to make sure that there was consistency in effect and in safety with what they've observed thus far. So hopefully that gives you a little flavor of the pathway and the timing that we're looking at.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Our next question comes from the line of Ian Somaiya from BMO Capital Markets. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, just two questions. One, can you just remind us of the capacity of this plan will be, just how many patients you'll be able to treat? And second, was your decision to use the final product at all influenced by [some notion] and potential for that product to get approve for Type 1 and Type 2 patients?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, Ian, the answer to the second question is no. This was a strategic decision based on the reasons that we put forward. We did not look at this through the lens of what another company maybe doing at this particular juncture.
 The second question regarding -- can you just clarify the question.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Just from the capacity, the manufacturing capacity. How many patients do you think you can treat the -- from the commercial so far?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [17]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, I would say this at a very high level, we know that to have the study start, our goal will be to have product inventory for the U.S. pivotal trial. We want to have inventory for the Type 2 trial that we're talking about and we're feeling encouraged with where we are right now to guide the timelines that we've indicated. Beyond that, I think you'll see our plan will be to provide more detail around specifically the manufacturing process and capacity of things of that nature once we have that Type B meeting with the FDA and have the minutes from that meeting.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ian Somaiya,  BMO Capital Markets - Analyst   [18]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 All right. Sean, does it make sense to just increase the size of the Type 2 study, just generate as much data possible while you have -- while you still have access to patients? I know you want to obviously wait to have the FDA discussion, but does that just seems intuitive right now.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [19]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, I think that's a very valid point and obviously those are the type of things that as we've thought about what that protocol design looks like and what we want to accomplish we're -- I would say we have thought through that and we're very confident and what we're putting forward is the right approach that again allows us to maximize the dataset. And again, we'll provide more detail on that once we initiate the trial.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [20]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Our next question comes from the line of Gbola Amusa from Chardan Capital. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Gbola Amusa,  Chardan Capital - Analyst   [21]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 All right. Thanks for taking my call, and I apologize but I joined about 10 minutes in, so I hope my questions weren't covered already. But my question is how do you plan to define the SMA Type 2 patients in any upcoming trials? And secondly, how did you define your Type 1 patients in the ongoing trial and why do you feel confident that that definition is consistent with natural history data in terms of what that data predicts for outcomes?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [22]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, Gbola, the high-level answer to the first question is essentially similar to what we did in the Type 1 trial, we'll use a combination of clinical diagnosis and genotyping. So, we will use what is considered the standard of care and diagnosis to make sure that we're getting the most consistent patient types possible in the clinical trials.
 Relative to the Type 1 program, we really -- I'll walk you through it. I think we've done everything you possibly can do to make sure that we're looking at the appropriate defined patient having a Type 1 diagnosis. And what I mean by that is all the -- all the children in the Type 1 trial had clinical presentation of symptoms in the first six months of age.
 Number two, all of the kids were tested at the site in genotypes to determine that they only had two copies of SMN2. And in general, if you look at our studies, if you look at other studies that are going on in the field in SMA Type 1, everyone is very consistent in using clinical symptom onset less than six months and two copies of SMN2 for their trial. So, I think we're very consistent there.
 In addition to that, what we did in the ongoing trial for Type 1 is we also excluded for the only known clinically meaningful modifier, the exon 7 Modifier, so that could predict if you have that modifier a less severe form of the disease, we excluded that patient.
 Now, in addition to that, what we did is we actually reconsented patients and then rerun the genotyping at an independent facility and confirmed again the two copies of SMN2 and we also confirmed that there was no modifier there. So, we feel that we've done everything you possibly can to, if you will, ensure that the patients that you're looking at truly have SMA Type 1.
 And the only other thing I would -- I would comment on is the fact to keep in mind many of these patients came from outside the call of the recruitment area or the catchment area in the Midwest. So, as an example we have children from Australia, we have children from Montreal, multiple states and in fact most of these kids including that there was one child who had a very high CHOP-INTEND score as an example that came from Texas, so these kids were diagnosed oftentimes in other facilities and then referred and that's where the genotyping occurred.
 So, again to the best of our ability, we have made sure that these kids have SMA Type 1 and I also think if you talk to KOLs, they would be very consistent in the criteria that we're using is the best known proven scientific methodology to ensure that you've got the appropriate study population.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Gbola Amusa,  Chardan Capital - Analyst   [23]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thanks, that's helpful. Can you talk about the distinction between point mutations and deletions and how the single study, for example, is defined versus your Phase 1 study, just to see if they're comparable for example.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [24]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sure. I would ask -- I'd ask Suku to comment on that question. Just one introductory comment would be at a very macro level, number one, about 95% of SMA Type 1 is based on a deletion of 5% on the point mutation. There is a view that if you have a point mutation that there may be a less severe manifestation of the disease. I can tell you that all 15 of the kids and our ongoing trial have the deletion. Nobody has the point mutation.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Gbola Amusa,  Chardan Capital - Analyst   [25]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Okay, and has that been stated previously?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [26]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I would ask Suku to comment further relative to the PNCR data.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Suku Nagendran,  AveXis Inc. - SVP, Chief Medical Officer   [27]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, thanks, Sean. Hi, Gbola. How are you? So, as Sean said, almost 95% of patients with SMA 1 have deletions; and in our study, all our patients had biallelic deletions. And actually if you look at the largest databases out there, you would find that point mutation is actually quite uncommon. And with regards to the clinical phenotype of point mutations being milder, I would say that's still unclear because there haven't been a collective pool of patients with point mutations, I would say, to do an adequate assessment.
 Now, to answer your question around the Finkel or PNCR dataset, all those patients in the SMA1 category had biallelic deletions and not point mutations.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [28]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Our next question comes from the line of Jim Birchenough from Wells Fargo Securities. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yanan Zhu,  Wells Fargo Securities - Analyst   [29]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hi, thanks for taking the question. This is actually Yanan in for Jim. The first -- a couple of questions on the intrathecal delivery and the dose, so would you be able to comment on the dose that is going to be used in the intrathecal Type 2 study whether -- comparing it to the dose used in the Type 1 studies because it's intrathecal, I think it could be potentially a lot lower, but just wondering if you are able to comment on that.
 And then also would you be able to talk about the extent of -- the extent that AAV vector could move about in the -- within the CNS after the intrathecal injection to transduce the neurons and whether it matters -- whether the AAV could transduce the upper motor neuron versus the lower motor neuron. And maybe related to that which of the spinal cord segment are you planning to do the intrathecal injection? Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [30]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 You're welcome. I would ask Suku to please take the first question and then Brian Kaspar to please take the second question. Suku?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Suku Nagendran,  AveXis Inc. - SVP, Chief Medical Officer   [31]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, thanks, Sean. So, with regards to the actual dose, we will actually disclose and get into details as we launched the study and walk you through the protocol with regard -- and with regards to giving you a much greater detail with regards to the actual dose that we plan to study. But what I can say at the present time is that the doses that we plan to evaluate is also based off of some of the work that Brian and his team have done from a preclinical standpoint, which I will allow him to give more detail, which we think will translate directly into the Phase 1 trial in children with SMA 2 as well. Brian?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Brian Kaspar,  AveXis Inc. - Chief Scientific Officer   [32]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great, thank you, Suku, and happy to address these questions regarding our delivery. We have extensive experience with the use of intrathecal delivery of the adeno-associated virus serotype 9 for effective targeting of both lower as well as upper motor neurons. So, we have spent many years in performing preclinical studies along with safety studies with the use of intrathecal delivery so that is delivering into the cerebral spinal fluid of the AAV9 vectors.
 We performed extensive characterization of when we have delivered AAV9 into the CSF and our translational studies in non-human primates have injected at the lumbar enlargement into the CSF space where we have delivered a bolus injection.
 We've published this work in peer-reviewed journals and have extensive characterizations again as far as where the AAV vector goes, what is the proper dosing that should be achieved. And let me just highlight that we have done extensive characterization of the brain of the motor neurons that reside within the brain and paying very particular attention to the brain stem such as the hypoglossal and trigeminal nuclei. These regions are very important for respiration as well as the swallow reflex as well as the cervical, thoracic and lumbar regions of the spinal cord.
 So, again our primary cell target within the central components of the disease, are motor neurons. Again, our delivery and the dosings that we have derived in our preclinical studies have effectively allowed us to target those neurons and more specifically motor neurons at very high efficiencies.
 Our safety data to date has been extremely safe and well-tolerated following again a one-time bolus injection into the cerebrospinal fluid. These studies have been performed in mice as well as non-human primates. Hopefully, that provides you the answers to those questions.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yanan Zhu,  Wells Fargo Securities - Analyst   [33]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, it does. Thank you very much. Lastly, a very quick question, on the scalability of the manufacturing system given that it is adherent cell system, so I'm just curious on the scalability of the system. Thanks.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [34]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, so there are a number of things we're looking at as we talked about. On one hand, we have been doing and we have successfully completed the tech transfer from NCH to a third-party manufacturer which is HYPERStack which is one type of an adherent cell technology. And that other path that I mentioned, we will keep an adherent cell basis, we're not going to move into something like suspension or what have you, but there are other -- there are other mechanisms, other means, other bioreactors to take a look at that could potentially help improve the scalability over the existing process.
 So, we're pleased with both paths and the progress that we've made and we'll continue to share more information with you subsequent to the FDA CMC meeting we have planned in the first quarter.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [35]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions)
 Our next question comes from the line of Katherine Breedis from Stifel. Your line is open.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Katherine Breedis,  Stifel - Analyst   [36]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great, thank you very much for taking my questions. The first question is have you completed the comparability analysis of AVXS-101 manufactured for the NCH trial versus the material manufactured by your contract manufacturer that will ultimately be used in the upcoming SMA Type 1 pivotal study?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [37]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, as I mentioned at the onset, Katherine, that there is a great deal of work that is -- that is coming in real time and ongoing and obviously a core to the discussion that we're going to have with the FDA at that Type B CMC meeting is exactly that. So, at this point in time, we continue to build the dataset and bring in what is needed to have that most productive and constructive conversation. And again as we've outlined, once we have that meeting, we'll definitely sit down and share that information with all of you.
 I do just want to make the point again that based on the progress that we're seeing and the work that's been done thus far, we're encouraged by the process and the progress.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Katherine Breedis,  Stifel - Analyst   [38]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's great. Could you help us understand the requirements for doing the comparability analysis and how this change in plan to enroll the SMA Type 2 patients with the GMP material will actually translate into time savings long range?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [39]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Well, I think at a high level, it's essentially this, if you use a let's call it product source A in your initial study and yet that's not going to be the final process that you're going to use from a commercial GMP perspective, the FDA generally prefers that in your pivotal trials you use that final process -- you use that final process and product. So, the point is if you don't start with it, at some point you have to tie back to it.
 And that can be a function of a combination of preclinical work to tie back, but oftentimes there's bridging studies that are required where you may have to dose a subset of patients and tie back and demonstrate consistent efficacy, consistent safety and alignment around the dosing. So, it's simpler to move forward with one product if you can do that; and if you can't, again there's that added steps sometimes that you have to go through.
 So, for those reasons, we felt that if we could start the study with the GMP type product that was the most expeditious way to facilitate the overall program and ultimately the review of the data to get it to the patients as quickly as possible. We're effectively removing a step.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Katherine Breedis,  Stifel - Analyst   [40]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Right. And this will ultimately be the product that you take into commercialization apart from the ongoing work that you have at your liberty bill facility is that correct?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [41]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 So, the short answer is that the product that we are talking about -- the process that we're talking about, the GMP process, the product derived from that we will use in the Type 2 trial that we're discussing in the -- in the pivotal U.S. trial that we're discussing and that it would be the commercial product as well and that product will be made at third-party manufacturers, but also in the AveXis facility.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Katherine Breedis,  Stifel - Analyst   [42]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Terrific. And then one last question, are there material differences in the properties of the intrathecal formulation of AVXS-101 for SMA Type 2 versus the IV dose of AVXS-101 for SMA Type 1 or is it simply a difference based on volume?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [43]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Now, the difference at this point is based on volume and route of administration.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [44]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions)
 I'm seeing no other questioners from the queue at this time, so I would like to turn the call back over to management for closing comments.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Sean Nolan,  AveXis Inc. - President and CEO   [45]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you very much, operator.
 Again, appreciate everyone's time today. Hopefully, you get an appreciation for the rationale, the strategic decision that went into making this happen and we ultimately feel this is the best path forward -- the optimal path forward for patients and that will ultimately reduce the time to development and get AVXS-101 to the Type 2 patient population as quickly and as safely as possible. We thank you for your time and your interest. Have a good night.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [46]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ladies and gentlemen, thank you again for your participation in today's conference. This now concludes the program and you may all disconnect at this time.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[AveXis SMA Type 2 Conference Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>BANNOCKBURN</city>
  <companyName>AveXis Inc</companyName>
  <companyTicker>AVXS</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 9:30pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>