<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7331098" lastUpdate="Thursday, December 22, 2016 at 11:10:20am GMT" eventTypeId="5" eventTypeName="Corporate Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7331098.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 12:00:00pm GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of 853.HK conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 12:00pm GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[MicroPort Scientific Corp Corporate Call

Shanghai Dec 22, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of MicroPort Scientific Corp conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 12:00:00pm GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Jonathan Chen
      MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR
   *  Martin Sun
      MicroPort Scientific Corp - CFO

================================================================================
Conference Call Participants
================================================================================
   *  Jessica Li
      BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ladies and gentlemen, thank you for standing by and welcome to the recent Company updates conference call. (Operator Instructions). I must advise you that this conference is being recorded today, December 21, 2016.
 I would now like to hand the conference over to your first speaker today, Miss Jessica Li. Please go ahead, ma'am. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Good morning and good evening, everyone. I am Jessica Li, China Healthcare analyst at Bank of America, Merrill Lynch. We appreciate your participation in MicroPort's conference call to discuss its investment and strategic partnership with Lombard Medical.
 Conflict disclosures relating to the individual companies or securities discussed on this call today can be found on the call invitation. There will be a replay of today's call, details of which are also included in the call invitation.
 With me today are Mr. Martin Sun, CFO; Mr. Jonathan Chen, Senior VP of International Business Operations and IR; and Miss Leanne Li, Board Secretary.
 And now, I would like to turn the call over to Jonathan for a briefing on the strategic investment and partnership with Lombard. Jonathan.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you very much, Jessica. Good morning and good evening to everyone. MicroPort management is pleased to have announced yesterday an investment agreement and strategic partnership transaction with Lombard Medical, a publicly traded medical device company based in the United Kingdom that specializes in developing innovative stent graft medical devices to treat patients suffering from abdominal aortic aneurysms.
 The key highlights of the transactions are as follows. There is an equity investment of $5 million in Lombard common stock and this is issued at a price of $0.62 per share, representing a discount of approximately 23% to the Lombard closing stock price on December 16, 2016. This equity investment represents a MicroPort ownership percentage of approximately 29%.
 Second, a convertible bond issued by Lombard in the principal amount of $10 million, with an interest rate of LIBOR plus 4% with interest payment in kind. The term of the convertible bond is five years with a conversion price of $0.90 per share, representing a premium of approximately 12% to Lombard closing stock price on December 16, 2016.
 The underlying shares of the convertible bond are approximately 11.1 million shares. And the ranking of the convertible bond is unsecured and subordinated to Lombard's existing senior debt.
 The strategic partnership between MicroPort and Lombard will have the following elements. First, China distribution and manufacturing rights to Lombard's two key products, Altura and Aorfix. MicroPort will be granted exclusive commercial manufacturing rights for these two products for the territory of Mainland China, Hong Kong and Macau.
 We also have a component manufacturing agreement. Both parties recognize the importance of reducing the current cost of manufacturing for Lombard's two products. As a result of this manufacturing agreement, MicroPort will manufacture certain components of Lombard's Aorfix and Altura devices at our endovascular manufacturing facility in Shanghai, where our current MicroPort endovascular business has extensive manufacturing expertise for producing stent grafts for our current China business.
 And third, we have obtained Brazilian registration and distribution rights for Altura and Aorfix. MicroPort will register these two products with the Brazil regulatory body and exclusively distribute products upon receipt of regulatory approval.
 The parties have agreed to finalize agreements for the above within 90 days of closing. And, as part of this transaction, Lombard Medical will reconfigure its Board of Directors to have five Board members, two of which will be MicroPort representatives.
 I'll now summarize, very quickly, the endovascular aortic repair market; we call it EVAR. The global EVAR market is a large, growing market with room for expansion and according to industry reports, in 2015 this market was approximately $1.6 billion and growing at approximately 6% per year.
 The key industry drivers are an aging and westernization of the global population; number two, conversion from open surgical repair to EVAR procedures that's facilitated by technology such as Lombard's. Approximately 75% of the AAA cases today are performed using EVAR, as compared to only 45% cases in 2007.
 Third, we have expanding indications with newer technologies for this market; four, we have strong reimbursement and screening; and five, AAA still is considerably under-diagnosed. It's estimated that approximately only 10% of all AAA procedures are currently being diagnosed. In the US alone there are approximately 200,000 patients diagnosed every year with AAA. This market is still highly fragmented and still a percentage of the aneurysm patients have very difficult to treat neck angles and comorbidities that will need longer hospital stays and appropriate devices to treat their complex anatomies.
 Today, almost two-thirds of the patients with AAA are EVAR candidates. The other one-third constitute important market segment, but extending EVAR to these patients may be challenging due to patients with challenging neck anatomy, including short necks, highly angulated necks or large diameter necks. Outcomes for these patients tend to be worse than in those with standard anatomy and it's difficult to pose the stent grafts and avoid migration or blood leakage.
 Lombard Medical has a portfolio of products that offer on-label treatment options for up to 85% of AAA patient cases, including those with challenging anatomy and not treatable by many other standard industry stent grafts. Lombard's two EVAR stent graft systems, Altura and Aorfix, treat a multitude of patients with AAA.
 I'll now begin to describe each of these technologies; first, with Altura. For patients with uncomplicated aortic anatomy, Altura is specifically designed to simplify treatment of patients with normal AAA anatomy. This Altura stent graft system is CE marked, is ultra low profile at 14-French diameter, and consists of two D-shaped kissing stents that overlap with distal segments for each iliac artery.
 The noteworthy features of Altura are as follows: it has an uncommonly low profile delivery system at 14-French; number two, it eliminates the need to cannulate the grafts in the main body; number three, its full device repositioning ability during the procedure.
 At this year's VEITHsymposium in New York in November 2016, the Altura stent graft was featured in a scientific presentation by Dr. David Murray, a vascular surgeon based in Manchester in the UK.
 The data showed that out of 24 patients that were treated electively, about 75%, or 18 patients, were discharged at or before 24 hours. There were no deaths within 90 days, there were no immediate or delayed access-related complications, and deployment time was 19 to 45 minutes, which is significantly lower than cases treated with other stent grafts. Technical success was 100% with freedom from type 1 or type 3 endoleaks at 100%, and there is no evidence of stent graft migration.
 In addition to this early safety and clinical success, Altura has a very low inventory management feature where we only need six product codes to treat all different types of AAA cases. This compares to competitor stent graft systems that have upwards of 30 product codes in order to have consignment stock.
 The real potential for Altura is that it can be able to deliver outpatient EVAR, meaning that patients can receive the EVAR procedure and be home after surgery the same day. This not only increases patient satisfaction with the procedure, but significantly and radically changes the health economics of treating AAA patients. The company estimates that 50% to 75% of patients could ultimately be eligible for outpatient EVAR.
 Currently, Lombard has commercially launched Altura in the UK and in Germany, and has started the commercial launch in early 2016. The company expects to activate upwards of 20 centers with using the Altura stent graft in those countries.
 As for US approval, Lombard anticipates IDE approval in 2017. The company has already filed for IDE, made their IDE submission in 2016, and expectation of patient enrolment starting in second half of 2017, with potential FDA approval sometime in 2020.
 Next, I will discuss Aorfix, the second stent graft system from Lombard. For patients with both routine and difficult anatomy, there is Aorfix, which is a CE marked and FDA approved stent graft system that is specifically indicated for aortic necks angulated up to 90 degrees. Most market-leading aortic stent grafts are only approved for a 60 degree or less angulation, so in this respect Aorfix is very specialized.
 At this year's VEITHsymposium, Professor Mahmoud Malas of Johns Hopkins University presented five-year clinical data from Lombard's US PYTHAGORAS trial for Aorfix. The trial studied 218 patients, 151 which had neck angles of 60 degrees and higher, which are off-label for all other approved stent grafts available in the US market.
 Professor Malas showed that this group of patients had several other characteristics that were predictive of poor outcomes, including a very high percentage of female patients and higher average age. At the fifth year, there were no type 1 or 3 endoleaks, migration was seen at 3.3% of cases, in line with other stents, and freedom from aneurysm-related mortality in patients with neck angles 60 degrees and greater was 95%. This rose to 99% in patients with neck angles less than 60 degrees.
 Based on this data, Professor Malas concluded that these patients, having severely challenging anatomy and multiple other predictions of poor outcomes, the performance of Aorfix after five years is very similar to that of competitor devices in normal risk patients. This long-term data has been accepted for publication by Journal of Vascular Surgery and will be published in the coming months. FDA approved the Aorfix device in 2013 and currently, to date, there have been over 4,000 patients worldwide that have been implanted with Aorfix.
 Lombard recently introduced a new delivery system called IntelliFlex for Aorfix, which is a lower profile delivery system, sized at 15-French and 18-French. The company received CE Mark approval for IntelliFlex in mid-2016 and has already begin to sell the delivery device in Europe, where the company has seen an increase in adoption of the Aorfix in Europe. The company will need to complete an IDE trial in the US for IntelliFlex to gain FDA approval and expects to do so sometime mid-2017.
 Now, I begin to speak, summarize MicroPort's transaction rationale. So recall that MicroPort's endovascular business is a market leader in the China endovascular market. And this year, MicroPort's endovascular business is the fastest growing within MicroPort, growing at 40% in the first half of 2016, compared to the first half of 2015. With this strategic partnership with Lombard, MicroPort believes that we've strengthened our existing endovascular business.
 First, MicroPort has expanded our technology portfolio of MicroPort's endovascular business by securing the distribution rights for Altura and Aorfix for the China market. With the combined portfolio of our existing endovascular business with Altura and Aorfix would create the broadest product portfolio for the endovascular AAA market in China to address multiple segments, market segments.
 MicroPort endovascular will bring to the China market additional stent graft systems that can treat difficult to treat aortic neck anatomies, and also offer a stent graft system that could potentially allow same-day outpatient AAA procedures without sacrificing long-term patient safety. These are both consistent with MicroPort's mantra of the patient comes first.
 In addition, MicroPort endovascular will be the only endovascular business in China that can offer both a low profile AAA device and a low profile TAA device, which our endo business already sells. This is a very powerful combination. MicroPort endovascular will begin the work in the CFDA registration process for both Aorfix and Altura in 2017 and we would expect that CFDA approval for these devices to be sometime in late 2019.
 Second, through the strategic partnership, MicroPort will leverage our endovascular business their manufacturing expertise in manufacturing these endovascular devices. This will significantly improve the gross margin of both Altura and Aorfix, which is currently a limitation from Lombard's product portfolio. And having increased the gross margin, we will significantly increase the profitability for both of these devices. MicroPort endovascular has the expertise in manufacturing endovascular devices in our facility in Shanghai.
 In the near term, MicroPort endovascular will produce lower cost components for both Lombard's Altura and Aorfix systems. In the long term, MicroPort endovascular will have the China manufacturing rights to support the commercialization of Altura and Aorfix for the China market. Both of these activities will significantly leverage the existing MicroPort endovascular operations.
 Third, through this strategic partnership, MicroPort will expand our endovascular business in international markets by securing the commercial rights of Aorfix and Altura for Brazil. Brazil is an emerging market economy that offers growth potential in the endovascular market.
 From a commercial standpoint, the addition of these two devices leverages the commercial activities that MicroPort has previously executed in our base international business with cross-border interactions between China and Brazil endovascular surgeons. MicroPort's regulatory team will register Aorfix and Altura with the Brazil regulatory body and we anticipate receiving approvals in sometime in late 2019.
 In summary, we believe that this Lombard Medical transaction is an exciting development for MicroPort endovascular business and MicroPort Scientific. Just as a reminder that, due to the fact that Lombard Medical is a publicly traded company on NASDAQ, we're limited to sharing information on the company, only to what previously has been disclosed publicly by Lombard. Accordingly, we'll update our investors on the financial impact of this transaction for the year 2017 in our March 2017 investor call.
 I will pause there for the formal comments. And now, I'll turn it over to the operator and open it up for any questions.
================================================================================
Questions and Answers
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Jonathan, on the briefing. We'll now begin question and answer session. As we are waiting for the questions to be queued up, I will maybe ask a couple of questions, if you don't mind?
 First of all, congratulations on your investment. I think the first question comes to my mind is, how does this company, Lombard, come to your attention? Why did you pick to form a strategic partnership with Lombard, not somebody else? And do you have any intention to potentially acquire the whole company? So that's one.
 And then, two, can you just comment a little bit more on the sales potential or peak sales for the two products in China and Brazil? So why these two regions? Obviously, it makes perfect sense for you [to work and provide] in China, but why Brazil? Why not other regions? Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Sun,  MicroPort Scientific Corp - CFO   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica, thank you for your question. This is Martin. I try to answer this first question, why we considered, why we choose Lombard. Because as we mentioned before, first, MicroPort we have the endovascular business. We are the market leaders in the China endovascular market. Our endovascular market in China grows very fast. So with this strategic partnership, we think that Lombard is the best one because, first, Lombard has great technologies.
 As Jonathan mentioned before a lot to introduce the features of this there are two AAA products. One is the Aorfix. Aorfix is the only stent graft to hold global approval for the uniquely treat AAA with aortic neck angles up to 90 degrees. And another one is also we are very interesting is Altura, because Altura right now they have a very innovative design and the low profile 14-French delivery systems. So we have some PPT already uploaded to our IR section for all the investors can assess that.
 You can know in the future, MicroPort also we want to touch the subcutaneous EVAR market and Altura is one of the best devices for us to touch that market. So that is the technology wise. And also, you can see that because of this strategic partnership, MicroPort can leverage MicroPort's endo expertise in manufactured device then to help Lombard to improve their gross margin, reduce significantly their manufacturing cost.
 You can see Lombard right now is a loss-making company listed in NASDAQ. I think one of the root cause for their loss is their very low gross margin. So if leverage our MicroPort's manufacturing expertise, I think we believe that we can help the Lombard company to get a higher gross margin and a very nice profitability to continuously expand their technology and products.
 The third, of course, that is with this strategic partnership and we think that's the win-win strategy because MicroPort right now is the leading position in the China market. We have also very great products like we call the TAA and AAA products, Hercules and Aegis. We have a quite small international infrastructure, like in European and in Japan. So then right now, we have the Lombard strategic partnership so we can leverage that and Lombard team can help us to commercialize MicroPort's products on international markets. So that's why we choose this. Lombard is a great company; we should invest [in that].
 Jonathan, you can add some more comments.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [3]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, I think Martin touched on all the strong points. It's a very good match in terms of capabilities between Lombard and MicroPort endovascular, particularly on the manufacturing side. That is of paramount importance in the near term to reduce the manufacturing costs.
 And then it's a good match also for geography in our endovascular business. Outside of China, the next largest market for our current endovascular business is Brazil. So that's why it was an opportunity to increase our portfolio for the Brazil market and also the pipeline for the Brazil market. Both Aorfix and Altura will have to go through registration, and so it will be at least a couple of years before we'll be in a position to sell profitability in Brazil.
 It also takes some time to help with reducing the manufacturing costs. So we feel that this is in terms of timing and for seeding the future pipeline for both our China business and international business, this is a great match for us.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [4]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 How about answering peak sales questions?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [5]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 I would answer the question peak sales potentially this way. So if you look at who are the top competitors in the endovascular market, AAA market, there's Medtronic, Cook and Gore, those are principally the top three market share leaders, globally. Additionally, in China market, we are in the top three in terms of market share. And I would say that our peak market share, if you look at our China business, is quite strong. It's high 20%, roughly 30%.
 I think, for these devices, we viewed the endovascular market is that not one device is going to be able to treat all AAA cases. We do see market segmentation; there's difficult to treat anatomies that will require different types of devices. And so we feel that this product portfolio will help us certainly maintain our market share lead in China and certainly increase our market share lead.
 But certainly, in the geographies outside of China, particularly in Europe and in the US and international markets, currently Lombard is not in that top three. Certainly, in the US, they still have to get approval for Altura and so I think a reasonable expectation of peak market share is in that 15% to 20% range for those Western countries. But it takes some time to get to that point; it's not on day one that we'll be able to achieve that.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [6]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. Thank you so much. Operator?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [7]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 (Operator Instructions). No questions at the moment, ma'am. Over to you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [8]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Great. I think everyone is getting ready to celebrate Christmas and New Year. I think I won't have any more questions, so I will turn over to the management and see whether you would have any closing remarks, Martin or Jonathan?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [9]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 This is Jonathan. I think it's probably yearend and so it's been a long year and people are probably getting ready for the holidays. But I do want to mention that MicroPort management, both Martin and I, will be at JPMorgan conference in a few weeks in San Francisco and so certainly welcome the opportunity to further discuss this transaction, and also MicroPort in general, with our investors and analysts at that point as well.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [10]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's great. Martin?
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Sun,  MicroPort Scientific Corp - CFO   [11]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Yes, I think it's good. Thank you, Jessica. As Jonathan mentioned, for MicroPort management we are quite very welcome to every questions from the investors, today and also futures. Just also for information, if the investors or analysts want to get more information about Lombard, I think Lombard right now still remain a NASDAQ listing public company, so it is quite easy for all of you to get more information about the products, about the financials. And also I think at the beginning of next year, Lombard will give also the guidance of 2017 to all of the interested investors. So I think, for this transaction, all the information quite be transparent to everyone.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jessica Li,  BofA Merrill Lynch - Moderator   [12]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 That's great. Thank you so much and thank you, everyone, for dialing in, in this holiday season. I wish everyone a Merry Christmas and Happy New Year. Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [13]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you, Jessica.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Martin Sun,  MicroPort Scientific Corp - CFO   [14]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Jonathan Chen,  MicroPort Scientific Corporation - SVP, International Business Operations &amp; IR   [15]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Thank you. Goodbye.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Operator   [16]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Ladies and gentlemen, that does conclude our conference for today. Thank you for participating, you may all disconnect now.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[MicroPort Scientific Corp Corporate Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>Shanghai</city>
  <companyName>MicroPort Scientific Corp</companyName>
  <companyTicker>853.HK</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 12:00pm GMT</startDate>
</Event>