<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?>
<Event Id="7331107" lastUpdate="Thursday, December 22, 2016 at 11:11:51am GMT" eventTypeId="34" eventTypeName="M&amp;A Conference Call/Presentation">
  <EventStory Id="7331107.F" expirationDate="Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 10:59:00am GMT" action="publish" storyType="transcript" version="Final">
    <Headline><![CDATA[Edited Transcript of 6762.T M&A conference call or presentation 21-Dec-16 10:59am GMT]]></Headline>
    <Body><![CDATA[TDK Corp to Acquire InvenSense Inc Conference Call

Tokyo Dec 22, 2016 (Thomson StreetEvents) -- Edited Transcript of TDK Corp M&A conference call or presentation Wednesday, December 21, 2016 at 10:59:00am GMT

TEXT version of Transcript

================================================================================
Corporate Participants
================================================================================
   *  Shigenao Ishiguro
      TDK Corp - President &amp; CEO

================================================================================
Presentation
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Shigenao Ishiguro,  TDK Corp - President &amp; CEO   [1]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Hello, everybody. This is Ishiguro speaking from TDK. First of all, I'd like to thank you for your precious time, despite your busy schedule.
 TDK, in our Board meeting, actually had a resolution to acquire the stocks of the global inertial sensors company, InvenSense, to make it a wholly owned subsidiary.
 As for details, please can you refer to the joint press release we have disclosed as of 17:00, as well as the (inaudible) materials that we have disclosed.
 Without further ado I'd like to make the following presentation to help you. And please refer to page 2. This shows the outline of the acquisition. The total acquisition value, in terms of the stock value, $1.3 billion or JPY157.2 billion; in terms of the corporate value basis, $1.2 billion or JPY145.6 billion.
 This is actually $13.00 per stock and compared with [gross] stock and as of December 20, 2016, this is going to be 19.9% premium to the stock price then. And we do believe that we should be able to cover the whole of the required money for the acquisition by the cash flow.
 And also, (inaudible) InvenSense initially received approval from the shareholders' meeting, as well as from the countries in question, and we do believe that we should be able to close the acquisition in the second quarter, in March 2018.
 Please turn to page 3. We believe that there are three major aspects behind this acquisition. The first objective is we'd like to become the technology leader, global net player, particularly in the sensor solution domain.
 InvenSense is, of course, is an inertial sensor company, and by this acquisition, we should be able to extend our capabilities in the non-optical sensors. And also the [modern] sensors is going to be a part of the sensor fusion; this is going to become possible for us. And also, we should be able to actually meet with the wants and needs of high performance coming from the customers, for example multi-function and small and [concise] functionalities can be delivered by us to our customers.
 And furthermore, the commission of the sensors and the software, the so-called sensor solutions and others, can be actually offered to other customers now with higher values.
 The second goal behind this acquisition is the acquisition of the inertial sensor technology and software technology. This inertial sensor domain is expected to become the largest in the non-optical, covering AR and VR, and automotive, as well as industrial equipment. And so there is going to be heightened needs in this area, and we do believe that there is going to be then high growth opportunities.
 By acquiring this global player, InvenSense, we should be able to actually make sure that we can enjoy high growth as time goes on. And also, InvenSense has invented software and we should be able to actually expect to receive a good contribution coming from this acquired company in terms of higher value solutions to be offered.
 The third goal behind this acquisition is having to do with the synergy effect by combining our technologies and channels, as well as technology coming from InvenSense.
 In January, we announced and also established RF360 collaboration with Qualcomm, and actually out of these activities, we should be able to [encourage] then our capabilities in ICT and IoT domains. Of course, we have accumulated channel know-how, and also InvenSense, on the products and technologies, by putting them together we should be able to actually put a lot more (inaudible) on the automotive, as well as incentive on the industrial equipment opportunities going forward.
 And finally, sensor fusion and software to be a part of the solution development we would like to work on, we should be able to actually get higher values out of this process and out of this merger.
 Please refer to page 4. We [would like to actually] -- we have a three year mid-term plan by the end of March 2018. We have three major areas; automotive; ICT; and also industrial equipment and energy. So they are the three most important areas for us to grow.
 And throughout (inaudible) [three domains] and again, we will actually gain more business opportunities in the IoT area, so sensor actuators and energy units, and also next-generation electronic components, all defined as the strategic growth in products.
 This acquisition I am explaining to you actually is going to help us to grow in the sensor actuator area and we should be able to actually increase our competiveness in IoT. I do believe that this acquisition is going to give us more competitiveness as time goes on, in terms of business opportunities.
 Please turn to page 5. This is trying to explain the set of core technologies, now we do believe are now going to be quite important.
 In the sensor business, of course, it's (inaudible) to meet with expectations of customers, for example materials, and for example magnetic, and also magnetic sensors and the inertial sensors are to be combined.
 On top of that, on processing (inaudible) and all software and also probably the packaging can be created into the module and that is going to give us great values. The InvenSense that we're going to now acquire, of course, has lots of values in the inertial sensors and the pressure sensors and also the sensor devices.
 And also, they have innovative technologies and developed their own software and algorithm. At the same time, TDK, of course, has the magnetic sensors microphone in the sensor technologies. And also, we have sales hub and other packaging module technologies.
 As shown in here, by buying InvenSense we should be able to extend our product portfolio, and also, we should be able to actually have the complete end-to-end in coverage and starting with the materials. I think that is going to result in our capabilities to offer the higher values to our customers.
 Next, page 6 please. As I have explained this point earlier, the inertial sensors actually is expected to grow in the biggest way in the non-optical sensor segment. This shows by segmentation and the five-year opportunities. And inertial sensors actually is shown in the dark blue area in the bottom.
 Starting from 2016, for five years to come, as you see, it is going to have the biggest market opportunities in terms of size. In inertial sensors, it is having broader applications, and also on a customer basis, I do believe that this is going to become quite important essential the core technology for us to have.
 Having said that, of course, we have a long history working on temperature sensors and the pressure sensors, and we have EPCOS and also we have magnetic sensors and Micronas. And also, inertial sensors actually in electronics, and we have grown through the process of acquiring ideas and companies and technologies in trying to extend our technology portfolio.
 And this time, through this acquisition I'm explaining to you, we should be able to actually address the issues in the field of the inertial sensor technologies and the domains, and also, we should be able to actually have better capabilities to offer the high-end values.
 And us, TDK and InvenSense, actually by combining these together, we should be able to actually promote our best efforts in terms of development and sales and distribution.
 Please turn to page 7. So I would like to introduce the company InvenSense.
 InvenSense, along with the inertial sensors, has developed many sensors, including the pressure microphone and also the ultrasonic sensors. And is a fabless maker development and also the production and all sales. And also, they are able to have information technology with regard to the software sensors.
 It was established in June 2003. Headquarters in San Jose, United States; and listed in New York Stock Exchange market in 2011. And the number of employees as of end of October is 675. And in the past decade, it has grown gradually, and the recent sales amount is $420 million.
 As you can see in the pie chart on the right-hand side, looking at the regional breakdown, the 50% (sic - see slide 7, "45%") is from the United States, and the rest is from China, South Korea, Taiwan, Japan and Asia. And looking at the application breakdown, 64% for the smartphone and the tablet; and 16% for IoT and others; and also the remaining is for the so-called optical image stabilization, is 20%.
 Please turn to page 8. InvenSense has developed the world's first six-axis and nine-axis sensors and has been a global player in the motion sensor market, and it has various applications and also provides its existence in the wearable and also the gaming industries for the consumer market.
 It has produced in this area more than 2 billion inertia sensors, and for the six-axis area, it exceeds 60%. And also, in the automobile industry, including the ADAS, has provided the smallest six-axis sensors in order to develop its customer base.
 So InvenSense has a [regional] seamless and also the MEMS production process, and also is developing high-performance devices.
 Please turn to page 9. As you can see, InvenSense has provided the world's first OIS, which is the optical image stabilization for the consumers. In 2010, it has developed the world's first six-axis; in 2013, provided the world's first nine-axis sensors.
 In recent years, it has provided the AR application required high-technology inertia sensors, like Pokemon GO. Therefore, the InvenSense six-axis is providing its best stability and also the sensitivity and the responsiveness, and has provided a great impact on the consumer and also the user experience.
 As I have said, that they are able to develop the software and algorithm in-house and, therefore, they're able to provide the high value-added solutions. For example, electronic image stabilization is able to reduce so-called camera shock during taking the pictures. Therefore, this high functional motion sensor provides the appropriate optical image stabilization in order to reduce the noise of the movies.
 Also InvenSense IPL, so-called the InvenSense Positioning Library, is providing the GPS and is also able to provide the high-quality positioning technology. Therefore, through their latest software, they're able to provide the sensor solution.
 Please turn to page 10. I would like to explain about the synergy effects through our acquisition. In the areas of ICT and IoT, as we have announced, the joint venture with Qualcomm that we are able to establish RF360 and also, utilizing the technology of Qualcomm, we are able to express our synergy impacts.
 Therefore, we are able to provide the passive components, the batteries, contactless power transfer, sensor, MEMS, and also the next-generation mobile. Also, we are able to have a technological cooperation in the automobile industry.
 Therefore, we are able to strengthen the presence of InvenSense in ICT and also the IoT, for example, in the smartphone zone, the RAR, wearable, home automation and automobile industry, as well as the industry equipment.
 Page 11 please. Also, we are expecting to have a further synergy effect in automobile industry. TDK has provided the EVs, DCCs, DC capacitors and also the condensers and the current, and also we are able to provide the automobile sensors. As shown in the graph, that we are able to have a triple in comparison to the end of 2009.
 Also, we are able to exercise the customer platform of OEM and Tier 1 customers. And also, by providing the planning and development know-how of automobile to InvenSense, we expect that we are able to expand our sensor business for the automobile industry. Also, in the ADAS area, we believe there is a huge growth in this area. Therefore, there is an expectation that there will be a strong demand for the sensor fusion.
 Also, the numbers of sensors for the ADAS for the automobile industry will increase. Therefore, we expect to have a further synergy impact through the share acquisition.
 Page 12 please. As you can see, through the implementation of sensor fusion and also the sensor solution, we are able to exercise the synergy impact. Our Company, and also InvenSense, are able to have the sensor technology. Therefore, by combining our technology with that of InvenSense, we are able to provide the various sensor fusion products.
 Also, with that information, and also by processing those information and also by controlling those information, we are able to provide a higher value-added sensor solution.
 For example, for the nine-axis, by combining with our products, we are able to have the sensor fusion base and also we are able to combine with the navigation software of IPL of InvenSense. Also, by providing the mapping information, we are able to have an indoor navigation technology.
 At the same time, sensor fusion with the next-generation wireless technology by RF360, we are able to provide the integrated system in the IoT arena.
 Based on that, we would like to have further expansion of our sensor business; page 13 please.
 As you can see in this quadrant picture, and this is for the vertical axis industry, and also in the horizontal axis is the sensor technology. This shows the mapping of the sensor businesses.
 The blue part shows the TDK's focus sensor business. For example, by acquiring Micronas, we are able to provide the sensors for automobile and for the industry uses. However, after the acquisition of InvenSense, the red part shows the customer platform that we are able to expand, that we are able to provide the sensor products and also by providing and acquiring the technology from the InvenSense, we are able to expand our business platform in ICT.
 As you can see in the arrow for number one, with our customer platform and also with the collaboration of Qualcomm, the InvenSense business platform will expand in the ICT areas, as well as the inertial sensors for automobile and for the industry uses.
 In addition, as you can see in the number two arrow, by providing the sensor fusion and sensor solutions, we are able to expand our business in the sensor business because, at the beginning, of course, we do have a strength in the magnetic sensors for the automobile industries. However, the InvenSense holds the nine-axis sensor. Therefore, by combining with nine-axis sensor, we are able to provide the high-spec products and therefore, we are able to provide further business in the magnetic sensors in the area of ICT.
 Therefore, our sales expectation for the sensor business in 2021 will be 4 times larger, which is JPY200 billion, with the strong partner of InvenSense that we would like to create our position as a global player in sensor market and also, we would like to expand further our business.
 Lastly, please turn to page 14. This is our forecast for the sensor business. As I have said, through the acquisition, we are able to cover the technology and also the product in the non-optical sensor business.
 From the middle of fourth quarter, we are going to curve out the major business for the high frequency component business. However, with the sensor business will become our pillar, and within four years, we would like to have a sales of JPY200 billion.
 That concludes my explanation. Thank you very much.
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
Editor   [2]
--------------------------------------------------------------------------------
 Statements in English on this transcript were spoken by an interpreter present on the live call. The interpreter was provided by the Company sponsoring this Event.
]]></Body>
  </EventStory>
  <eventTitle><![CDATA[TDK Corp to Acquire InvenSense Inc Conference Call]]></eventTitle>
  <city>Tokyo</city>
  <companyName>TDK Corp</companyName>
  <companyTicker>6762.T</companyTicker>
  <startDate>21-Dec-16 10:59am GMT</startDate>
</Event>